-DOCSTART- -X- O O

350 CD - O
, , - O
Wellesley NNP - I-LOC
, , - O
Massachusetts NNP - I-LOC
02481 CD - O
doing VBG - O
business NN - O
as IN - O
" NN - O
Silicon NNP - I-LOC
Valley NNP - I-LOC
East NNP - I-LOC
" NNP - O
and CC - O
AKAMAI NNP - I-ORG
TECHNOLOGIES NNPS - I-ORG
, , - O
INC NNP - O
. . - O
(" : - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
"), , - O
whose WP$ - O
address NN - O
is VBZ - O
201 CD - I-LOC
Broadway NNP - I-LOC
, , - O
4th JJ - O
Floor NNP - O
, , - O
Cambridge NNP - I-LOC
, , - O
Massachusetts NNP - I-LOC
02139 CD - O
provides VBZ - O
the DT - O
terms NNS - O
on IN - O
which WDT - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
lend VB - O
to TO - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
repay VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

The DT - O
parties NNS - O
agree VBP - O
as RB - O
follows VBZ - O
: : - O

The DT - O
term NN - O
" : - O
financial JJ - O
statements NNS - O
" : - O
includes NNS - O
the DT - O
notes NNS - O
and CC - O
schedules NNS - O
. . - O

The DT - O
terms NNS - O
" : - O
including VBG - O
" NN - O
and CC - O
" CD - O
includes NNS - O
" : - O
always RB - O
mean JJ - O
" NN - O
including VBG - O
( NN - O
or CC - O
includes VBZ - O
) CD - O
without IN - O
limitation NN - O
," : - O
in IN - O
this DT - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Document NNP - O
. . - O

2 LS - O
LOAN NNP - O
AND NNP - O
TERMS NNP - O
OF NNP - O
PAYMENT NNP - O

2 LS - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
CREDIT NN - O
EXTENSIONS NNS - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
pay VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
the DT - O
unpaid NN - O
principal NN - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
all DT - O
Credit NNP - O
Extensions NNPS - O
and CC - O
interest NN - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
unpaid NN - O
principal NN - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Credit NNP - O
Extensions NNP - O
. . - O

2 LS - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
EQUIPMENT NNP - O
FACILITY NNP - O
. . - O

Subject JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
terms NNS - O
and CC - O
conditions NNS - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
, , - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
agrees VBZ - O
to TO - O
lend VB - O
to TO - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
, , - O
from IN - O
time NN - O
to TO - O
time VB - O
prior RB - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Commitment NNP - O
Termination NNP - O
Date NNP - O
, , - O
equipment NN - O
advances NNS - O
( VBP - O
each DT - O
an DT - O
" NN - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
" NNP - O
and CC - O
collectively RB - O
the DT - O
" NN - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advances NNP - O
"). NNP - O

If IN - O
prepaid VBN - O
, , - O
the DT - O
principal JJ - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advances NNP - O
may MD - O
not RB - O
be VB - O
re RB - O
- : - O
borrowed VBN - O
. . - O

Each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
shall MD - O
be VB - O
considered VBN - O
a DT - O
promissory NN - O
note NN - O
evidencing VBG - O
the DT - O
amounts NNS - O
due JJ - O
hereunder NN - O
for IN - O
all DT - O
purposes NNS - O
. . - O

( NN - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
To TO - O
obtain VB - O
an DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
deliver VB - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
a DT - O
completed VBN - O
supplement NN - O
in IN - O
substantially RB - O
the DT - O
form NN - O
attached VBD - O
(" CD - O
Loan NNP - O
Supplement NNP - O
"), , - O
together RB - O
with IN - O
invoices NNS - O
and CC - O
such JJ - O
additional JJ - O
information NN - O
as IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
may MD - O
request VB - O
at IN - O
least JJS - O
five CD - O
( CD - O
5 CD - O
) CD - O
Business NNP - O
Days NNP - O
before IN - O
the DT - O
proposed VBN - O
funding NN - O
date NN - O
( : - O
the DT - O
" NN - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
"). NNP - O

On IN - O
each DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
, , - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
specify VB - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Supplement NNP - O
for IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
Basic NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Factor NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
Payment NNP - O
Dates NNP - O
, , - O
and CC - O
a DT - O
table JJ - O
of IN - O
Stipulated NNP - O
Loan NNP - O
Values NNP - O
, , - O
together RB - O
with IN - O
a DT - O
UCC NNP - O
Financing NNP - O
Statement NNP - O
covering VBG - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
described VBD - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Supplement NNP - O
. . - O

If IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
satisfies NNS - O
the DT - O
conditions NNS - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
specified VBD - O
from IN - O
time NN - O
to TO - O
time VB - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
, , - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
disburse VB - O
such PDT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
by IN - O
internal JJ - O
transfer NN - O
to TO - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
deposit NN - O
account NN - O
with IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

4 LS - O
< `` - O
PAGE NN - O
> : - O
5 CD - O
2 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
INTEREST NN - O
RATE NNP - O
, , - O
PAYMENTS NNP - O
. . - O

( NN - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
Principal NNP - O
and CC - O
Interest NNP - O
Payments NNP - O
On NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
Dates NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
make VB - O
payments NNS - O
monthly RB - O
in IN - O
advance NN - O
of IN - O
principal NN - O
and CC - O
accrued VBD - O
interest NN - O
for IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
( NNP - O
collectively RB - O
, , - O
" : - O
Scheduled NNP - O
Payments NNP - O
"), , - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
first JJ - O
Business NN - O
Day NNP - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
month NN - O
following VBG - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
( NNP - O
or CC - O
commencing VBG - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
if IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
first JJ - O
Business NN - O
Day NNP - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
month NN - O
) : - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
and CC - O
continuing VBG - O
thereafter NN - O
during IN - O
the DT - O
Repayment NNP - O
Period NNP - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
first JJ - O
Business NN - O
Day NNP - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
calendar NN - O
month NN - O
( : - O
each DT - O
a DT - O
" NN - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
"), , - O
in IN - O
an DT - O
amount NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Factor NNP - O
multiplied VBD - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Amount NNP - O
for IN - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
as IN - O
of IN - O
such JJ - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
. . - O

All DT - O
unpaid VBD - O
principal JJ - O
and CC - O
accrued VBN - O
interest NN - O
is VBZ - O
due JJ - O
and CC - O
payable JJ - O
in IN - O
full JJ - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
last JJ - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
. . - O

( NN - O
b NN - O
) : - O
Interest NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
pay VB - O
interest NN - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
unpaid NN - O
principal NN - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
first JJ - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
after IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
of IN - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
until IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
has VBZ - O
been VBN - O
paid VBN - O
in IN - O
full JJ - O
, , - O
at IN - O
the DT - O
per NN - O
annum NN - O
rate NN - O
of IN - O
interest NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Basic NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
determined VBD - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
as IN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
for IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
in IN - O
accordance NN - O
with IN - O
the DT - O
definition NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Basic NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
Basic NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
, , - O
as IN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
per NN - O
annum NN - O
rate NN - O
of IN - O
interest NN - O
( : - O
based VBN - O
on IN - O
a DT - O
year NN - O
of IN - O
360 CD - O
days NNS - O
) : - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
sum NN - O
of IN - O
( NNP - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
the DT - O
U NNP - O
. . - O
S NNP - O
. . - O
Treasury NNP - O
note NN - O
yield NN - O
to TO - O
maturity NN - O
for IN - O
a DT - O
term NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Treasury NNP - O
Note NNP - O
Maturity NNP - O
as IN - O
quoted VBN - O
in IN - O
The DT - I-ORG
Wall NNP - I-ORG
Street NNP - I-ORG
Journal NNP - I-ORG
on IN - O
the DT - O
day NN - O
the DT - O
applicable JJ - O
Loan NNP - O
Terms NNP - O
Schedule NNP - O
is VBZ - O
prepared VBN - O
, , - O
plus CC - O
( : - O
b NN - O
) : - O
the DT - O
applicable JJ - O
Loan NNP - O
Margin NNP - O
for IN - O
the DT - O
type NN - O
of IN - O
Eligible NNP - O
Equipment NNP - O
being VBG - O
financed VBN - O
. . - O

The DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Margin NNP - O
is VBZ - O
275 CD - O
basis NN - O
points NNS - O
. . - O

The DT - O
Treasury NNP - O
Note NNP - O
Maturity NNP - O
is VBZ - O
36 CD - O
months NNS - O
. . - O

( NN - O
c NN - O
) : - O
Interim NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
. . - O

In IN - O
addition NN - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Scheduled NNP - O
Payments NNP - O
, , - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
for IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
( NNP - O
unless IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
first JJ - O
Business NN - O
Day NNP - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
month NN - O
) : - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
shall MD - O
pay VB - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
, , - O
on IN - O
behalf NN - O
of IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
, , - O
an DT - O
amount NN - O
( : - O
the DT - O
" NN - O
Interim NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
") NNP - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
initial JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
multiplied VBD - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
product NN - O
of IN - O
( NNP - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
the DT - O
quotient NN - O
derived VBD - O
from IN - O
dividing VBG - O
the DT - O
initial JJ - O
Loan NNP - O
Factor NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
multiplied VBD - O
by IN - O
30 CD - O
, , - O
and CC - O
( : - O
ii NN - O
) : - O
the DT - O
number NN - O
of IN - O
days NNS - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
Funding NNP - O
Date NNP - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
Loan NNP - O
until IN - O
the DT - O
first JJ - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
. . - O

( NN - O
d VBD - O
) CD - O
Final NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
. . - O

On IN - O
the DT - O
Maturity NNP - O
Date NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
pay VB - O
, , - O
in IN - O
addition NN - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
unpaid NN - O
principal NN - O
and CC - O
accrued VBD - O
interest NN - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
other JJ - O
amounts NNS - O
due JJ - O
on IN - O
such JJ - O
date NN - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
an DT - O
amount NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Final NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
Final NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
a DT - O
payment NN - O
( : - O
in IN - O
addition NN - O
to TO - O
and CC - O
not RB - O
a DT - O
substitution NN - O
for IN - O
the DT - O
regular JJ - O
monthly JJ - O
payments NNS - O
of IN - O
principal JJ - O
plus CC - O
accrued VBN - O
interest NN - O
) : - O
due JJ - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
maturity NN - O
date NN - O
for IN - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Amount NNP - O
for IN - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
at IN - O
such JJ - O
time NN - O
multiplied VBN - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
Final NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
Percentage NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
Final NNP - O
Payment NNP - O
Percentage NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
, , - O
for IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
7 CD - O
. . - O
5 CD - O
%. : - O

" NN - O
Loan NNP - O
Amount NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
original JJ - O
principal NN - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
less JJR - O
the DT - O
aggregate NN - O
of IN - O
all DT - O
Prepayment NNP - O
Amounts NNP - O
relating VBG - O
to TO - O
payments NNS - O
of IN - O
such JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
prior RB - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
dates NNS - O
. . - O

( NN - O
e NN - O
) : - O
Prepayment NNP - O
Upon NNP - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
. . - O

If IN - O
any DT - O
Financed NNP - O
Equipment NNP - O
is VBZ - O
subject JJ - O
to TO - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
and CC - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
is VBZ - O
required VBN - O
to TO - O
or CC - O
elects NNS - O
to TO - O
prepay VB - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O

If IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advances NNP - O
are VBP - O
accelerated VBN - O
following VBG - O
the DT - O
occurrence NN - O
of IN - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
or CC - O
otherwise RB - O
( : - O
other JJ - O
than IN - O
following VBG - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
), , - O
then RB - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
immediately RB - O
pay VB - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
( NNP - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
all DT - O
unpaid VBN - O
Scheduled NNP - O
Payments NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
due JJ - O
prior NN - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
prepayment NN - O
, , - O
( : - O
ii NN - O
) : - O
the DT - O
Stipulated NNP - O
Loss NNP - O
Value NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
, , - O
and CC - O
( : - O
iii NN - O
) : - O
all DT - O
other JJ - O
sums NNS - O
, , - O
if IN - O
any DT - O
, , - O
that IN - O
shall MD - O
have VB - O
become VBN - O
due JJ - O
and CC - O
payable JJ - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
any DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
. . - O

( NN - O
g NN - O
) : - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
repay VB - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advances NNP - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
terms NNS - O
provided VBN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Supplement NNP - O
. . - O

Any DT - O
amounts NNS - O
outstanding JJ - O
during IN - O
the DT - O
continuance NN - O
of IN - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
shall MD - O
bear VB - O
interest NN - O
at IN - O
a DT - O
per NN - O
annum NN - O
rate NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Basic NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
plus VBZ - O
5 CD - O
percent NN - O
. . - O

If IN - O
any DT - O
change NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
law NN - O
increases VBZ - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
expenses NNS - O
or CC - O
decreases NNS - O
its PRP$ - O
return NN - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advances NNP - O
, , - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
pay VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
upon IN - O
request NN - O
the DT - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
such JJ - O
increase NN - O
or CC - O
decrease VB - O
. . - O

( NN - O
h NN - O
) : - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
may MD - O
debit VB - O
any DT - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
deposit NN - O
accounts NNS - O
including VBG - O
Account NNP - O
Number NNP - O
_____________ NNP - O
for IN - O
principal JJ - O
and CC - O
interest NN - O
payments NNS - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
amounts NNS - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
owes NNS - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
notify VB - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
when WRB - O
it PRP - O
debits VBZ - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
accounts NNS - O
. . - O

These DT - O
debits NNS - O
are VBP - O
not RB - O
a DT - O
set NN - O
- : - O
off IN - O
. . - O

Payments NNS - O
received VBD - O
after IN - O
12 CD - O
: : - O
00 CD - O
noon NN - O
Eastern NNP - I-LOC
time NN - O
are VBP - O
considered VBN - O
received VBN - O
at IN - O
the DT - O
opening VBG - O
of IN - O
business NN - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
next JJ - O
Business NN - O
Day NNP - O
. . - O

When WRB - O
a DT - O
payment NN - O
is VBZ - O
due JJ - O
on IN - O
a DT - O
day NN - O
that WDT - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
a DT - O
Business NNP - O
Day NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
payment NN - O
is VBZ - O
due JJ - O
the DT - O
next JJ - O
Business NN - O
Day NNP - O
and CC - O
additional JJ - O
fees NNS - O
or CC - O
interest NN - O
accrue NN - O
. . - O

2 LS - O
. . - O
3 CD - O
FEES NNS - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
pay VB - O
: : - O

( NN - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
Expenses NNP - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
obligations NNS - O
to TO - O
make VB - O
each DT - O
Credit NNP - O
Extension NNP - O
, , - O
including VBG - O
the DT - O
initial JJ - O
Credit NN - O
Extension NN - O
, , - O
is VBZ - O
subject JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
following VBG - O
: : - O

( NN - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
timely RB - O
receipt JJ - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
Payment NNP - O
/ NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
Form NNP - O
, , - O
together RB - O
with IN - O
an DT - O
invoice NN - O
for IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
purchased VBD - O
; : - O
and CC - O

( NN - O
b NN - O
) : - O
the DT - O
representations NNS - O
and CC - O
warranties NNS - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
5 CD - O
must MD - O
be VB - O
materially RB - O
true JJ - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Payment NNP - O
/ NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
Form NNP - O
and CC - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
effective JJ - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
Credit NNP - O
Extension NNP - O
and CC - O
no DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
may MD - O
have VB - O
occurred VBN - O
and CC - O
be VB - O
continuing VBG - O
, , - O
or CC - O
result VB - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
Credit NNP - O
Extension NNP - O
. . - O

Each DT - O
Credit NN - O
Extension NN - O
is VBZ - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
representation NN - O
and CC - O
warranty NN - O
on IN - O
that DT - O
date NN - O
that IN - O
the DT - O
representations NNS - O
and CC - O
warranties NNS - O
of IN - O
Section NN - O
5 CD - O
remain NN - O
true JJ - O
. . - O

6 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NNP - O
> NNP - O
7 CD - O
4 CD - O
CREATION NNP - O
OF NNP - O
SECURITY NNP - O
INTEREST NNP - O

4 LS - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
GRANT NNP - O
OF NNP - O
SECURITY NNP - O
INTEREST NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
grants NNS - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
a DT - O
continuing VBG - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
in IN - O
all DT - O
presently RB - O
existing VBG - O
and CC - O
later JJ - O
acquired VBN - O
Collateral NNP - O
to TO - O
secure VB - O
all DT - O
Obligations NNS - O
and CC - O
performance NN - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
of IN - O
Borrowers NNPS - O
duties NNS - O
under IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
. . - O

Any DT - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
will MD - O
be VB - O
a DT - O
first JJ - O
priority NN - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
represents VBZ - O
and CC - O
warrants NNS - O
as IN - O
follows NNS - O
: : - O

5 LS - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
DUE NNP - O
ORGANIZATION NNP - O
AND NNP - O
AUTHORIZATION NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
each DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
is VBZ - O
duly RB - O
existing VBG - O
and CC - O
in IN - O
good JJ - O
standing NN - O
in IN - O
its PRP$ - O
state NN - O
of IN - O
formation NN - O
and CC - O
qualified VBD - O
and CC - O
licensed VBN - O
to TO - O
do VB - O
business NN - O
in IN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
in IN - O
good JJ - O
standing NN - O
in IN - O
, , - O
any DT - O
state NN - O
in IN - O
which WDT - O
the DT - O
conduct NN - O
of IN - O
its PRP$ - O
business NN - O
or CC - O
its PRP$ - O
ownership NN - O
of IN - O
property NN - O
requires VBZ - O
that IN - O
it PRP - O
be VB - O
qualified VBN - O
. . - O

The DT - O
execution NN - O
, , - O
delivery NN - O
and CC - O
performance NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
have VBP - O
been VBN - O
duly RB - O
authorized VBN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
do VB - O
not RB - O
conflict VB - O
with IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
formation NN - O
documents NNS - O
, , - O
nor CC - O
constitute NN - O
an DT - O
event NN - O
of IN - O
default NN - O
under IN - O
any DT - O
material NN - O
agreement NN - O
by IN - O
which WDT - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
is VBZ - O
bound VBN - O
. . - O

5 LS - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
COLLATERAL NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
has VBZ - O
good JJ - O
title NN - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
, , - O
free JJ - O
from IN - O
liens NNS - O
. . - O

5 LS - O
. . - O
3 CD - O
LITIGATION NN - O
. . - O

Except IN - O
as IN - O
shown NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Schedule NNP - O
, , - O
there EX - O
are VBP - O
no DT - O
actions NNS - O
or CC - O
proceedings NNS - O
pending VBG - O
or CC - O
, , - O
to TO - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
knowledge NN - O
, , - O
threatened VBN - O
by IN - O
or CC - O
against IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
or CC - O
any DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
in IN - O
which WDT - O
an DT - O
adverse NN - O
decision NN - O
could MD - O
cause VB - O
a DT - O
Material JJ - O
Adverse NNP - O
Change NNP - O
. . - O

5 LS - O
. . - O
4 CD - O
NO DT - O
MATERIAL NN - O
ADVERSE NNP - O
CHANGE NNP - O
IN NNP - O
FINANCIAL NNP - O
STATEMENTS NNP - O
. . - O

All DT - O
consolidated VBN - O
financial JJ - O
statements NNS - O
for IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
, , - O
and CC - O
any DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
, , - O
delivered VBD - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
fairly RB - O
present JJ - O
in IN - O
all DT - O
material NN - O
respects NNS - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
consolidated VBD - O
financial JJ - O
condition NN - O
and CC - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' '' - O
s VBZ - O
consolidated VBN - O
results NNS - O
of IN - O
operations NNS - O
. . - O

There EX - O
has VBZ - O
not RB - O
been VBN - O
any DT - O
material NN - O
deterioration NN - O
in IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
consolidated VBD - O
financial JJ - O
condition NN - O
since IN - O
the DT - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
most RBS - O
recent JJ - O
financial JJ - O
statements NNS - O
submitted VBN - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

5 LS - O
. . - O
5 CD - O
SOLVENCY NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
engaged VBN - O
as IN - O
one CD - O
of IN - O
its PRP$ - O
important JJ - O
activities NNS - O
in IN - O
extending VBG - O
credit NN - O
for IN - O
margin NN - O
stock NN - O
( : - O
under IN - O
Regulations NNS - O
G NNP - O
, , - O
T NNP - O
and CC - O
U NNP - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Federal NNP - I-ORG
Reserve NNP - I-ORG
Board NNP - I-ORG
of IN - I-ORG
Governors NNP - I-ORG
). NNP - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
has VBZ - O
not RB - O
violated VBN - O

7 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NNP - O
> NNP - O
8 CD - O
any DT - O
laws NNS - O
, , - O
ordinances NNS - O
or CC - O
rules NNS - O
, , - O
the DT - O
violation NN - O
of IN - O
which WDT - O
could MD - O
cause VB - O
a DT - O
Material JJ - O
Adverse NNP - O
Change NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
each DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
has VBZ - O
timely RB - O
filed VBN - O
all DT - O
required VBN - O
tax NN - O
returns NNS - O
and CC - O
paid VBD - O
, , - O
or CC - O
made VBN - O
adequate JJ - O
provision NN - O
to TO - O
pay VB - O
, , - O
all DT - O
taxes NNS - O
, , - O
except IN - O
those DT - O
being VBG - O
contested VBN - O
in IN - O
good JJ - O
faith NN - O
with IN - O
adequate JJ - O
reserves NNS - O
under IN - O
GAAP NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
each DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
has VBZ - O
obtained VBN - O
all DT - O
consents NNS - O
, , - O
approvals NNS - O
and CC - O
authorizations NNS - O
of IN - O
, , - O
made VBN - O
all DT - O
declarations NNS - O
or CC - O
filings NNS - O
with IN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
given VBN - O
all DT - O
notices NNS - O
to TO - O
, , - O
all DT - O
government NN - O
authorities NNS - O
that WDT - O
are VBP - O
necessary JJ - O
to TO - O
continue VB - O
its PRP$ - O
business NN - O
as IN - O
currently RB - O
conducted VBN - O
. . - O

5 LS - O
. . - O
7 CD - O
FULL NNP - O
DISCLOSURE NNP - O
. . - O

6 CD - O
AFFIRMATIVE CD - O
COVENANTS NNS - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
do VB - O
all PDT - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
following JJ - O
: : - O

6 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
GOVERNMENT NN - O
COMPLIANCE NN - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
maintain VB - O
its PRP$ - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
Subsidiaries NNPS - O
' POS - O
legal JJ - O
existence NN - O
and CC - O
good JJ - O
standing NN - O
in IN - O
its PRP$ - O
jurisdiction NN - O
of IN - O
formation NN - O
and CC - O
maintain VB - O
qualification NN - O
in IN - O
each DT - O
jurisdiction NN - O
in IN - O
which WDT - O
the DT - O
failure NN - O
to TO - O
so RB - O
qualify VB - O
could MD - O
have VB - O
a DT - O
material NN - O
adverse NN - O
effect NN - O
on IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
business NN - O
or CC - O
operations NNS - O
. . - O

6 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
FINANCIAL NNP - O
STATEMENTS NNP - O
, , - O
REPORTS VBZ - O
. . - O

( NN - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
deliver VB - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
: : - O
( : - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
as IN - O
soon RB - O
as IN - O
available JJ - O
, , - O
but CC - O
not RB - O
later JJ - O
than IN - O
30 CD - O
days NNS - O
after IN - O
the DT - O
last JJ - O
day NN - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
month NN - O
, , - O
a DT - O
company NN - O
prepared VBN - O
consolidated VBD - O
balance NN - O
sheet NN - O
and CC - O
income NN - O
statement NN - O
covering VBG - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
consolidated VBD - O
operations NNS - O
during IN - O
the DT - O
period NN - O
, , - O
in IN - O
a DT - O
form NN - O
and CC - O
certified VBD - O
by IN - O
a DT - O
Responsible NNP - O
Officer NNP - O
acceptable JJ - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
; : - O
( NNP - O
ii NN - O
) : - O
as IN - O
soon RB - O
as IN - O
available JJ - O
, , - O
but CC - O
not RB - O
later JJ - O
than IN - O
90 CD - O
days NNS - O
after IN - O
the DT - O
last JJ - O
day NN - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
fiscal JJ - O
year NN - O
, , - O
audited VBN - O
consolidated VBN - O
financial JJ - O
statements NNS - O
prepared VBN - O
under IN - O
GAAP NNP - O
, , - O
consistently RB - O
applied VBD - O
, , - O
together RB - O
with IN - O
an DT - O
unqualified JJ - O
opinion NN - O
on IN - O
the DT - O
financial JJ - O
statements NNS - O
from IN - O
Pricewaterhouse NNP - O
Coopers NNP - O
, , - O
LLP NNP - O
or CC - O
another DT - O
independent JJ - O
certified JJ - O
public JJ - O
accounting NN - O
firm NN - O
reasonable JJ - O
acceptable JJ - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
; : - O
( NNP - O
iii NN - O
) : - O
a DT - O
prompt NN - O
report NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
legal JJ - O
actions NNS - O
pending VBG - O
or CC - O
threatened VBN - O
against IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
or CC - O
any DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
that IN - O
could MD - O
result VB - O
in IN - O
damages NNS - O
or CC - O
costs NNS - O
to TO - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
or CC - O
any DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
of IN - O
$ $ - O
100 CD - O
, , - O
000 CD - O
or CC - O
more JJR - O
; : - O
and CC - O
( : - O
iv NN - O
) : - O
budgets NNS - O
, , - O
sales NNS - O
projections NNS - O
, , - O
operating VBG - O
plans NNS - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
financial JJ - O
information NN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
requests NNS - O
. . - O

6 CD - O
. . - O
3 CD - O
TAXES NNS - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
make VB - O
, , - O
and CC - O
cause VB - O
each DT - O
Subsidiary NNP - O
to TO - O
make VB - O
, , - O
timely RB - O
payment NN - O
of IN - O
all DT - O
material NN - O
federal JJ - O
, , - O
state NN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
local JJ - O
taxes NNS - O
or CC - O
assessments NNS - O
and CC - O
will MD - O
deliver VB - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
, , - O
on IN - O
demand NN - O
, , - O
appropriate JJ - O
certificates NNS - O
attesting VBG - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
payment NN - O
. . - O

8 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NN - O
> : - O
9 CD - O
6 CD - O
. . - O
4 CD - O
INSURANCE NN - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
keep VB - O
its PRP$ - O
business NN - O
and CC - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
insured VBD - O
for IN - O
risks NNS - O
and CC - O
in IN - O
amounts NNS - O
, , - O
as IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
requests NNS - O
. . - O

Insurance NN - O
policies NNS - O
will MD - O
be VB - O
in IN - O
a DT - O
form NN - O
, , - O
with IN - O
companies NNS - O
, , - O
and CC - O
in IN - O
amounts NNS - O
that WDT - O
are VBP - O
satisfactory JJ - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

All DT - O
property NN - O
policies NNS - O
will MD - O
have VB - O
a DT - O
lender NN - I-PER
' '' - O
s NNS - O
loss NN - O
payable JJ - O
endorsement NN - O
showing VBG - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
as IN - O
an DT - O
additional JJ - O
loss NN - O
payee NN - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
liability NN - O
policies NNS - O
will MD - O
show VB - O
the DT - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
as IN - O
an DT - O
additional JJ - O
insured VBN - O
and CC - O
provide VB - O
that IN - O
the DT - O
insurer NN - O
must MD - O
give VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
at IN - O
least JJS - O
20 CD - O
days NNS - O
notice NN - O
before IN - O
canceling VBG - O
its PRP$ - O
policy NN - O
. . - O

At IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
request NN - O
, , - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
deliver VB - O
certified VBN - O
copies NNS - O
of IN - O
policies NNS - O
and CC - O
evidence NN - O
of IN - O
all DT - O
premium NN - O
payments NNS - O
. . - O

Proceeds NNS - O
payable VBP - O
under IN - O
any DT - O
policy NN - O
will MD - O
, , - O
at IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
option NN - O
, , - O
be VB - O
payable JJ - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
on IN - O
account NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Obligations NNS - O
. . - O

6 CD - O
. . - O
5 CD - O
PRIMARY NNP - O
ACCOUNTS NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
maintain VB - O
its PRP$ - O
primary JJ - O
depository NN - O
and CC - O
operating NN - O
accounts NNS - O
with IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

6 CD - O
. . - O
6 CD - O
FURTHER NNP - O
ASSURANCES NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
execute VB - O
any DT - O
further JJ - O
instruments NNS - O
and CC - O
take VB - O
further JJ - O
action NN - O
as IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
requests NNS - O
to TO - O
perfect VB - O
or CC - O
continue VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
or CC - O
to TO - O
effect VB - O
the DT - O
purposes NNS - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
. . - O

6 CD - O
. . - O
7 CD - O
LOSS NNP - O
; : - O
DESTRUCTION NNP - O
; : - O
OR NNP - O
DAMAGE NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
bear VB - O
the DT - O
risk NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
being VBG - O
lost VBN - O
, , - O
stolen VBN - O
, , - O
destroyed VBN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
damaged VBN - O
. . - O

If IN - O
during IN - O
the DT - O
term NN - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
any DT - O
item NN - O
of IN - O
Financed NNP - O
Equipment NNP - O
is VBZ - O
lost VBN - O
, , - O
stolen VBN - O
, , - O
destroyed VBN - O
, , - O
damaged VBN - O
beyond NN - O
repair NN - O
, , - O
rendered VBD - O
permanently RB - O
unfit JJ - O
for IN - O
use NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
seized VBN - O
by IN - O
a DT - O
governmental JJ - O
authority NN - O
for IN - O
any DT - O
reason NN - O
whatsoever NN - O
for IN - O
a DT - O
period NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
at IN - O
least JJS - O
the DT - O
remainder NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
term NN - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
( NNP - O
an DT - O
" NN - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
"), , - O
then RB - O
in IN - O
each DT - O
case NN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
receive VB - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
proceeds NNS - O
of IN - O
insurance NN - O
maintained VBD - O
pursuant JJ - O
to TO - O
Section NNP - O
6 CD - O
, , - O
from IN - O
any DT - O
award NN - O
paid VBD - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
seizing VBG - O
governmental JJ - O
authority NN - O
or CC - O
, , - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
extent NN - O
not RB - O
received VBN - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
proceeds NNS - O
of IN - O
insurance NN - O
or CC - O
award NN - O
or CC - O
both DT - O
, , - O
from IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
, , - O
on IN - O
or CC - O
before IN - O
the DT - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
next JJ - O
succeeding NN - O
such JJ - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
for IN - O
each DT - O
such JJ - O
item NN - O
of IN - O
Financed NNP - O
Equipment NNP - O
subject NN - O
to TO - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
, , - O
an DT - O
amount NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
sum NN - O
of IN - O
: : - O
( : - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
all DT - O
accrued VBN - O
and CC - O
unpaid VBD - O
Scheduled NNP - O
Payments NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Loan NNP - O
due JJ - O
prior NN - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
next JJ - O
such JJ - O
Payment NNP - O
Date NNP - O
, , - O
( NNP - O
ii NN - O
) : - O
a DT - O
prepayment NN - O
in IN - O
an DT - O
amount NN - O
equal JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Stipulated NNP - O
Loss NNP - O
Value NNP - O
and CC - O
( NNP - O
iii NN - O
) : - O
all DT - O
other JJ - O
sums NNS - O
, , - O
if IN - O
any DT - O
, , - O
that IN - O
shall MD - O
have VB - O
become VBN - O
due JJ - O
and CC - O
payable JJ - O
, , - O
including VBG - O
interest NN - O
at IN - O
the DT - O
Default NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
any DT - O
past JJ - O
due JJ - O
amounts NNS - O
. . - O

On IN - O
the DT - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
receipt NN - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
of IN - O
the DT - O
amount NN - O
specified VBN - O
above IN - O
with IN - O
respect NN - O
to TO - O
each DT - O
such JJ - O
item NN - O
of IN - O
Financed NNP - O
Equipment NNP - O
subject NN - O
to TO - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Loss NNP - O
, , - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
shall MD - O
terminate VB - O
as IN - O
to TO - O
such JJ - O
Financed NNP - O
Equipment NNP - O
. . - O

Any DT - O
proceeds NNS - O
of IN - O
insurance NN - O
maintained VBD - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
pursuant JJ - O
to TO - O
this DT - O
Section NN - O
and CC - O
received VBD - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
be VB - O
paid VBN - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
, , - O
promptly RB - O
upon IN - O
their PRP$ - O
receipt NN - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
. . - O

If IN - O
any DT - O
proceeds NNS - O
of IN - O
insurance NN - O
or CC - O
awards NNS - O
received VBD - O
from IN - O
governmental JJ - O
authorities NNS - O
are VBP - O
in IN - O
excess NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
amount NN - O
owed VBD - O
under IN - O
this DT - O
Section NN - O
, , - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
shall MD - O
promptly RB - O
remit VB - O
to TO - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
the DT - O
amount NN - O
in IN - O
excess NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
amount NN - O
owed VBD - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

7 CD - O
NEGATIVE NNP - O
COVENANTS NNP - O

Change NNP - O
its PRP$ - O
name NN - O
or CC - O
the DT - O
chief NN - O
executive NN - O
office NN - O
or CC - O
principal NN - O
place NN - O
of IN - O
business NN - O
, , - O
move NN - O
or CC - O
dispose NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
interest NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
, , - O
permit NN - O
any DT - O
lien NN - O
or CC - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
to TO - O
attach VB - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
, , - O
or CC - O
enter NN - O
into IN - O
any DT - O
transaction NN - O
outside IN - O
the DT - O
ordinary JJ - O
course NN - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
business NN - O
. . - O

8 CD - O
. . - O
3 CD - O
MATERIAL NNP - O
ADVERSE NNP - O
CHANGE NNP - O
. . - O

If IN - O
there EX - O
( : - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
occurs NNS - O
a DT - O
material NN - O
adverse NN - O
change NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
business NN - O
, , - O
operations NNS - O
, , - O
or CC - O
condition NN - O
( : - O
financial JJ - O
or CC - O
otherwise RB - O
) : - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
, , - O
or CC - O
( : - O
ii NN - O
) : - O
is VBZ - O
a DT - O
material NN - O
impairment NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
prospect NN - O
of IN - O
repayment NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
portion NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Obligations NNS - O
. . - O

8 CD - O
. . - O
4 CD - O
ATTACHMENT NNP - O
. . - O

These DT - O
are VBP - O
not RB - O
Events NNS - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
if IN - O
stayed VBN - O
or CC - O
if IN - O
a DT - O
bond NN - O
is VBZ - O
posted VBN - O
pending VBG - O
contest JJS - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
( NNP - O
but CC - O
no DT - O
Credit NN - O
Extensions NNS - O
will MD - O
be VB - O
made VBN - O
during IN - O
the DT - O
cure NN - O
period NN - O
); : - O

8 CD - O
. . - O
5 CD - O
INSOLVENCY NNP - O
. . - O

8 CD - O
. . - O
7 CD - O
JUDGMENTS NNS - O
. . - O

If IN - O
a DT - O
money NN - O
judgment NN - O
( : - O
s NNS - O
) VBP - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
aggregate NN - O
of IN - O
at IN - O
least JJS - O
$ $ - O
50 CD - O
, , - O
000 CD - O
is VBZ - O
rendered VBN - O
against IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
is VBZ - O
unsatisfied VBN - O
and CC - O
unstayed VBN - O
for IN - O
10 CD - O
days NNS - O
( : - O
but CC - O
no RB - O
Advances NNS - O
will MD - O
be VB - O
made VBN - O
before IN - O
the DT - O
judgment NN - O
is VBZ - O
stayed VBN - O
or CC - O
satisfied VBN - O
); : - O
or CC - O

8 CD - O
. . - O
8 CD - O
MISREPRESENTATIONS NNS - O
. . - O

If IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
or CC - O
any DT - O
Person NNP - O
acting NN - O
for IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
makes VBZ - O
any DT - O
material NN - O
misrepresentation NN - O
or CC - O
material NN - O
misstatement NN - O
now RB - O
or CC - O
later JJ - O
in IN - O
any DT - O
warranty NN - O
or CC - O
representation NN - O
in IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NN - O
or CC - O
in IN - O
any DT - O
writing NN - O
delivered VBN - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
or CC - O
to TO - O
induce VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
to TO - O
enter VB - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Document NNP - O
. . - O

9 CD - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
S NNP - O
RIGHTS NNP - O
AND NNP - O
REMEDIES NNP - O

9 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
RIGHTS NNS - O
AND CC - O
REMEDIES NNP - O
. . - O

When WRB - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
occurs NNS - O
and CC - O
continues VBZ - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
may MD - O
, , - O
without IN - O
notice NN - O
or CC - O
demand NN - O
, , - O
do VBP - O
any DT - O
or CC - O
all DT - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
following JJ - O
: : - O

( NN - O
c NN - O
) : - O
Make NNP - O
any DT - O
payments NNS - O
and CC - O
do VBP - O
any DT - O
acts NNS - O
it PRP - O
considers VBZ - O
necessary JJ - O
or CC - O
reasonable JJ - O
to TO - O
protect VB - O
its PRP$ - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
assemble VB - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
if IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
requires VBZ - O
and CC - O
make VB - O
it PRP - O
available JJ - O
as IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
designates NNS - O
. . - O

9 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
POWER NN - O
OF IN - O
ATTORNEY NNP - O
. . - O

Effective JJ - O
only RB - O
when WRB - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
occurs NNS - O
and CC - O
continues VBZ - O
, , - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
irrevocably RB - O
appoints VBZ - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
as IN - O
its PRP$ - O
lawful JJ - O
attorney NN - O
to TO - O
: : - O
( : - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
transfer JJ - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
into IN - O
the DT - O
name NN - O
of IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
or CC - O
a DT - O
third JJ - O
party NN - O
as IN - O
the DT - O
Code NNP - O
permits VBZ - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
may MD - O
exercise VB - O
the DT - O
power NN - O
of IN - O
attorney NN - O
to TO - O
sign VB - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
name VBD - O
on IN - O
any DT - O
documents NNS - O
necessary JJ - O
to TO - O
perfect VB - O
or CC - O
continue VB - O
the DT - O
perfection NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
regardless NN - O
of IN - O
whether IN - O
an DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
has VBZ - O
occurred VBN - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
appointment NN - O
as IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
attorney NN - O
in IN - O
fact NN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
of IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
rights NNS - O
and CC - O
powers NNS - O
, , - O
coupled VBN - O

9 CD - O
. . - O
3 CD - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
EXPENSES NNP - O
. . - O

If IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
fails VBZ - O
to TO - O
pay VB - O
any DT - O
amount NN - O
or CC - O
furnish JJ - O
any DT - O
required VBN - O
proof NN - O
of IN - O
payment NN - O
to TO - O
third JJ - O
persons NNS - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
may MD - O
make VB - O
all PDT - O
or CC - O
part NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
payment NN - O
or CC - O
obtain VB - O
insurance NN - O
policies NNS - O
required VBN - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
6 CD - O
. . - O
4 CD - O
, , - O
and CC - O
take VB - O
any DT - O
action NN - O
under IN - O
the DT - O
policies NNS - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
deems NNS - O
prudent VBD - O
Any NNP - O
amounts NNS - O
paid VBD - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
are VBP - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
Expenses NNP - O
and CC - O
immediately RB - O
due JJ - O
and CC - O
payable JJ - O
, , - O
bearing VBG - O
interest NN - O
at IN - O
the DT - O
then RB - O
applicable JJ - O
rate NN - O
and CC - O
secured VBD - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
. . - O

No DT - O
payments NNS - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
are VBP - O
deemed VBN - O
an DT - O
agreement NN - O
to TO - O
make VB - O
similar JJ - O
payments NNS - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
future NN - O
or CC - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' '' - O
s VBZ - O
waiver RB - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
. . - O

9 CD - O
. . - O
4 CD - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
S NNP - O
LIABILITY NNP - O
FOR NNP - O
COLLATERAL NNP - O
. . - O

If IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
complies NNS - O
with IN - O
reasonable JJ - O
banking NN - O
practices NNS - O
it PRP - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
liable JJ - O
for IN - O
( NN - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
the DT - O
safekeeping NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
; : - O
( : - O
b NN - O
) : - O
any DT - O
loss NN - O
or CC - O
damage NN - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
; : - O
( : - O
c NN - O
) : - O
any DT - O
diminution NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
value NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
; : - O
or CC - O
( : - O
d JJ - O
) NN - O
any DT - O
act NN - O
or CC - O
default NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
carrier NN - O
, , - O
warehouseman NN - O
, , - O
bailee NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
person NN - O
. . - O

9 CD - O
. . - O
5 CD - O
REMEDIES NNS - O
CUMULATIVE NNP - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
rights NNS - O
and CC - O
remedies NNS - O
under IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
, , - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
other JJ - O
agreements NNS - O
are VBP - O
cumulative JJ - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
has VBZ - O
all DT - O
rights NNS - O
and CC - O
remedies NNS - O
provided VBN - O
under IN - O
the DT - O
Code NNP - O
, , - O
by IN - O
law NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
in IN - O
equity NN - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
exercise VBP - O
of IN - O
one CD - O
right JJ - O
or CC - O
remedy JJ - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
an DT - O
election NN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' '' - O
s VBZ - O
waiver RB - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
Event NNP - O
of IN - O
Default NNP - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
a DT - O
continuing VBG - O
waiver NN - O
. . - O

Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
delay VBP - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
a DT - O
waiver NN - O
, , - O
election NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
acquiescence NN - O
. . - O

9 CD - O
. . - O
6 CD - O
DEMAND NNP - O
WAIVER NNP - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
waives VBZ - O
demand NN - O
, , - O
notice NN - O
of IN - O
default NN - O
or CC - O
dishonor NN - O
, , - O
notice NN - O
of IN - O
payment NN - O
and CC - O
nonpayment NN - O
, , - O
notice NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
default NN - O
, , - O
nonpayment NN - O
at IN - O
maturity NN - O
, , - O
release NN - O
, , - O
compromise NN - O
, , - O
settlement NN - O
, , - O
extension NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
renewal JJ - O
of IN - O
accounts NNS - O
, , - O
documents NNS - O
, , - O
instruments NNS - O
, , - O
chattel NN - O
paper NN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
guarantees NNS - O
held VBD - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
on IN - O
, , - O
which WDT - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
is VBZ - O
liable JJ - O
. . - O

10 CD - O
NOTICES NNS - O

EACH DT - O
OF IN - O
BORROWER NNP - I-PER
AND NNP - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
HEREBY NNP - O
SUBMITS NNP - O
TO NNP - O
THE NNP - O
EXCLUSIVE NNP - O
JURISDICTION NNP - O
OF NNP - O
THE NNP - O
STATE NNP - O
AND NNP - O
FEDERAL NNP - O
COURTS NNP - O
LOCATED NNP - O
IN NNP - O
THE NNP - O
COMMONWEALTH NNP - I-LOC
OF NNP - I-LOC
MASSACHUSETTS NNP - I-LOC
, , - O
BUT CC - O
IF NNP - O
FOR NNP - O
ANY NNP - O
REASON NNP - O
THE NNP - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
IS NNP - O
DENIED NNP - O
ACCESS NNP - O
TO NNP - O
SUCH NNP - O
COURTS NNP - O
, , - O
THEN NNP - O
THE NNP - O
VENUE NNP - O
WILL NNP - O
BE NNP - O
IN NNP - O
THE NNP - O
STATE NNP - O
AND NNP - O
FEDERAL NNP - O
COURTS NNP - O
LOCATED NNP - O
IN NNP - O
THE NNP - O
COUNTY NNP - O
OF NNP - O
SANTA NNP - I-LOC
CLARA NNP - I-LOC
, , - O
STATE NNP - O
OF NNP - O
CALIFORNIA NNP - I-LOC
. . - O

BORROWER JJR - I-PER
AND CC - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
EACH NNP - O
HEREBY NNP - O
WAIVE NNP - O
THEIR NNP - O
RESPECTIVE NNP - O
RIGHTS NNP - O
TO NNP - O
A DT - O
JURY NNP - O
TRIAL NNP - O
OF NNP - O
ANY NNP - O
CLAIM NNP - O
OR NNP - O
CAUSE NNP - O
OF NNP - O
ACTION NNP - O
BASED NNP - O
UPON NNP - O
OR NNP - O
ARISING NNP - O
OUT NNP - O
OF NNP - O
ANY NNP - O
OF NNP - O
THE NNP - O
LOAN NNP - O
DOCUMENTS NNP - O
OR NNP - O
ANY NNP - O
OF NNP - O
THE NNP - O
TRANSACTIONS NNP - O
CONTEMPLATED NNP - O
THEREIN NNP - O
, , - O
INCLUDING NNP - O

12 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NNP - O
> NNP - O
13 CD - O
CONTRACT NNP - O
CLAIMS NNP - O
, , - O
TORT NNP - O
CLAIMS NNP - O
, , - O
BREACH NNP - O
OF NNP - O
DUTY NNP - O
CLAIMS NNP - O
, , - O
AND CC - O
ALL DT - O
OTHER NNP - O
COMMON NNP - O
LAW NNP - O
OR NNP - O
STATUTORY NNP - O
CLAIMS NNP - O
. . - O

EACH DT - O
PARTY NNP - O
RECOGNIZES NNP - O
AND NNP - O
AGREES NNP - O
THAT NNP - O
THE NNP - O
FOREGOING NNP - O
WAIVER NNP - O
CONSTITUTES NNP - O
A NNP - O
MATERIAL NNP - O
INDUCEMENT NNP - O
FOR NNP - O
IT PRP - O
TO TO - O
ENTER NNP - O
INTO NNP - O
THIS NNP - O
AGREEMENT NNP - O
. . - O

EACH DT - O
PARTY NNP - O
REPRESENTS NNP - O
AND NNP - O
WARRANTS NNP - O
THAT NNP - O
IT PRP - O
HAS VBZ - O
REVIEWED VBN - O
THIS DT - O
WAIVER NNP - O
WITH NNP - O
ITS NNP - O
LEGAL NNP - O
COUNSEL NNP - O
AND NNP - O
THAT NNP - O
IT PRP - O
KNOWINGLY NNP - O
AND NNP - O
VOLUNTARILY NNP - O
WAIVES NNP - O
ITS NNP - O
JURY NNP - O
TRIAL NNP - O
RIGHTS NNP - O
FOLLOWING NNP - O
CONSULTATION NNP - O
WITH NNP - O
LEGAL NNP - O
COUNSEL NNP - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
GENERAL NNP - O
PROVISIONS NNP - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
SUCCESSORS NNS - O
AND CC - O
ASSIGNS NNP - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
INDEMNIFICATION NN - O
. . - O

Borrower NNP - I-PER
will MD - O
indemnify VB - O
, , - O
defend NN - O
and CC - O
hold VB - O
harmless NN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
and CC - O
its PRP$ - O
officers NNS - O
, , - O
employees NNS - O
, , - O
and CC - O
agents NNS - O
against IN - O
: : - O
( : - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
all DT - O
obligations NNS - O
, , - O
demands NNS - O
, , - O
claims VBZ - O
, , - O
and CC - O
liabilities NNS - O
asserted VBD - O
by IN - O
any DT - O
other JJ - O
party NN - O
in IN - O
connection NN - O
with IN - O
the DT - O
transactions NNS - O
contemplated VBD - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
; : - O
and CC - O
( : - O
b NN - O
) : - O
all DT - O
losses NNS - O
or CC - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
Expenses NNP - O
incurred VBD - O
, , - O
or CC - O
paid VBD - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
from IN - O
, , - O
following VBG - O
, , - O
or CC - O
consequential JJ - O
to TO - O
transactions NNS - O
between IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
and CC - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
( NNP - O
including VBG - O
reasonable JJ - O
attorneys NNS - O
fees NNS - O
and CC - O
expenses NNS - O
), : - O
except IN - O
for IN - O
losses NNS - O
caused VBN - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
gross VBP - O
negligence NN - O
or CC - O
willful JJ - O
misconduct NN - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
3 CD - O
TIME NNP - O
OF NNP - O
ESSENCE NNP - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
4 CD - O
SEVERABILITY NN - O
OF IN - O
PROVISION NNP - O
. . - O

Each DT - O
provision NN - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
is VBZ - O
severable JJ - O
from IN - O
every DT - O
other JJ - O
provision NN - O
in IN - O
determining NN - O
the DT - O
enforceability NN - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
provision NN - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
5 CD - O
AMENDMENTS NNS - O
IN IN - O
WRITING NNP - O
, , - O
INTEGRATION NNP - O
. . - O

All DT - O
amendments NNS - O
to TO - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
must MD - O
be VB - O
in IN - O
writing NN - O
and CC - O
signed VBD - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

This DT - O
Agreement NN - O
represents VBZ - O
the DT - O
entire JJ - O
agreement NN - O
about IN - O
this DT - O
subject NN - O
matter NN - O
, , - O
and CC - O
supersedes VBZ - O
prior RB - O
negotiations NNS - O
or CC - O
agreements NNS - O
. . - O

All DT - O
prior RB - O
agreements NNS - O
, , - O
understandings NNS - O
, , - O
representations NNS - O
, , - O
warranties NNS - O
, , - O
and CC - O
negotiations NNS - O
between IN - O
the DT - O
parties NNS - O
about IN - O
the DT - O
subject NN - O
matter NN - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
merge NN - O
into IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
and CC - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
7 CD - O
SURVIVAL NNP - O
. . - O

All DT - O
covenants NNS - O
, , - O
representations NNS - O
and CC - O
warranties NNS - O
made VBD - O
in IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NN - O
continue VBP - O
in IN - O
full JJ - O
force NN - O
while IN - O
any DT - O
Obligations NNS - O
remain VBP - O
outstanding JJ - O
. . - O

The DT - O
obligations NNS - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
in IN - O
Section NNP - O
12 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
to TO - O
indemnify VB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
survive VB - O
until IN - O
all DT - O
statutes NNS - O
of IN - O
limitations NNS - O
for IN - O
actions NNS - O
that WDT - O
may MD - O
be VB - O
brought VBN - O
against IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
have VBP - O
run VBN - O
. . - O

13 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NNP - O
> NNP - O
14 CD - O
12 CD - O
. . - O
8 CD - O
CONFIDENTIALITY NNP - O
. . - O

In IN - O
handling NN - O
any DT - O
confidential JJ - O
information NN - O
, , - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
will MD - O
exercise VB - O
the DT - O
same JJ - O
degree NN - O
of IN - O
care NN - O
that IN - O
it PRP - O
exercises VBZ - O
for IN - O
its PRP$ - O
own JJ - O
proprietary JJ - O
information NN - O
, , - O
but CC - O
disclosure NN - O
of IN - O
information NN - O
may MD - O
be VB - O
made VBN - O
( -NONE- - O
i PRP - O
) VBP - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
subsidiaries NNS - O
or CC - O
affiliates NNS - O
in IN - O
connection NN - O
with IN - O
their PRP$ - O
business NN - O
with IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
, , - O
( NNP - O
ii NN - O
) : - O
to TO - O
prospective VB - O
transferees NNS - O
or CC - O
purchasers NNS - O
of IN - O
any DT - O
interest NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Loans NNPS - O
, , - O
( NNP - O
iii NN - O
) : - O
as IN - O
required VBN - O
by IN - O
law NN - O
, , - O
regulation NN - O
, , - O
subpoena NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
order NN - O
, , - O
( : - O
iv NN - O
) : - O
as IN - O
required VBN - O
in IN - O
connection NN - O
with IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
examination NN - O
or CC - O
audit NN - O
and CC - O
( CD - O
v NN - O
) : - O
as IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
considers NNS - O
appropriate VBP - O
exercising VBG - O
remedies NNS - O
under IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
. . - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
9 CD - O
COUNTERSIGNATURE NN - O
. . - O

This DT - O
Agreement NN - O
shall MD - O
become VB - O
effective JJ - O
only RB - O
when WRB - O
it PRP - O
shall MD - O
have VB - O
been VBN - O
executed VBN - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
( NNP - O
provided VBD - O
, , - O
however RB - O
, , - O
in IN - O
no DT - O
event NN - O
shall MD - O
this DT - O
Agreement NN - O
become NN - O
effective JJ - O
until IN - O
signed JJ - O
by IN - O
an DT - O
officer NN - O
of IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
in IN - O
California NNP - I-LOC
). NNP - O

12 CD - O
. . - O
10 CD - O
ATTORNEYS NNS - O
' POS - O
FEES NNS - O
, , - O
COSTS NNS - O
AND CC - O
EXPENSES NNP - O
. . - O

In IN - O
any DT - O
action NN - O
or CC - O
proceeding VBG - O
between IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
arising NN - O
out IN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
prevailing VBG - O
party NN - O
will MD - O
be VB - O
entitled VBN - O
to TO - O
recover VB - O
its PRP$ - O
reasonable JJ - O
attorneys NNS - O
' POS - O
fees NNS - O
and CC - O
other JJ - O
costs NNS - O
and CC - O
expenses NNS - O
incurred VBD - O
, , - O
in IN - O
addition NN - O
to TO - O
any DT - O
other JJ - O
relief NN - O
to TO - O
which WDT - O
it PRP - O
may MD - O
be VB - O
entitled VBN - O
. . - O

13 CD - O
DEFINITIONS NNS - O

13 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
DEFINITIONS NNS - O
. . - O

In IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NN - O
: : - O

" NN - O
ACCOUNTS NNS - O
" : - O
are VBP - O
all DT - O
existing VBG - O
and CC - O
later JJ - O
arising NN - O
accounts NNS - O
, , - O
contract NN - O
rights NNS - O
, , - O
and CC - O
other JJ - O
obligations NNS - O
owed VBD - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
in IN - O
connection NN - O
with IN - O
its PRP$ - O
sale NN - O
or CC - O
lease VB - O
of IN - O
goods NNS - O
( : - O
including VBG - O
licensing NN - O
software NN - O
and CC - O
other JJ - O
technology NN - O
) : - O
or CC - O
provision NN - O
of IN - O
services NNS - O
, , - O
all DT - O
credit NN - O
insurance NN - O
, , - O
guaranties NNS - O
, , - O
other JJ - O
security NN - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
merchandise NN - O
returned VBD - O
or CC - O
reclaimed VBN - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' '' - O
s VBZ - O
Books NNP - O
relating NN - O
to TO - O
any DT - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
foregoing NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
AFFILIATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
of IN - O
a DT - O
Person NNP - O
is VBZ - O
a DT - O
Person NNP - O
that WDT - O
owns VBZ - O
or CC - O
controls NNS - O
directly RB - O
or CC - O
indirectly RB - O
the DT - O
Person NNP - O
, , - O
any DT - O
Person NNP - O
that IN - O
controls NNS - O
or CC - O
is VBZ - O
controlled VBN - O
by IN - O
or CC - O
is VBZ - O
under IN - O
common JJ - O
control NN - O
with IN - O
the DT - O
Person NNP - O
, , - O
and CC - O
each DT - O
of IN - O
that DT - O
Person NNP - O
' POS - O
s NNS - O
senior JJ - O
executive NN - O
officers NNS - O
, , - O
directors NNS - O
, , - O
partners NNS - O
and CC - O
, , - O
for IN - O
any DT - O
Person NNP - O
that IN - O
is VBZ - O
a DT - O
limited VBN - O
liability NN - O
company NN - O
, , - O
that IN - O
Person NNP - O
' POS - O
s NNS - O
managers NNS - O
and CC - O
members NNS - O
. . - O

" NN - O
BANK NNP - I-ORG
EXPENSES NNP - O
" NNP - O
are VBP - O
all DT - O
audit NN - O
fees NNS - O
and CC - O
expenses NNS - O
and CC - O
reasonable JJ - O
costs NNS - O
or CC - O
expenses NNS - O
( VBP - O
including VBG - O
reasonable JJ - O
attorneys NNS - O
' POS - O
fees NNS - O
and CC - O
expenses NNS - O
) : - O
for IN - O
preparing NN - O
, , - O
negotiating VBG - O
, , - O
administering VBG - O
, , - O
defending VBG - O
and CC - O
enforcing VBG - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Documents NNP - O
( NNP - O
including VBG - O
appeals NNS - O
or CC - O
Insolvency NNP - O
Proceedings NNP - O
). NNP - O

" NN - O
BORROWER NN - I-PER
' '' - O
S NNP - O
BOOKS NNP - O
" NNP - O
are VBP - O
all DT - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
books NNS - O
and CC - O
records NNS - O
including VBG - O
ledgers NNS - O
, , - O
records NNS - O
regarding VBG - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
assets NNS - O
or CC - O
liabilities NNS - O
, , - O
the DT - O
Collateral NNP - O
, , - O
business NN - O
operations NNS - O
or CC - O
financial JJ - O
condition NN - O
and CC - O
all DT - O
computer NN - O
programs NNS - O
or CC - O
discs NNS - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
equipment NN - O
containing VBG - O
the DT - O
information NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
BUSINESS NN - O
DAY NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
any DT - O
day NN - O
that IN - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
a DT - O
Saturday NNP - O
, , - O
Sunday NNP - O
or CC - O
a DT - O
day NN - O
on IN - O
which WDT - O
the DT - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
is VBZ - O
closed VBN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
CLOSING NN - O
DATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
. . - O

14 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NNP - O
> NNP - O
15 CD - O
" CD - O
COLLATERAL NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
property NN - O
described VBD - O
on IN - O
Exhibit NNP - O
A NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
COMMITMENT NN - O
TERMINATION NN - O
DATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
January NNP - O
27 CD - O
, , - O
2000 CD - O
. . - O

The DT - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
a DT - O
Contingent NNP - O
Obligation NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
stated VBN - O
or CC - O
determined VBN - O
amount NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
primary JJ - O
obligation NN - O
for IN - O
which WDT - O
the DT - O
Contingent NNP - O
Obligation NNP - O
is VBZ - O
made VBN - O
or CC - O
, , - O
if IN - O
not RB - O
determinable JJ - O
, , - O
the DT - O
maximum NN - O
reasonably RB - O
anticipated VBN - O
liability NN - O
for IN - O
it PRP - O
determined VBD - O
by IN - O
the DT - O
Person NNP - O
in IN - O
good JJ - O
faith NN - O
; : - O
but CC - O
the DT - O
amount NN - O
may MD - O
not RB - O
exceed VB - O
the DT - O
maximum NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
obligations NNS - O
under IN - O
the DT - O
guarantee NN - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
support NN - O
arrangement NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
CREDIT NN - O
EXTENSION NN - O
" : - O
is VBZ - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
other JJ - O
extension NN - O
of IN - O
credit NN - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
for IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
benefit NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
ELIGIBLE NNP - O
EQUIPMENT NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
general JJ - O
purpose NN - O
computer NN - O
equipment NN - O
, , - O
office NN - O
equipment NN - O
, , - O
test NN - O
and CC - O
laboratory NN - O
equipment NN - O
, , - O
furnishings NNS - O
, , - O
and CC - O
, , - O
subject JJ - O
to TO - O
the DT - O
limitations NNS - O
set VBD - O
forth JJ - O
below IN - O
, , - O
Other JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
that IN - O
complies NNS - O
with IN - O
all DT - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
' POS - O
s NNS - O
representations NNS - O
and CC - O
warranties NNS - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
and CC - O
which WDT - O
is VBZ - O
acceptable JJ - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
in IN - O
all DT - O
respects NNS - O
. . - O

Unless IN - O
otherwise RB - O
agreed VBN - O
to TO - O
by IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
: : - O
not RB - O
more JJR - O
than IN - O
25 CD - O
% NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
financed VBD - O
with IN - O
the DT - O
proceeds NNS - O
of IN - O
each DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
shall MD - O
consist VB - O
of IN - O
Other JJ - O
Equipment NNP - O
. . - O

All DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
financed VBD - O
with IN - O
the DT - O
proceeds NNS - O
of IN - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advances NNPS - O
shall MD - O
be VB - O
new JJ - O
and CC - O
purchased VBN - O
within IN - O
120 CD - O
days NNS - O
from IN - O
the DT - O
date NN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
. . - O

Equipment NNP - O
to TO - O
be VB - O
located VBN - O
outside IN - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
United NNP - I-LOC
States NNPS - I-LOC
shall MD - O
be VB - O
limited VBN - O
to TO - O
a DT - O
maximum NN - O
of IN - O
$ $ - O
150 CD - O
, , - O
000 CD - O
. . - O

" NN - O
EQUIPMENT NN - O
" : - O
is VBZ - O
all DT - O
present NN - O
and CC - O
future JJ - O
machinery NN - O
, , - O
equipment NN - O
, , - O
tenant JJ - O
improvements NNS - O
, , - O
furniture NN - O
, , - O
fixtures NNS - O
, , - O
vehicles NNS - O
, , - O
tools NNS - O
, , - O
parts NNS - O
and CC - O
attachments NNS - O
in IN - O
which WDT - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
has VBZ - O
any DT - O
interest NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
EQUIPMENT NN - O
ADVANCE NN - O
" : - O
is VBZ - O
defined VBN - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
2 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O

" NN - O
EQUIPMENT NN - O
AVAILABILITY NN - O
END NN - O
DATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
defined VBN - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
2 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O

" NN - O
EQUIPMENT NN - O
MATURITY NN - O
DATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
defined VBN - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
2 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O
1 CD - O
. . - O

" NN - O
ERISA NNP - I-ORG
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
Employment NNP - O
Retirement NNP - O
Income NNP - O
Security NNP - O
Act NNP - O
of IN - O
1974 CD - O
, , - O
and CC - O
its PRP$ - O
regulations NNS - O
. . - O

" NN - O
FINAL NNP - O
PAYMENT NNP - O
PERCENTAGE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
defined VBN - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
2 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
( CD - O
d NN - O
). : - O

" NN - O
FINANCED VBN - O
EQUIPMENT NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
defined VBN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Supplement NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
FUNDING NN - O
DATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
any DT - O
date NN - O
on IN - O
which WDT - O
an DT - O
Equipment NNP - O
Advance NNP - O
is VBZ - O
made VBN - O
to TO - O
or CC - O
on IN - O
account NN - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
. . - O

15 CD - O
< `` - O
PAGE NNP - O
> NNP - O
16 CD - O
" CD - O
INDEBTEDNESS NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
( NNP - O
a DT - O
) NN - O
indebtedness NN - O
for IN - O
borrowed VBN - O
money NN - O
or CC - O
the DT - O
deferred VBN - O
price NN - O
of IN - O
property NN - O
or CC - O
services NNS - O
, , - O
such JJ - O
as IN - O
reimbursement NN - O
and CC - O
other JJ - O
obligations NNS - O
for IN - O
surety NN - O
bonds NNS - O
and CC - O
letters NNS - O
of IN - O
credit NN - O
( : - O
b NN - O
) : - O
obligations NNS - O
evidenced VBD - O
by IN - O
notes NNS - O
, , - O
bonds NNS - O
, , - O
debentures NNS - O
or CC - O
similar JJ - O
instruments NNS - O
, , - O
( : - O
c NN - O
) : - O
capital NN - O
lease NN - O
obligations NNS - O
and CC - O
( : - O
d NN - O
) : - O
Contingent NNP - O
Obligations NNPS - O
. . - O

" NN - O
INSOLVENCY NN - O
PROCEEDING NNP - O
" NNP - O
are VBP - O
proceedings NNS - O
by IN - O
or CC - O
against IN - O
any DT - O
Person NNP - O
under IN - O
the DT - O
United NNP - I-LOC
States NNPS - I-LOC
Bankruptcy NNP - O
Code NNP - O
, , - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
other JJ - O
bankruptcy NN - O
or CC - O
insolvency NN - O
law NN - O
, , - O
including VBG - O
assignments NNS - O
for IN - O
the DT - O
benefit NN - O
of IN - O
creditors NNS - O
, , - O
compositions NNS - O
, , - O
extensions NNS - O
generally RB - O
with IN - O
its PRP$ - O
creditors NNS - O
, , - O
or CC - O
proceedings NNS - O
seeking VBG - O
reorganization NN - O
, , - O
arrangement NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
relief NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
INVESTMENT NN - O
" : - O
is VBZ - O
any DT - O
beneficial JJ - O
ownership NN - O
of IN - O
( NNP - O
including VBG - O
stock NN - O
, , - O
partnership NN - O
interest NN - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
securities NNS - O
) : - O
any DT - O
Person NNP - O
, , - O
or CC - O
any DT - O
loan NN - O
, , - O
advance NN - O
or CC - O
capital NN - O
contribution NN - O
to TO - O
any DT - O
Person NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
LIEN NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
a DT - O
mortgage NN - O
, , - O
lien VBN - O
, , - O
deed VBN - O
of IN - O
trust NN - O
, , - O
charge NN - O
, , - O
pledge NN - O
, , - O
security NN - O
interest NN - O
or CC - O
other JJ - O
encumbrance NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
LOAN NN - O
DOCUMENTS NNS - O
" : - O
are VBP - O
, , - O
collectively RB - O
, , - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
, , - O
any DT - O
note NN - O
, , - O
or CC - O
notes NNS - O
or CC - O
guaranties NNS - O
executed VBN - O
by IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
or CC - O
Guarantor NNP - O
, , - O
and CC - O
any DT - O
other JJ - O
present NN - O
or CC - O
future JJ - O
agreement NN - O
between IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
and CC - O
/ NNP - O
or CC - O
for IN - O
the DT - O
benefit NN - O
of IN - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
in IN - O
connection NN - O
with IN - O
this DT - O
Agreement NNP - O
, , - O
all DT - O
as IN - O
amended VBN - O
, , - O
extended VBD - O
or CC - O
restated VBN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
LOAN NN - O
FACTOR NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
the DT - O
amount NN - O
set VBD - O
forth NN - O
as IN - O
a DT - O
percentage NN - O
in IN - O
the DT - O
Loan NNP - O
Supplement NNP - O
calculated VBD - O
using VBG - O
the DT - O
Basic NNP - O
Rate NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
LOAN NN - O
SUPPLEMENT NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
attached VBN - O
as RB - O
Exhibit NNP - O
C NNP - O
. . - O

" NN - O
OBLIGATIONS NNS - O
" : - O
are VBP - O
debts NNS - O
, , - O
principal JJ - O
, , - O
interest NN - O
, , - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
Expenses NNP - O
and CC - O
other JJ - O
amounts NNS - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
owes NNS - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
now RB - O
or CC - O
later JJ - O
, , - O
including VBG - O
letters NNS - O
of IN - O
credit NN - O
and CC - O
exchange NN - O
contracts NNS - O
and CC - O
including VBG - O
interest NN - O
accruing VBG - O
after IN - O
Insolvency NNP - O
Proceedings NNP - O
begin NN - O
and CC - O
debts NNS - O
, , - O
liabilities NNS - O
, , - O
or CC - O
obligations NNS - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
assigned VBD - O
to TO - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
. . - O

" NN - O
ORIGINAL NNP - O
STATED NNP - O
COST NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
defined VBN - O
in IN - O
Section NN - O
2 CD - O
. . - O
2 CD - O
( CD - O
d NN - O
). : - O

" NN - O
OTHER JJ - O
EQUIPMENT NN - O
" : - O
is VBZ - O
leasehold VBN - O
improvements NNS - O
, , - O
intangible JJ - O
property NN - O
such JJ - O
as IN - O
computer NN - O
software NN - O
and CC - O
software NN - O
licenses NNS - O
, , - O
equipment NN - O
specifically RB - O
designed VBN - O
or CC - O
manufactured VBN - O
for IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
, , - O
other JJ - O
intangible JJ - O
property NN - O
, , - O
limited VBN - O
use NN - O
property NN - O
and CC - O
other JJ - O
similar JJ - O
property NN - O
and CC - O
soft JJ - O
costs NNS - O
, , - O
including VBG - O
sales NNS - O
tax NN - O
, , - O
freight VBD - O
and CC - O
installation NN - O
expenses NNS - O
. . - O

" NN - O
PRIME NNP - O
RATE NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
most JJS - O
recently RB - O
announced VBD - O
" CD - O
prime JJ - O
rate NN - O
," : - O
even RB - O
if IN - O
it PRP - O
is VBZ - O
not RB - O
Bank NNP - I-ORG
' POS - O
s NNS - O
lowest JJS - O
rate NN - O
. . - O

" NN - O
RESPONSIBLE NNP - O
OFFICER NNP - O
" NNP - O
is VBZ - O
each DT - O
of IN - O
the DT - O
Chief NNP - O
Executive NNP - O
Officer NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
President NNP - O
, , - O
the DT - O
Chief NNP - I-ORG
Financial NNP - I-ORG
Officer NNP - I-ORG
and CC - O
the DT - O
Controller NNP - O
of IN - O
Borrower NNP - I-PER
. . - O

