BREAKING	O
WSJ	B-ORG
:	O
Intel	O
Detected	O
Surface	O
Missile	O
Launch	O
,	O
Tracked	O
Explosion	O
of	O
#MH17,	O
Official	O
Says	O
/	O
/	O
Story	O
to	O
follow	O
http://t.co/gAq9IU4nxf	O

The	O
Putin	B-PER
mercenary	O
who	O
boasted	O
about	O
downing	O
a	O
plane	O
before	O
he	O
realized	O
the	O
plane	O
was	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/A4vngh0Oed	O
http://t.co/XhKUT7dQyW	O
"	O

Airlines	O
leery	O
of	O
airspace	O
where	O
#MH17	O
and	O
two	O
military	O
jets	O
recently	O
crashed	O
:	O
http://t.co/SlMFyTemrl	O
http://t.co/G1sCNdUjE9	O

NOW	O
:	O
US	B-LOC
officials	O
conclude	O
#MH17	O
shot	O
down	O
.	O
Radar	O
system	O
saw	O
a	O
surface-to-air	O
missile	O
track	O
plane	O
right	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
shot	O
down	O
,	O
says	O
CNN	B-ORG

Is	O
it	O
Doomsday	O
today	O
or	O
what	O
exactly	O
?	O
#Gaza	B-LOC
#MH17	O
#Libya	B-LOC
#Iraq	I-LOC
#Syria	I-LOC

Passengers	O
on	O
board	O
#MH17	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
Dutch	O
officials	O
)	O
Dutch	O
154	O
Australians	O
27	O
Malaysia	B-LOC
23	O
Indonesia	B-LOC
11	O
UK	B-LOC
6	O
Germany	B-LOC
4	O
Belgium	B-LOC
4	O

White	B-LOC
House	I-LOC
says	O
Obama	B-PER
called	O
Malaysian	O
prime	O
minister	O
,	O
Ukrainian	O
president	O
about	O
downed	O
jet	O
from	O
Air	O
Force	O
One	O
.	O
#MH17	O

#MH17	O
Known	O
nationalities	O
:	O
154	O
Dutch	O
,	O
27	O
Australians	O
,	O
23	O
Malaysians	O
,	O
11	O
Indonesians	O
,	O
6	O
UK	O
,	O
4	O
Germans	O
;	O
4	O
Belgians	O
,	O
3	O
Filipinos	O
,	O
1	O
Canadian	O

Statement	O
by	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
of	O
Malaysia	B-LOC
,	O
Dato	B-PER
'	I-PER
Seri	I-PER
Najib	I-PER
Razak	I-PER
on	O
#MH17	O
Incident	O
http://t.co/fqjkS5xIbX	O

Spain	B-LOC
based	O
air	O
traffic	O
controller	O
says	O
#MH17	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
2	O
Ukrainian	O
fighter	O
jets	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
blown	O
up	O
.	O
https://t.co/DBFO5CsAsm	O

What	O
the	O
#MH17	O
wreckage	O
is	O
already	O
revealing	O
http://t.co/PfbpmVQgmJ	O

Firefighter	O
at	O
site	O
of	O
#MH17	O
crash	O
:	O
"	O
It	O
was	O
like	O
ground	O
zero	O
,	O
total	O
devastation	O
"	O
http://t.co/EZkrpxuDhY	O
http://t.co/qAouhvtsEw	O

At	O
midnight	O
we	O
hear	O
of	O
#MH17	O
crashed	O
;	O
later	O
t	O
massive	O
ground	O
bombings	O
in	O
#Gaza.	B-LOC
Let	O
's	O
together	O
#pray4safety	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
http://t.co/qcrATb0Spo	O

Rest	O
in	O
peace	O
my	O
lovely	O
aunt	O
.	O
.	O
💔 	O
MH17 	O
PrayForMH17 	O
ttp://t.co/sGX65yebKk	O

PHOTO	O
:	O
Hundreds	O
at	O
Netherlands	B-LOC
Embassy	I-LOC
in	O
Kiev	B-LOC
lay	O
down	O
flowers	O
for	O
those	O
who	O
perished	O
in	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/e6foyd6OTd	O
pic	O
by	O
@cool_mindsUA	O

Ukraine	B-LOC
Officials	O
claim	O
to	O
have	O
data	O
of	O
call	O
between	O
Pro	B-ORG
Russian	I-ORG
separatists	I-ORG
and	O
a	O
Russian	O
Intel	O
Officer	O
before	O
taking	O
the	O
plane	O
down	O
#MH17	O

The	O
plane	O
was	O
flying	O
over	O
non-restricted	O
aerospace	O
-	O
IATA	B-ORG
#MH17	O
http://t.co/pr8MELq5L6	O

from	O
Paestine	B-LOC
to	O
Malaysia	B-LOC
,	O
Be	O
Strong	O
as	O
you	O
always	O
are	O
.	O
#MH17	O
#PrayForMH17	O
Malaysian	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
All	O
295	O
http://t.co/JmTnE3ZXnn	O

A	O
passenger	O
posted	O
before	O
boarding	O
Malaysian	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
#MH17.	O
It	O
says	O
"	O
If	O
it	O
disappears	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
it	O
looks	O
like	O
.	O
"	O
http://t.co/u7VETPtegd	O

People	O
mourn	O
#MH17	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
Netherlands	B-LOC
Embassy	I-LOC
.	O
The	O
day	O
in	O
photos	O
:	O
http://t.co/wRGNmgNE1J	O
(	O
AFP	B-ORG
/	O
Getty	B-ORG
Images	I-ORG
)	O
http://t.co/gGqBNl0P52	O

So	O
on	O
top	O
of	O
#MH17,	O
#Gaza,	O
#Libya,	O
Assad	O
has	O
started	O
gassing	O
toddlers	O
again	O
.	O
Night	O
all	O
!	O

What	O
a	O
heavy	O
feeling	O
to	O
wake	O
up	O
to	O
.	O
Such	O
violence	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
we	O
love	O
in	O
.	O
#MH17	O

Families	O
of	O
passengers	O
on	O
Malaysia	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
Flight	O
#MH17	O
demand	O
answers	O
http://t.co/bHKXhtbSZd	O

My	O
deepest	O
condolence	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
the	O
crew	O
and	O
passengers	O
of	O
MH	O
17	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
truly	O
sorry	O
for	O
your	O
lost	O
.	O
Stay	O
strong	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
out	O
of	O
words	O
.	O
#MH17	O

All	O
at	O
McLaren	B-ORG
offer	O
heartfelt	O
condolences	O
to	O
everyone	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
tragic	O
loss	O
of	O
#MalaysiaAirlines	B-ORG
#MH17.	O

"	O
Slaughter	O
at	O
32	O
,	O
000ft	O
"	O
&	O
"	O
Putin	B-PER
's	O
missile	O
"	O
–	O
#MH17	O
on	O
Friday	O
's	O
UK	B-LOC
front	O
pages	O
http://t.co/cfKq92sjbJ	O
#BBCPapers	O
http://t.co/RM8bTt3ILw	O

#MH17	O
crashed	O
.	O
Meanwhile	O
in	O
Gaza	B-LOC
,	O
Israel	B-LOC
continues	O
bullying	O
.	O
Terrorist	O
in	O
Sabah	B-LOC
.	O
Sad	O
day	O
for	O
Malaysians	O
.	O
Sad	O
day	O
for	O
Muslims	O
.	O
#PrayForMH17	O

Meanwhile	O
#Moscow	B-LOC
residents	O
write	O
'	O
Excuse	O
us	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
Dutch	B-ORG
embassy	I-ORG
in	O
#Russia	B-LOC
#MH17	O
#Ukraine	B-LOC
http://t.co/I7qzRIVF3F	O

This	O
is	O
possibly	O
now	O
more	O
relevant	O
than	O
ever	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/qrEDrcfdv4	O

I	O
offer	O
my	O
deepest	O
condolences	O
to	O
#MH17	O
victims	O
’	O
families	O
and	O
friends	O
.	O
May	O
their	O
soul	O
rest	O
in	O
peace	O
.	O
#Dieptriest	B-PER
http://t.co/MZYzfjTkEL	O

Awesome	O
gig	O
@ushuaiaibiza	O
but	O
cant	O
celebrate	O
after	O
the	O
terrible	O
news	O
about	O
#MH17.	O
No	O
words	O
for	O
it	O
.	O

With	O
295	O
confirmed	O
dead	O
,	O
#MH17	O
is	O
the	O
deadliest	O
terrorist	O
attack	O
involving	O
a	O
plane	O
crash	O
since	O
9	O
/	O
11	O
.	O

Meanwhile	O
#Moscow	B-LOC
residents	O
write	O
'	O
Excuse	O
us	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
Dutch	B-LOC
embassy	I-LOC
in	O
#Russia	B-LOC
#MH17	O
http://t.co/HoMsaz5D2I	O
"	O
@	B-ORG
MoscowTimes	B-ORG
@	B-PER
EvaHartog	B-PER

Russian	O
cmdr	O
Strelkov	B-PER
(	O
in	O
#Ukraine)	B-LOC
:	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
reason	O
for	O
ceasefire	O
/	O
humanitarian	O
corridor	O
to	O
help	O
w	O
/	O
#MH17	O
investigation	O
.	O
We	O
're	O
at	O
war	O
here	O
.	O

Now	O
i	O
know	O
why	O
airports	O
see	O
more	O
sincere	O
kisses	O
than	O
wedding	O
halls	O
:	O
'	O
(	O
#Pray4MH17	O
#MH17	O

Death	O
could	O
be	O
right	O
around	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
.	O
You	O
just	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
it	O
coming	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
RIP	O
to	O
everyone	O
on	O
that	O
flight	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/UnAKpH6c9w	O

MAS	B-ORG
said	O
298	O
people	O
boarded	O
MH	O
17	O
comprising	O
283	O
passengers	O
,	O
15	O
crew	O
#MH17	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
@	B-ORG
MAS	B-ORG
revises	O
up	O
#MH17	O
count	O
to	O
298	O
:	O
283	O
passengers	O
,	O
including	O
3	O
infants	O
,	O
15	O
crew	O
.	O

Nationalities	O
:	O
Netherlands	B-LOC
(	O
154	O
)	O
,	O
Malaysia	B-LOC
(	O
45	O
)	O
,	O
Australia	B-LOC
(	O
27	O
)	O
,	O
Indonesia	B-LOC
(	O
12	O
)	O
,	O
UK	B-LOC
(	O
9	O
)	O
,	O
among	O
298	O
people	O
boarded	O
MH	O
17	O
#MH17	O

RT	O
@	B-PER
MichelSidibe	B-PER
:	O
My	O
thoughts	O
&	O
prayers	O
to	O
families	O
of	O
those	O
tragically	O
lost	O
on	O
flight	O
#MH17.	O
Many	O
passengers	O
were	O
enroute	O
to	O
#AIDS2014	O

My	O
condolences	O
to	O
the	O
families	O
of	O
the	O
victims	O
of	O
#MH17.	O
The	O
terrorists	O
and	O
their	O
insane	O
suppliers	O
have	O
to	O
be	O
stopped	O
!	O
http://t.co/bZz4UHurL3	O

Hundreds	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
flowers	O
&	O
toys	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
#Dutch	O
embassy	B-LOC
,	O
#Kiev.	B-LOC
No	O
words	O
.	O
RIP	O
|	O
EMPR	O
#MH17	O
#RussiaAttacksUkraine	O
http://t.co/7x39buSfNR	O

#ASEAN	B-ORG
expresses	O
its	O
sympathy	O
to	O
family	O
of	O
crew	O
&	O
passengers	O
of	O
@	B-ORG
MAS	B-ORG
Flight	O
#MH17	O
which	O
crashed	O
yesterday	O
in	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/4KceX5PbT5	O

My	O
deepest	O
condolences	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
/	O
friends	O
of	O
those	O
on	O
board	O
Malaysia	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
flight	O
#MH17.	O
http://t.co/AkQEKvGLlQ	O

Here	O
's	O
the	O
passenger	O
breakdown	O
by	O
nationality	O
:	O
http://t.co/q53Gu6FsVq	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/ZWudzjAORL	O

In	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
tragic	O
loss	O
of	O
life	O
on	O
#MH17,	O
including	O
those	O
travelling	O
for	O
#Aids2014	B-ORG
we	O
have	O
cancelled	O
this	O
evening	O
’	O
s	O
Docklands	B-LOC
fireworks	O
.	O

#MalaysiaAirlines	B-ORG
#MH17	O
crash	O
:	O
Distraught	O
families	O
of	O
passengers	O
waiting	O
at	O
#KL	B-LOC
airport	I-LOC
http://t.co/D1KysrHH8c	O
http://t.co/4LeyYb9mQt	O

Current	O
passenger	O
breakdown	O
by	O
nationality	O
-	O
via	O
@	B-ORG
theage	B-ORG
@	B-ORG
smh	B-ORG
#MH17	O
http://t.co/MjswmQhwI8	O
http://t.co/1bP78hLPBH	O

"	O
Will	O
not	O
forget	O
.	O
Will	O
not	O
forgive	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
"	O
#Dutch	B-ORG
Embassy	I-ORG
,	O
#Kyiv	B-LOC
|	O
EMPR	O
Photo	O
#MH17	O
#RussiaAttacksUkraine	O
http://t.co/qMEduprGTd	O

I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
why	O
some	O
ppl	O
are	O
blaming	O
MAS	B-ORG
for	O
this	O
incident	O
.	O
The	O
plane	O
was	O
shot	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
freaking	O
missile	O
!	O
How	O
stupid	O
can	O
u	O
be	O
?	O
#mh17	O

#MalaysiaAirlines	B-ORG
#MH17	O
crash	O
:	O
Australian	O
,	O
Korean	O
airlines	O
shifted	O
Ukrainian	O
flight	O
routes	O
months	O
ago	O
http://t.co/pYVEW2zsoF	O

How	O
local	O
and	O
global	O
#frontpages	O
are	O
covering	O
the	O
#MH17	O
tragedy	O
http://t.co/TVcvMhkEwS	O
http://t.co/NRotFia7ns	O

Readout	O
of	O
President	O
Obama	B-PER
's	O
Call	O
with	O
President	O
Poroshenko	B-PER
of	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
http://t.co/Ac33lag8Z4	O
#MH17	O

'	O
Unspeakable	O
crime	O
'	O
Graphic	O
:	O
#MH17's	O
last	O
flight	O
http://t.co/r2UTIRQGmG	O
http://t.co/kR2jTLdzqm	O

Ukrainian	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
releases	O
unconfirmed	O
audio	O
purportedly	O
of	O
pro-	B-ORG
Russian	I-ORG
separatists	I-ORG
discussing	O
#MH17:	O
http://t.co/sR2jw9JSjf	O

.	O
@	B-ORG
SingaporeAir	B-ORG
flight	O
SQ	O
351	O
was	O
just	O
25km	O
from	O
last	O
recorded	O
position	O
of	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/DLOReJkmue	O
http://t.co/6pu5tCKMw6	O

Deeply	O
impressed	O
by	O
spontaneous	O
memorial	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
our	O
Mission	O
for	O
victims	O
#MH17	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
#NewYork	B-LOC
citizens	O
.	O
http://t.co/eysuhzFTYC	O

Powerful	O
language	O
towards	O
Russia	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
morning	O
editions	O
of	O
English	O
tabloids	O
.	O
#Ukraine	B-LOC
#MH17	O
http://t.co/DoIm5AGmVw	O

Doa	O
pramugara	O
#MH17:	O
“	O
Arwah	O
ada	O
cakap	O
masa	O
insiden	O
MH	O
370	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
flight	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/pAN05oofXE	O

MORE	O
:	O
Emergency	O
service	O
workers	O
in	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
combing	O
through	O
debris	O
at	O
#MH17	O
crash	O
site	O
http://t.co/W7R4kui8v0	O
http://t.co/QGS4sivSAT	O

The	O
black	O
box	O
from	O
Flight	O
MH	O
17	O
has	O
reportedly	O
been	O
found	O
!	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/fR1IiLPuEA	O

READ	O
:	O
Najib	B-PER
's	O
statement	O
on	O
the	O
deal	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
agreed	O
upon	O
just	O
moments	O
ago	O
.	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/gvYZwEOg1R	O

Shrapnel	O
damage	O
suggests	O
SA-	O
11	O
proximity	O
frag	O
warhead	O
may	O
have	O
exploded	O
slightly	O
below	O
and	O
ahead	O
of	O
#MH17's	O
port	O
wing	O
http://t.co/27bceCkacD	O

Incredible	O
satellite	O
images	O
of	O
the	O
#MH17	O
crash	O
site	O
,	O
courtesy	O
of	O
Airbus	B-ORG
DS	I-ORG
|	O
AllSource	B-ORG
Analysis	I-ORG
(	O
h	O
/	O
t	O
@	B-PER
LMartinezABC	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/ehvMGy4UIE	O

The	B-LOC
Netherlands	I-LOC
,	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
only	O
country	O
where	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
a	O
debate	O
about	O
whether	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
national	O
day	O
of	O
mourning	O
.	O
#MH17	O

'	O
Obama	B-PER
blamed	O
#Russia	B-LOC
with	O
no	O
evidence	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
propaganda	O
'	O
-	O
fmr	O
Kremlin	O
advisor	O
#MH17	O
#Ukraine	B-LOC
https://t.co/pJtlwv6U8c	O
http://t.co/gj3IkbEUbL	O

Football	O
fans	O
unite	O
for	O
#MH17	O
victims	O
http://t.co/NG6Y33yoxa	O
http://t.co/DvDDYaF9e7	O

Russian	O
military	O
laid	O
out	O
its	O
data	O
on	O
#MH17	O
which	O
BBC	B-ORG
chose	O
to	O
report	O
on	O
in	O
Russian	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
Impartiality	O
?	O
http://t.co/RUIqpI4PBu	O

Malaysians	O
all	O
leave	O
room	O
with	O
Borodai	B-PER
and	O
return	O
to	O
their	O
half-eaten	O
dinners	O
.	O
None	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
black	O
boxes	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
#MH17	B-ORG

Watch	O
as	O
BBC	B-ORG
reporter	O
is	O
handed	O
#MH17	O
victim	O
's	O
wallet	O
in	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
http://t.co/Mpn9QBdjiM	O

Borodai	O
walks	O
into	O
hotel	O
lobby	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
a	O
cigarette	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
negotiate	O
with	O
the	O
Malaysians	O
here	O
#MH17	O

Ukraine	B-LOC
's	O
pro-	O
Russia	B-LOC
rebels	O
hand	O
over	O
Malaysia	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
#MH17's	O
black	O
boxes	O
http://t.co/sWs4wDau3m	O
http://t.co/9GyZCurIkM	O

#MH17:	O
New	B-ORG
York	I-ORG
Times	I-ORG
praises	O
PM	O
Najib	B-PER
for	O
brokering	O
deal	O
to	O
recover	O
black	O
boxes	O
,	O
remains	O
of	O
victims	O
and	O
secure	O
safe	O
access	O
to	O
crash	O
site	O

#MH17:	O
Six	O
members	O
of	O
one	O
Malaysian	O
family	O
mourned	O
-	O
video	O
http://t.co/0akvRxF3Yn	O
http://t.co/L9f4jNgAyE	O

#AssholeOfTheDay	O
Rebel	O
commander	O
Igor	B-PER
Girkin	I-PER
,	O
for	O
claiming	O
passengers	O
on	O
#MH17	O
were	O
already	O
dead	O
when	O
he	O
shot	O
it	O
down	O
http://t.co/FA2Xh12EjZ	O

Families	O
and	O
friends	O
were	O
sitting	O
together	O
on	O
#MH17.	O
See	O
their	O
stories	O
with	O
our	O
seat	O
map	O
:	O
http://t.co/1k2SkaDo5b	O
http://t.co/tRmHlHepbh	O

"	O
We	O
're	O
very	O
appreciative	O
ofthe	O
Malaysian	B-ORG
government	I-ORG
's	O
position	O
that	O
is	O
neutral	O
&	O
not	O
blaming	O
anyone	O
.	O
"	O
Russia	B-LOC
envoy	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/0NaCAKQ5C6	O

Australia	B-LOC
's	O
seat	O
on	O
UN	B-ORG
Security	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
was	O
a	O
big	O
joke	O
to	O
conservatives	O
.	O
Remember	O
that	O
,	O
Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
?	O
#MH17	O
#auspol	O
http://t.co/pOAmuHVWCp	O

Awkward	O
moment	O
when	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
media	O
baron	O
and	O
everyone	O
remembers	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
#MH17	O
#SecurityCouncil	B-ORG
http://t.co/0q5LyRuePI	O

Proud	O
of	O
our	O
Foreign	O
Minister	O
Timmermans	B-PER
at	O
#UNSC	B-ORG
and	O
his	O
heartbraking	O
speech	O
about	O
the	O
#MH17	O
flight	O
https://t.co/iHhZnqZcHb	O
#bringthemhome	O

10	O
more	O
questions	O
Russian	O
military	O
pose	O
to	O
#Ukraine,	O
#US	O
over	O
#MH17	O
crash	O
http://t.co/5r9d2yd7DI	O
http://t.co/edMPUZMM3A	O

Protestors	O
gathering	O
outside	O
Russian	B-LOC
embassy	O
in	O
Kuala	B-LOC
Lumpur	I-LOC
.	O
For	O
most	O
,	O
the	O
answer	O
to	O
below	O
question	O
is	O
"	O
No	O
"	O
#mh17	O
http://t.co/3ufw381C4f	O

Heartbreaking	O
.	O
Dutch	O
father	O
writes	O
open	O
letter	O
to	O
“	O
murderers	O
”	O
of	O
daughter	O
after	O
#MH17	O
tragedy	O
.	O
http://t.co/t1jRaobesK	O
http://t.co/FbkfdQFiTi	O

POTUS	B-PER
msg	O
to	O
Dutch	O
ppl	O
after	O
signing	O
condolence	O
book	O
:	O
"	O
Will	O
not	O
rest	O
until	O
we	O
're	O
certain	O
that	O
justice	O
is	O
done	O
.	O
"	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/BcmSqvqwJU	O

Imagine	O
if	O
Obama	B-PER
offered	O
the	O
same	O
condolences	O
to	O
Gazans	O
that	O
he	O
just	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Dutch	O
victims	O
of	O
#MH17	O

U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
to	O
reveal	O
intelligence	O
today	O
that	O
supports	O
claims	O
that	O
missile	O
that	O
downed	O
#MH17	O
came	O
from	O
separatist-controlled	O
area	O
:	O
State	B-ORG
Dept	I-ORG
.	O

U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
Admits	O
Its	O
#MH17	O
‘	O
Evidence	O
’	O
is	O
Based	O
on	O
YouTube	B-ORG
Clips	O
&	O
Social	O
Media	O
Posts	O
-	O
http://t.co/6jsjFq4ZWs	O

Crash	O
site	O
in	O
Rozsypne	B-LOC
,	O
day	O
six	O
.	O
Almost	O
want	O
to	O
put	O
caution	O
tape	O
around	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/OgnEJwZNN6	O

Heartwarming	O
to	O
see	O
Leader	O
of	O
the	O
Opposition	O
@	B-PER
anwaribrahim	B-PER
convey	O
clear	O
understanding	O
and	O
support	O
of	O
PM	O
@	B-PER
NajibRazak	B-PER
's	O
handling	O
of	O
#MH17.	O

Tragically	O
,	O
her	O
son	O
didn	O
’	O
t	O
want	O
to	O
fly	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
of	O
two	O
#MH17	O
victims	O
tells	O
of	O
her	O
regrets	O
:	O
http://t.co/Ho0LmvZHN3	O
http://t.co/K2KIDWvUFy	O

I	O
want	O
to	O
wish	O
Selamat	O
Hari	O
Jadi	O
to	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
@	B-PER
NajibRazak	B-PER
.	O
Thank	O
u	O
for	O
spending	O
it	O
on	O
d	O
#MH17	O
tragedy	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
nation	O
.	O
Respect	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O

In	O
our	O
latest	O
dispatch	O
,	O
we	O
witness	O
contamination	O
at	O
the	O
#MH17	O
site	O
:	O
http://t.co/v7o5A0noP0	O
http://t.co/xYTM6oao5I	O

Despite	O
#MH17	O
and	O
#MH370	O
disasters	O
,	O
Malaysia	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
reports	O
no	O
surge	O
in	O
ticket	O
cancellations	O
http://t.co/DZIE081b5z	O

Hari	O
Raya	O
Card	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
location	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
heartbreaking	O
.	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/spJglEpUmC	O

At	O
Eindhoven	B-LOC
airbase	I-LOC
I	O
think	O
we	O
are	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
moment	O
when	O
the	O
passengers	O
of	O
#MH17	O
are	O
afforded	O
the	O
respect	O
and	O
dignity	O
they	O
deserve	O
.	O

Parents	O
who	O
lost	O
3	O
children	O
on	O
#MH17:	O
"	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
hell	O
beyond	O
hell	O
"	O
http://t.co/zRfQ7aCQXD	O
http://t.co/OT05cF8jIQ	O

1	O
minute	O
of	O
silence	O
in	O
our	O
studio	O
.	O
Today	O
our	O
thoughts	O
are	O
with	O
the	O
victims	O
of	O
flight	O
#mh17	O
http://t.co/SrhIpz6cdL	O

We	O
journalists	O
usually	O
are	O
not	O
overly	O
sentimental	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
admit	O
there	O
are	O
tears	O
in	O
my	O
eyes	O
as	O
I	O
watch	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
#MH17	O
victims	O
on	O
TV	O

Holland	B-LOC
holds	O
moment	O
of	O
silence	O
for	O
#MH17	O
dead	O
as	O
planes	O
carrying	O
remains	O
land	O
in	O
Eindhoven	B-LOC
:	O
http://t.co/PPdykSCczW	O
http://t.co/dAlSUH2Tkq	O

Dutch	O
King	O
,	O
Queen	O
&	O
PM	O
Mark	B-PER
Rutte	I-PER
wait	O
to	O
receive	O
first	O
coffins	O
of	O
victims	O
from	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/XCNjJKfCCo	O
http://t.co/oQ7RARBQXa	O

The	O
solemnity	O
of	O
#MH17	O
coffins	O
arrival	O
contrasted	O
with	O
traumatic	O
images	O
from	O
crash	O
scene	O
.	O
A	O
nation	O
breathes	O
again	O

#MH17	O
What	O
a	O
horrifying	O
scene	O
#EIndhoven	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
.	O
The	O
worst	O
plane	O
crash	O
disaster	O
ever	O
because	O
of	O
an	O
awfull	O
"	O
mistake	O
"	O
http://t.co/QZw0vMQzRE	O

Procession	O
underway	O
for	O
40	O
Flight	O
#MH17	O
victims	O
http://t.co/a1yRrJrtmH	O

In	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
love	O
will	O
always	O
prevail	O
.	O
In	O
memory	O
of	O
those	O
affected	O
by	O
the	O
#MH17	O
disaster	O
.	O
http://t.co/76I6ikQFt0	O

Dutch	O
air	O
accident	O
investigators	O
find	O
no	O
evidence	O
that	O
#MH17's	O
black	O
boxes	O
have	O
been	O
tampered	O
with	O
http://t.co/EzmlhiS5Ap	O

Ukraine	B-LOC
rebel	O
commander	O
Alexander	B-PER
Khodakovsky	I-PER
acknowledges	O
fighters	O
had	O
BUK	O
missile	O
#MH17	O
http://t.co/coLMEIN4UU	O
http://t.co/D0k30M21SO	O

The	O
#Dutch	O
are	O
giving	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
a	O
lesson	O
in	O
class	O
,	O
dignity	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
to	O
truly	O
respect	O
the	O
victims	O
of	O
#MH17	O
#Netherlands	B-LOC
#Holland	I-LOC

