Millions	O
of	O
family-run	O
#farms	O
hold	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
global	O
#hunger	O
reveals	O
#UN	B-ORG
report	O
.	O
http://t.co/9JKaxcMKJ0	O

Cousin	O
of	O
Reeva	B-PER
Steenkamp	I-PER
says	O
#Pistorius	B-PER
should	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
.	O
http://t.co/7gSdzwFjJ6	O

ICYMI	O
,	O
@	B-ORG
4corners	B-ORG
has	O
put	O
together	O
this	O
@	B-ORG
flipboard	B-ORG
magazine	O
for	O
their	O
program	O
'	O
Fat	O
Chance	O
'	O
https://t.co/t88BgE2ctL	O
http://t.co/sNoxagolWh	O

Returning	O
to	O
Kobane	B-LOC
:	O
18yo	O
woman	O
fleeing	O
Islamic	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
detained	O
by	O
Turkish	B-LOC
authorities	O
,	O
then	O
ejected	O
into	O
warzone	O
http://t.co/auzJPJeCKh	O

CFMEU	B-ORG
whistleblowers	O
claim	O
they	O
were	O
bullied	O
after	O
raising	O
corruption	O
concerns	O
with	O
union	O
chiefs	O
http://t.co/ABydsImHqi	O

Exercising	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
week	O
cuts	O
depression	O
risk	O
by	O
16	O
per	O
cent	O
,	O
scientists	O
find	O
http://t.co/srRFokVuU8	O
http://t.co/J7axF8skJL	O

Coles	B-ORG
taken	O
to	O
court	O
by	O
ACCC	B-ORG
for	O
allegedly	O
bullying	O
suppliers	O
to	O
boost	O
earnings	O
http://t.co/rh3L8ibGZA	O

Australia	B-LOC
unlikely	O
to	O
send	O
medics	O
to	O
West	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
to	O
fight	O
#Ebola	O
http://t.co/d26DKdhz9Z	O

Category	O
Three	O
Hurricane	O
Gonzalo	O
threatens	O
to	O
deluge	O
Bermuda	B-LOC
,	O
Bahamas	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
could	O
wreak	O
'	O
devastating	O
damage	O
'	O
http://t.co/Ntx3TdpSi6	O

Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
'	O
very	O
reluctant	O
'	O
to	O
send	O
Australians	B-LOC
to	O
#Ebola	O
hotspots	O
http://t.co/x5Do181Lht	O

Ten	B-ORG
Network	I-ORG
declares	O
major	O
full-year	O
loss	O
of	O
$	O
168	O
million	O
as	O
advertising	O
revenue	O
stalls	O
http://t.co/DkH7rHKWmn	O

Neil	B-PER
Patrick	I-PER
Harris	I-PER
to	O
host	O
2015	O
Academy	O
Awards	O
ceremony	O
http://t.co/FJEbuomnyZ	O

Japanese	O
cuisine	O
'	O
under	O
attack	O
'	O
from	O
Western	O
food	O
;	O
chefs	O
fight	O
back	O
with	O
school	O
programs	O
http://t.co/oFGiRLUDIx	O
http://t.co/4WrDJebDIK	O

Global	O
markets	O
slump	O
as	O
Wall	B-LOC
Street	I-LOC
's	O
volatility	O
index	O
jumps	O
to	O
highest	O
level	O
since	O
2011	O
http://t.co/GiqeFjMaEm	O

Baby	B-PER
Ferouz	I-PER
's	O
family	O
to	O
fight	O
visa	O
refusal	O
http://t.co/PWwnNHK02P	O

U	B-ORG
2	I-ORG
frontman	O
Bono	B-PER
says	O
'	O
Oops	O
,	O
sorry	O
'	O
for	O
U	B-ORG
2	I-ORG
album	O
download	O
debacle	O
after	O
complaints	O
by	O
Apple	B-ORG
iTunes	O
users	O
http://t.co/6VVSh766r0	O

Pentagon	B-LOC
says	O
IS	B-ORG
fighters	O
still	O
threaten	O
Kobane	B-LOC
,	O
despite	O
hundreds	O
killed	O
in	O
US-led	O
air	O
strikes	O
http://t.co/yzf2d1obgL	O

US	B-LOC
astronauts	O
race	O
the	O
clock	O
on	O
spacewalk	O
to	O
make	O
repairs	O
to	O
International	B-LOC
Space	I-LOC
Station	I-LOC
http://t.co/s5Fwu7h6DX	O

Salmonella	O
food	O
poisoning	O
cases	O
increasing	O
despite	O
education	O
campaigns	O
:	O
ANU	B-ORG
study	O
http://t.co/RcyM35giLv	O
http://t.co/U17fV7kHIr	O

Sacked	O
Liberal	B-PER
adviser	O
Don	B-PER
Coulson	I-PER
makes	O
MP	O
porn	O
ring	O
allegations	O
http://t.co/q730zRPTiC	O

China	B-LOC
's	O
influence	O
over	O
Australian	O
Chinese-language	O
media	O
outlets	O
growing	O
,	O
analysts	O
say	O
http://t.co/yFsxUOoHe3	O

Good	O
morning	O
Twitter	B-ORG
,	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
fantastic	O
Thursday	O
.	O

South	B-LOC
Australian	I-LOC
jockey	O
Caitlin	B-PER
Forrest	I-PER
killed	O
after	O
fall	O
at	O
Murray	B-LOC
Bridge	I-LOC
race	O
http://t.co/7Z7SWo7uwm	O

Cousin	O
tells	O
Oscar	B-PER
Pistorius	I-PER
sentencing	O
hearing	O
Steenkamp	O
family	O
'	O
ruined	O
'	O
by	O
Reeva	B-PER
's	O
death	O
http://t.co/ogULNMfDNs	O

Philippines	O
police	O
file	O
charges	O
against	O
US	B-ORG
Marine	O
over	O
death	O
of	O
transgender	O
woman	O
http://t.co/dX6oM9nWDT	O

Liberal	O
senators	O
are	O
urging	O
the	O
Government	B-ORG
against	O
buying	O
Australia	B-LOC
's	O
next	O
generation	O
of	O
submarines	O
from	O
overseas	O
http://t.co/Un5T7qTUu7	O

The	O
Federal	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG
is	O
resisting	O
internal	O
pressure	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
national	O
sex	O
offenders	O
register	O
http://t.co/7EtdAAUsck	O

Nicola	B-PER
Sturgeon	I-PER
to	O
replace	O
Alexander	B-PER
Salmond	I-PER
as	O
leader	O
of	O
Scottish	B-ORG
Nationalist	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG
and	O
country	O
's	O
first	O
minister	O
http://t.co/mHtMeEwz1k	O

ADF	B-ORG
personnel	O
among	O
'	O
best	O
paid	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
'	O
,	O
Vice	O
Chief	O
says	O
as	O
tribunal	O
defers	O
pay	O
deal	O
decision	O
http://t.co/WH0LbnsWGh	O

Concern	O
post-traumatic	O
stress	O
leading	O
to	O
an	O
increase	O
in	O
number	O
of	O
veterans	O
in	O
prison	O
@abc730	O
http://t.co/U6Tox0KAXb	O

#BREAKING:	O
A	O
second	O
health	O
care	O
worker	O
at	O
Texas	B-LOC
Health	I-LOC
Presbyterian	I-LOC
Hospital	I-LOC
has	O
tested	O
positive	O
for	O
#Ebola	O

WorkCover	B-ORG
finds	O
loose-fill	O
#asbestos	O
in	O
#Sydney	B-LOC
homes	O
for	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
more	O
positive	O
tests	O
in	O
city	O
likely	O
http://t.co/txwrocC6mC	O

Man	O
#bookerprize	B-ORG
winner	O
Richard	B-PER
Flanagan	I-PER
'	O
ashamed	O
to	O
be	O
Australian	B-LOC
'	O
http://t.co/Rt7JsNAwnb	O

Heavy	O
snowfall	O
on	O
Nepal	B-LOC
's	O
Annapurna	B-LOC
trekking	O
route	O
kills	O
four	O
,	O
leaves	O
more	O
than	O
100	O
missing	O
http://t.co/IHjuOcSErn	O

Hong	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC
tension	O
rises	O
as	O
police	O
officers	O
suspended	O
over	O
beating	O
of	O
protester	O
caught	O
on	O
film	O
http://t.co/rxevPAbq2U	O

University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
NSW	I-ORG
students	O
drive	O
#Sunswift	O
solar	O
car	O
into	O
the	O
record	O
books	O
http://t.co/6msMQtfaU9	O
http://t.co/pDcVyK3MjV	O

North	B-LOC
and	I-LOC
South	I-LOC
Korea	I-LOC
hold	O
'	O
high-level	O
military	O
talks	O
'	O
amid	O
heightened	O
tensions	O
on	O
Korean	B-LOC
Peninsula	I-LOC
http://t.co/GIiGHzcdG8	O

Riverina	B-LOC
farmers	O
'	O
confused	O
'	O
by	O
NSW	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG
water	O
allocation	O
as	O
dam	O
levels	O
strong	O
http://t.co/zbKFcPKLV3	O

Moranbah	B-LOC
's	O
housing	O
market	O
collapses	O
,	O
businesses	O
struggle	O
as	O
coal	O
prices	O
remain	O
depressed	O
http://t.co/UhT66NQmh5	O

Back	O
Story	O
:	O
Kumi	B-PER
Taguchi	I-PER
(	O
@	B-PER
kumitaguchi	B-PER
)	O
reflects	O
after	O
reporting	O
on	O
PTSD	O
experienced	O
by	O
returned	O
soldiers	O
http://t.co/1v4VNsDj67	O

#Doping	O
in	O
#sport:	O
Olympic	O
athletes	O
,	O
teams	O
divided	O
on	O
merit	O
of	O
proposed	O
expansion	O
to	O
ASADA	B-ORG
's	O
powers	O
http://t.co/FQfkA9SZh2	O

Catholic	B-ORG
Church	I-ORG
offered	O
MOU	O
on	O
child	O
abuse	O
despite	O
mandatory	O
reporting	O
laws	O
,	O
Police	B-ORG
Integrity	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG
hears	O
http://t.co/pQgah0a0ra	O

#Geelong	B-LOC
to	O
trial	O
program	O
allowing	O
corporations	O
to	O
partner	O
with	O
schools	O
,	O
Christopher	B-PER
Pyne	I-PER
says	O
http://t.co/29NWx8G9gA	O

Back	O
Story	O
:	O
Anna	B-PER
Henderson	I-PER
(	O
@	B-PER
annajhenderson	B-PER
)	O
goes	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
with	O
the	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
in	O
Arnhem	B-LOC
Land	I-LOC
http://t.co/mMHWF2XUF5	O

Australian	B-LOC
special	O
forces	O
troops	O
could	O
move	O
into	O
#Iraq	B-LOC
'	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
few	O
days	O
'	O
,	O
Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
says	O
http://t.co/SvW4Q9CzM6	O

Composer	O
@	B-PER
TimMinchin	B-PER
says	O
Roald	B-PER
Dahl	I-PER
's	O
Matilda	B-PER
'	O
has	O
been	O
"	O
the	O
most	O
incredible	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
"	O
http://t.co/mtm0knWbfq	O
via	O
@BreakfastNews	O

MP	O
Bruce	B-PER
Flegg	I-PER
sues	O
former	O
media	O
adviser	O
for	O
claiming	O
he	O
was	O
unfit	O
for	O
ministry	O
:	O
http://t.co/sOd8ccIDES	O

Islamic	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
fighter	O
and	O
former	O
Brisbane	B-ORG
Council	I-ORG
worker	O
Zia	B-PER
Abdul	I-PER
Haq	I-PER
killed	O
after	O
travelling	O
to	O
Syria	B-LOC
:	O
http://t.co/8yKNptsnPm	O

#Facebook	B-ORG
and	O
#Apple	B-ORG
offer	O
$	O
20	O
,	O
000	O
to	O
freeze	O
eggs	O
for	O
female	O
staff	O
:	O
http://t.co/wiDjc2Qsds	O

Tasmanian	B-PER
Government	O
names	O
Macquarie	B-ORG
Point	I-ORG
as	O
a	O
preferred	O
southern	O
woodchip	O
port	O
:	O
http://t.co/NX8BDjHkx4	O

US	B-LOC
pop	O
star	O
Kesha	B-PER
sues	O
music	O
producer	O
Dr	B-PER
Luke	I-PER
for	O
'	O
years	O
of	O
sexual	O
and	O
emotional	O
abuse	O
'	O
:	O
http://t.co/viWMwDeF1s	O

PNG	B-LOC
's	O
national	O
broadcaster	O
increases	O
security	O
after	O
three	O
female	O
staff	O
members	O
kidnapped	O
and	O
assaulted	O
:	O
http://t.co/2EQ7TpwQUG	O

Christian	B-ORG
Brothers	I-ORG
member	O
Peter	B-PER
Standen	I-PER
faces	O
more	O
indecent	O
assault	O
charges	O
in	O
Goulburn	B-LOC
Court	I-LOC
:	O
http://t.co/WKBtlxkDir	O

At	O
6pm	O
a	O
full	O
wrap	O
from	O
Day	O
1	O
of	O
the	O
Luke	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
inquest	O
.	O
Rosie	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
's	O
testimony	O
,	O
her	O
torment	O
&	O
her	O
wish	O
for	O
all	O
parents	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

#Adelaide	B-LOC
to	O
hit	O
37	O
C	O
and	O
severe	O
fire	O
danger	O
ratings	O
for	O
parts	O
of	O
SA	B-LOC
tomorrow	O
.	O
More	O
details	O
on	O
#pmagenda	O
tonight	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
(	O
Ben	B-PER
_	O
Domensin	B-PER

About	O
to	O
chat	O
with	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
and	O
@	B-PER
jamesmassola	B-PER
on	O
#fairwarning	O
(	O
@	B-PER
chriskkenny	B-PER
)	O

Aaron	B-PER
Connelly	I-PER
from	O
Lowy	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
discusses	O
the	O
new	O
Indonesian	B-LOC
President	O
"	O
Jokowi	B-PER
"	O
next	O
on	O
#pmagenda	O
(	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
)	O

@	B-PER
MathiasCormann	B-PER
plays	O
down	O
fears	O
privatised	O
Medibank	B-ORG
Private	I-ORG
will	O
increase	O
premiums	O
.	O
Govt	O
will	O
still	O
regulate	O
.	O
#pmagenda	O
(	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
)	O

up	O
next	O
on	O
#pmagenda	O
committee	O
chair	O
@	B-PER
DanTehanWannon	B-PER
discusses	O
how	O
to	O
improve	O
Foreign	O
Fighters	O
bill	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
)	O

Thanks	O
for	O
all	O
ur	O
support	O
guys	O
.	O
Please	O
follow	O
Paul	B-PER
's	O
personal	O
account	O
@	B-ORG
PMOnAir	B-ORG
&	O
our	O
super-producer	O
@	B-PER
skidner	B-PER
.	O
See	O
u	O
tonight	O
on	O
(	O
@pm_live	O
)	O

Should	O
we	O
reserve	O
some	O
gas	O
for	O
domestic	O
use	O
in	O
Australia	B-LOC
?	O
Next	O
on	O
#pmagenda	O
(	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
)	O

Join	O
me	O
&	O
@	B-ORG
vanOnselenP	B-ORG
for	O
QT	B-ORG
analysis	O
once	O
it	O
finishes	O
.	O
(	O
Not	O
sure	O
we	O
chose	O
the	O
most	O
exciting	O
day	O
to	O
start	O
this	O
)	O
.	O
#pmagenda	O
(	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
)	O

From	O
today	O
,	O
#pmagenda	O
will	O
begin	O
straight	O
after	O
QT	O
on	O
sitting	O
days	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
David_Speers	B-PER
)	O

A	O
comet	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
mountain	O
has	O
whizzed	O
past	O
Mars	B-LOC
in	O
a	O
once-in-a-million-years	O
encounter	O
!	O
https://t.co/zUGybtriKk	O

2	O
men	O
accused	O
of	O
killing	O
a	O
Brisbane	B-LOC
mother	O
&	O
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
40	O
years	O
ago	O
will	O
remain	O
behind	O
bars	O
until	O
Nov	O
24	O
#mcculkin	B-PER
(	O
@	B-PER
liztilley84	B-PER
)	O

PM	O
Abbott	B-PER
arrived	O
at	O
inauguration	O
of	O
Indonesian	O
President-elect	O
Joko	B-PER
Widodo	I-PER
(	O
@	B-PER
Dan_Bourchier	B-PER
)	O

#SHOWBIZ	O
interviews	O
fashion	O
legend	O
&	O
@AusNextTopModel	O
Guest	O
judge	O
@	B-PER
JPGaultier	B-PER
http://t.co/M16q2ABdTF	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Shellz_Zee	B-PER
)	O

#SHOWBIZ	O
interviews	O
fashion	O
legend	O
&	O
#ANTM	O
Guest	O
judge	O
Jean	B-PER
Paul	I-PER
Gautlier	I-PER
http://t.co/M16q2ABdTF	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Shellz_Zee	B-PER
)	O

AGENDA	O
Australia	B-LOC
ready	O
to	O
help	O
neighbours	O
http://t.co/A6FFW2cwQX	O
via	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Kieran_Gilbert	B-PER
)	O

Brendan	B-PER
O	I-PER
'	I-PER
Connor	I-PER
on	O
girly	O
man	O
,	O
"	O
dickhead	O
"	O
and	O
border	O
protection	O
#Viewpoint	O
http://t.co/dxwMfiQnIu	O
via	O
(	O
@	B-PER
chriskkenny	B-PER
)	O

On	O
political	O
eunuchs	O
-	O
#Viewpoint	O
Editorial	O
,	O
October	O
19	O
http://t.co/QzorlofzKC	O
via	O
(	O
@	B-PER
chriskkenny	B-PER
)	O

Average	O
households	O
in	O
major	O
cities	O
can	O
expect	O
gas	O
bills	O
to	O
soar	O
by	O
hundreds	O
of	O
dollars	O
a	O
year	O
http://t.co/q1aCXg9Ews	O
http://t.co/e0lCCT1qsP	O

QLD	B-LOC
health	O
warns	O
of	O
measles	O
exposure	O
for	O
passengers	O
flying	O
Jetstar	B-ORG
Brisbane	B-LOC
to	O
Denpasar	B-LOC
JQ	O
46	O
on	O
Wed	O
15	O
Oct	O
-	O
3	O
people	O
infected	O
(	O
brookewylie	B-PER

Kerry	B-PER
Stokes	I-PER
just	O
then	O
on	O
What	O
a	O
touching	O
story	O
about	O
the	O
VC	O
widow	O
.	O
Good	O
man	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
chriskkenny	B-PER
)	O

Kerry	B-PER
Stokes	I-PER
speaking	O
live	O
on	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
launch	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
book	O
about	O
his	O
life	O
-	O
"	O
The	O
boy	O
from	O
nowhere	O
"	O
(	O
@	B-PER
ash_gillon	B-PER
)	O

Rosie	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
is	O
due	O
shortly	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
witness	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
coronial	O
inquest	O
into	O
her	O
son	O
's	O
death	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
live	O
tweeting	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Coroner	B-PER
will	O
examine	O
roles	O
played	O
by	O
Vic	B-LOC
Dept	O
of	O
Human	O
Services	O
,	O
@	B-ORG
VictoriaPolice	B-ORG
and	O
Rosie	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
in	O
protecting	O
#lukebatty	B-PER
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Inquest	O
told	O
Greg	B-PER
Anderson	I-PER
emptied	O
his	O
belongings	O
including	O
a	O
large	O
knife	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
before	O
going	O
to	O
Tyabb	B-LOC
Oval	I-LOC
#LukeBatty	B-PER
(	O
@SimoLove	O
)	O

Coronial	O
inquest	O
told	O
an	O
8	O
yo	O
boy	O
in	O
Luke	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
's	O
cricket	O
team	O
witnessed	O
Greg	B-PER
Anderson	I-PER
smack	O
Luke	B-PER
to	O
ground	O
with	O
cricket	O
bat	O
(	O
@SimoLove	O
)	O

Coronial	O
Inquest	O
told	O
Luke	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
's	O
father	O
threatened	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
10	O
months	O
before	O
his	O
death	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

President-elect	O
Joko	B-PER
Widodo	I-PER
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
in	O
here	O
at	O
Indonesian	B-LOC
Parliament	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Details	O
soon	O
http://t.co/XftCQy8I0U	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Dan_Bourchier	B-PER
)	O

Security	O
is	O
tight	O
at	O
Indonesia	B-LOC
Parliament	I-LOC
for	O
the	O
inauguration	O
of	O
Joko	B-PER
Widodo	I-PER
http://t.co/yiChshCgwi	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Dan_Bourchier	B-PER
)	O

Deal	O
made	O
to	O
deploy	O
Australian	B-LOC
troops	O
to	O
#Iraq	B-LOC
More	O
here	O
:	O
http://t.co/GeCbP1Rt83	O
http://t.co/zKTx3jfsAN	O

The	O
McDonalds	B-LOC
restaurant	O
in	O
Swanston	B-LOC
St	I-LOC
where	O
a	O
15yo	O
was	O
attacked	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
http://t.co/iRt9QhT0J9	O
(	O
@	B-PER
AhronYoung	B-PER
)	O

Indonesia	B-LOC
prepares	O
for	O
new	O
president	O
.	O
Details	O
soon	O
.	O
@	B-PER
Kieran_Gilbert	B-PER
#indopol	O
#auspol	O
#indonesiavotes	B-LOC
(	O
@	B-PER
Dan_Bourchier	B-PER
)	O

Good	O
morning	O
SA-	B-LOC
Stay	O
hydrated	O
,	O
today	O
is	O
day	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
#Heatwave!	O
For	O
#Adelaide	B-LOC
34	O
C	O
=	O
is	O
12	O
C	O
above	O
the	O
Oct	O
avg	O
.	O
@	B-ORG
SkyWeatherAUS	B-ORG
(	O
@	B-PER
Samdawson01	B-PER
)	O

Another	O
person	O
assaulted	O
outside	O
a	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
McDonalds	I-LOC
restaurant	I-LOC
-	O
a	O
15yo	O
recovering	O
in	O
hospital	B-LOC
with	O
a	O
broken	O
nose	O
(	O
@	B-PER
AhronYoung	B-PER
)	O

Our	O
new	O
recruit	O
to	O
the	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
bureau	O
Jim	B-PER
Middleton	I-PER
is	O
about	O
to	O
report	O
on	O
the	O
PM	O
's	O
visit	O
to	O
Indonesia	B-LOC
.	O
Up	O
next	O
on	O
Sky	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
(	O
@	B-PER
AhronYoung	B-PER
)	O

Two	O
men	O
due	O
to	O
face	O
court	O
this	O
morning	O
charged	O
with	O
murder	O
over	O
a	O
cold	O
case	O
that	O
's	O
baffled	O
Queensland	B-LOC
police	O
for	O
40	O
years	O
(	O
@	B-PER
liztilley84	B-PER
)	O

Morning	O
:	O
200	O
Aust	B-ORG
special	I-ORG
forces	I-ORG
approved	O
to	O
advise	O
&	O
assist	O
Iraqi	B-LOC
troops	O
in	O
their	O
fight	O
against	O
IS	O
;	O
Widodo	B-PER
inauguration	O
(	O
@	B-PER
NinaBStevens	B-PER
)	O

Ca	O
n't	O
wait	O
for	O
a	O
fiery	O
#pmlive	O
w	O
/	O
@	B-PER
JasonMorrisonAU	B-PER
@	B-PER
greencate	B-PER
@	B-PER
georgiedent	B-PER
@	B-PER
Peter_Reith	B-PER
.	O
9pm	O
AEDT	O
http://t.co/WVeZVIVBLM	O
(	O
@PMOnAir	O
)	O

Bumper	O
#viewpoint	O
with	O
@	B-PER
Barnaby_Joyce	B-PER
and	O
@	B-PER
BOConnorMP	B-PER
plus	O
@	B-PER
samanthamaiden	B-PER
@	B-PER
mirandadevine	B-PER
and	O
girly	O
man	O
host	O
.	O
8pm	O
#auspol	O
(	O
@	B-PER
chriskkenny	B-PER
)	O

Indonesia	B-LOC
prepares	O
for	O
new	O
president	O
http://t.co/z5yWsMRRyn	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Dan_Bourchier	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
Wallabies	B-ORG
coach	O
Ewen	B-PER
McKenzie	I-PER
has	O
announced	O
he	O
resigned	O
from	O
his	O
position	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O

Trinity	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
statement	O
:	O
Joshua	B-PER
was	O
a	O
"	O
wonderful	O
student	O
&	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
's	O
sudden	O
passing	O
is	O
a	O
tremendous	O
shock	O
"	O
(	O
2	O
/	O
2	O
)	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Victim	O
of	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
fatal	O
bashing	O
identified	O
as	O
21yo	O
Trinity	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
student	O
Joshua	B-PER
Hardy	I-PER
,	O
originally	O
from	O
Darwin	B-LOC
(	O
1	O
/	O
2	O
)	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Tonight	O
,	O
I	O
interview	O
@QldSundayMail	O
editor	O
Peter	B-PER
Gleeson	I-PER
on	O
the	O
breakthrough	O
in	O
a	O
40	O
year	O
old	O
cold	O
case	O
triple	O
murder	O
(	O
@	B-PER
liztilley84	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
Police	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
into	O
custody	O
after	O
a	O
fatal	O
assault	O
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
this	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
second	O
man	O
is	O
also	O
assisting	O
police	O
.	O

Vic	B-ORG
Police	I-ORG
now	O
say	O
they	O
've	O
taken	O
a	O
27	O
year	O
old	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
man	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Manhunt	O
over	O
following	O
fatal	O
assault	O
this	O
morning	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Tonight	O
on	O
live	O
from	O
Brisbane	B-LOC
:	O
Police	O
solve	O
a	O
40	O
yold	O
cold	O
case	O
,	O
a	O
deadly	O
bashing	O
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
&	O
Putin	B-PER
to	O
cooperate	O
on	O
#MH17	O
(	O
@	B-PER
liztilley84	B-PER
)	O

BREAKING	O
1	O
man	O
has	O
come	O
forward	O
following	O
fatal	O
assault	O
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Police	O
say	O
he	O
's	O
"	O
assisting	O
with	O
inquiries	O
"	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

The	O
2	O
men	O
will	O
be	O
charged	O
with	O
murder	O
&	O
deprivation	O
of	O
liberty	O
#mcculkin	B-PER
#coldcase	O
(	O
@	B-PER
liztilley84	B-PER
)	O

Police	O
have	O
arrested	O
2	O
men	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
a	O
40	O
year	O
old	O
cold	O
case	O
involving	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Barbara	B-PER
McCulkin	I-PER
&	O
her	O
2	O
daughters	O
(	O
@	B-PER
liztilley84	B-PER
)	O

Hunt	O
continues	O
for	O
2	O
men	O
after	O
a	O
21	O
year	O
old	O
man	O
from	O
Yarraville	B-LOC
was	O
bashed	O
to	O
death	O
at	O
a	O
McDonalds	B-LOC
http://t.co/JG6XLEmnsf	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
Qld	B-LOC
police	O
have	O
arrested	O
two	O
men	O
over	O
the	O
deaths	O
of	O
a	O
Brisbane	B-LOC
mother	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
daughters	O
,	O
40	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O

How	O
prepared	O
is	O
Australia	B-LOC
for	O
an	O
Ebola	O
case	O
?	O
My	O
interview	O
with	O
infectious	O
diseases	O
expert	O
@	B-PER
sanj971	B-PER
http://t.co/rHUx9NMMWH	O
(	O
Vanessa	B-PER
_	O
Trezise	B-PER

Cormann	B-PER
labels	O
Shorten	B-PER
an	O
'	O
economic	O
girlie	O
man	O
'	O
http://t.co/lZN7G8dIcj	O
via	O
(	O
@	B-PER
lipporocks	B-PER
)	O

Replay	O
of	O
#saturdayagenda	O
on	O
now	O
(	O
@	B-PER
lipporocks	B-PER
)	O

More	O
CCTV	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
wanted	O
after	O
fatal	O
bashing	O
at	O
a	O
McDonalds	B-LOC
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
call	O
000	O
http://t.co/Z5GuAgZwUm	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

And	O
here	O
's	O
@	B-PER
edhusicMP	B-PER
urging	O
the	O
Cormannator	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
deodoriser	O
of	O
the	O
budget	O
stink	O
#saturdayagenda	O
http://t.co/SegV1JS0ki	O
(	O
@	B-ORG
lipporocks	B-ORG
)	O

Here	O
's	O
the	O
Cormannator	O
@	B-PER
MathiasCormann	B-PER
channelling	O
Arnold	B-PER
the	O
Governator	O
on	O
#saturdayagenda	O
http://t.co/eVTmP4aGP8	O
(	O
@	B-PER
lipporocks	B-PER
)	O

If	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
men	O
call	O
Triple	O
Zero	O
.	O
They	O
're	O
wanted	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
thrown	O
to	O
ground	O
&	O
kicked	O
fatally	O
http://t.co/SqO9fT9yZk	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

These	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
police	O
are	O
hunting	O
after	O
a	O
fatal	O
assault	O
outside	O
a	O
McDonalds	B-LOC
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
http://t.co/xMUl9rCkRt	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Cormann	B-PER
:	O
Bill	B-PER
Shorten	I-PER
is	O
an	O
economic	O
girly	O
man	O
.	O
#hereallysaidit	O
#arnold	B-PER
(	O
@	B-PER
lipporocks	B-PER
)	O

On	O
#satrudayagenda	O
shortly	O
Fin	O
Min	O
@	B-PER
MathiasCormann	B-PER
and	O
Parly	B-PER
Sec	I-PER
@	B-PER
edhusicMP	B-PER
#budget	O
#shirtfront	O
#ebola	O
(	O
@	B-PER
lipporocks	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
A	O
man	O
has	O
died	O
following	O
an	O
assault	O
outside	O
a	O
fast	O
food	O
restaurant	O
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
.	O

On	O
#FridayLive	O
Ebola	O
,	O
Iraq	B-LOC
,	O
Shirtfronts	O
,	O
PUP	B-ORG
and	O
prizes	O
.	O
@	B-PER
JacktheInsider	B-PER
@	B-PER
ali__clarke	B-PER
@	B-PER
SharriMarkson	B-PER
undercover	O
on	O
(	O
@	B-PER
chriskkenny	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
ASADA	B-ORG
has	O
issued	O
amended	O
'	O
show	O
cause	O
'	O
notices	O
to	O
34	O
former	O
and	O
current	O
Essendon	B-ORG
AFL	I-ORG
players	O
over	O
substance	O
use	O
.	O

Those	O
34	O
players	O
have	O
10	O
days	O
to	O
respond	O
to	O
the	O
notices	O
.	O
Each	O
notice	O
has	O
been	O
tailored	O
for	O
each	O
player	O
.	O
Some	O
are	O
350	O
pgs	O
long	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Breaking	O
:	O
ASADA	B-ORG
issues	O
amended	O
show-cause	O
notices	O
to	O
34	O
past	O
and	O
present	O
Essendon	B-ORG
FC	I-ORG
players	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

#KenCam	B-PER
on	O
now	O
-	O
tweet	O
Ross	B-PER
(	O
or	O
me	O
)	O
now	O
http://t.co/hW8J1gRJ2O	O
(	O
@	B-PER
KKeneally	B-PER
)	O

Australia	B-LOC
forces	O
have	O
killed	O
IS	O
militants	O
and	O
destroyed	O
their	O
facilities	O
on	O
at	O
least	O
two	O
bombing	O
raids	O
in	O
#Iraq	B-LOC
http://t.co/EetDmLm055	O

Exclusive	O
behind	O
the	O
scenes	O
planning	O
for	O
today	O
's	O
#KenCam	B-PER
on	O
-	O
starts	O
in	O
45	O
min	O
http://t.co/v4liGSIc1W	O
(	O
@	B-PER
KKeneally	B-PER
)	O

Labor	B-ORG
news	I-ORG
conference	O
with	O
@	B-PER
billshortenmp	B-PER
and	O
Mark	B-PER
Dreyfus	I-PER
LIVE	O
now	O
from	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
on	O
SKY	B-ORG
http://t.co/UXv3PZYonT	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

LIVE	O
NOW	O
on	O
@	B-ORG
APAC_ch648	B-ORG
Ian	B-PER
MacFarlane	I-PER
addressing	O
the	O
@	B-ORG
AmChamAU	B-ORG
Business	O
Luncheon	O
in	O
#Adelaide	B-LOC
(	O
@	B-PER
Staceylee_	B-PER
)	O

PM	O
defends	O
#Ebola	O
decision	O
More	O
here	O
:	O
http://t.co/Wdf5zVovhi	O
http://t.co/RkSAnDx6Ja	O

Virgin	B-ORG
buys	O
rest	O
of	O
Tiger	B-ORG
for	O
$	O
1	O
More	O
here	O
:	O
http://t.co/6HEOYVcWgD	O
http://t.co/xThL8UYH1d	O

It	O
's	O
#KenCam	B-PER
today	O
-	O
4pm	O
AEST	O
on	O
-	O
joining	O
us	O
on	O
panel	O
are	O
@	B-PER
JasonMorrisonAU	B-PER
and	O
@	B-PER
SamPCrosby	B-PER
-	O
tweet	O
your	O
#TeamAustralia	B-LOC
noms	O
(	O
@	B-PER
KKeneally	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
A	O
bi-partisan	O
committee	O
has	O
handed	O
down	O
its	O
report	O
on	O
foreign	O
fighters	O
legislation	O
with	O
36	O
recommendations	O
.	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Joint	B-ORG
Intelligence	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
tables	O
its	O
report	O
on	O
Foreign	O
Fighters	O
legislation	O
.	O
36	O
recommendations	O
.	O
More	O
on	O
(	O
@	B-PER
ljayes	B-PER
)	O

.	O
@	B-PER
TonyAbbottMHR	B-PER
:	O
My	O
message	O
to	O
the	O
Liberal	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
-	O
is	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
and	O
fight	O
#auspol	O

.	O
@	B-PER
TonyAbbottMHR	B-PER
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
play	O
politics	O
with	O
#Ebola	O
-	O
it	O
's	O
too	O
important	O
#auspol	O

.	O
@	B-PER
TonyAbbottMHR	B-PER
:	O
Without	O
proper	O
evacuation	O
plans	O
it	O
'd	O
be	O
reckless	O
to	O
send	O
our	O
people	O
#Ebola	O
#auspol	O

.	O
@	B-PER
TonyAbbottMHR	B-PER
commenting	O
on	O
the	O
Government	O
response	O
to	O
#Ebola	O
Live	O
now	O
CH	B-ORG
601	I-ORG
#auspol	O
http://t.co/eAQLbh34Cr	O

Joint	O
QLD	B-ORG
police	I-ORG
and	O
CCC	B-ORG
drug	O
trafficking	O
raids	O
underway	O
in	O
Brisbane	B-LOC
's	O
south	O
(	O
@	B-PER
brookewylie	B-PER
)	O

Blue	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
mayor	O
:	O
recovery	O
is	O
n't	O
over	O
today	O
-	O
it	O
's	O
just	O
a	O
milestone	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
One	O
year	O
anniversary	O
of	O
October	O
2013	O
bushfires	O
(	O
@	B-PER
DicksonLauren	B-PER
)	O

Girl	O
sustains	O
injuries	O
after	O
reportedly	O
being	O
bitten	O
by	O
shark	O
at	O
Avoca	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
this	O
morning	O
http://t.co/JkMLhMHYLC	O
http://t.co/TFg57qQ2DB	O

One	O
year	O
on	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
Blue	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
bushfire	O
anniversary	O
LIVE	O
on	O
http://t.co/b3dJJfXmaN	O
(	O
@	B-PER
DicksonLauren	B-PER
)	O

LIVE	O
from	O
Reservoir	B-LOC
after	O
a	O
body	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
abandoned	O
nursing	O
home	O
.	O
2	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
custody	O
http://t.co/aYERlLoFu3	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

AFP	B-ORG
lay	O
further	O
terror	O
related	O
charges	O
against	O
Agim	B-PER
Kruezi	I-PER
who	O
will	O
face	O
court	O
today	O
http://t.co/tISxR1g8r8	O
(	O
@	B-PER
brookewylie	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
US	B-LOC
President	O
Barack	B-PER
Obama	I-PER
has	O
authorised	O
call-up	O
of	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
if	O
needed	O
in	O
Ebola-stricken	O
Africa	B-LOC
.	O

#BREAKING:	O
Police	O
believe	O
a	O
man	O
killed	O
after	O
falling	O
through	O
a	O
roof	O
in	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
had	O
broken	O
into	O
the	O
property	O
.	O

Morning	O
:	O
NZ	B-LOC
wins	O
seat	O
on	O
UN	B-ORG
Security	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
,	O
Madrid	B-LOC
Ebola	O
scare	O
,	O
Kobani	B-LOC
air	O
strikes	O
,	O
Jackie	B-PER
Kelly	I-PER
quits	O
Libs	B-ORG
,	O
cricket	O
(	O
@	B-PER
NinaBStevens	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
Spanish	B-LOC
authorities	O
have	O
isolated	O
an	O
Air	B-ORG
France	I-ORG
plane	O
in	O
Madrid	B-LOC
for	O
a	O
possible	O
Ebola	O
case	O
with	O
183	O
passengers	O
onboard	O
.	O

Oh	O
dear	O
-	O
#SportsNight	O
-	O
right	O
now	O
@	B-PER
R1CHARDFREEDMAN	B-PER
@	B-PER
TadhgKennelly	B-PER
@	B-PER
adammacdougall5	B-PER
http://t.co/7FW7HYwYuK	O
(	O
@	B-PER
braceyjames	B-PER
)	O

A	O
great	O
#pmlive	O
is	O
on	O
Sky	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
NOW	O
!	O
Comment	O
:	O
http://t.co/WVeZVIVBLM	O
http://t.co/BkDR3xOuNM	O
(	O
@PMOnAir	O
)	O

Live	O
at	O
6pm	O
from	O
HMAS	B-LOC
Cerberus	I-LOC
after	O
police	O
Declared	O
a	O
hazardous	O
material	O
"	O
non	O
suspicious	O
"	O
&	O
30yo	O
navy	O
seaman	O
will	O
be	O
released	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

.	O
@DeptDefence	O
has	O
released	O
this	O
statement	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
unfolding	O
situation	O
at	O
HMAS	B-LOC
Cerberus	I-LOC
http://t.co/CyetDpWCS0	O

Vic	B-LOC
Police	O
say	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
HMAS	B-LOC
Cerberus	I-LOC
.	O
400m	O
exclusion	O
zone	O
in	O
place	O
.	O
Bomb	O
squad	O
en	O
route	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	O
A	O
400	O
metre	O
exclusion	O
zone	O
has	O
been	O
set	O
up	O
around	O
the	O
unit	O
on	O
the	O
HMAS	B-LOC
Cerberus	I-LOC
,	O
on	O
the	O
Mornington	B-LOC
Peninsula	I-LOC

#BREAKING:	O
One	O
man	O
has	O
been	O
arrested	O
and	O
an	O
exclusion	O
zone	O
is	O
in	O
place	O
while	O
bomb	O
squad	O
attends	O
naval	O
base	O
HMAS	B-LOC
Cerberus	I-LOC
in	O
Victoria	B-LOC
.	O

Breaking	O
:	O
A	O
person	O
is	O
in	O
custody	O
as	O
the	O
bomb	O
squad	O
attends	O
to	O
a	O
Vic	B-LOC
naval	O
training	O
base	O
where	O
an	O
exclusion	O
zone	O
is	O
in	O
place	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

#BREAKING:	B-ORG
Gold	I-ORG
Coast	I-ORG
Titans	I-ORG
among	O
5	O
NRL	B-ORG
clubs	O
fined	O
by	O
the	O
NRL	B-ORG
for	O
salary	O
cap	O
breaches	O

#BREAKING	B-ORG
The	O
NRL	B-ORG
says	O
a	O
portion	O
of	O
the	O
fine	O
&	O
loss	O
of	O
competition	O
points	O
is	O
suspended	O
as	O
club	O
self-reported	O

#BREAKING:	O
The	O
Gold	B-ORG
Coast	I-ORG
Titans	I-ORG
have	O
been	O
fined	O
$	O
300	O
,	O
000	O
and	O
docked	O
four	O
2015	O
competition	O
points	O
for	O
breaches	O
of	O
the	O
NRL	B-ORG
salary	O
cap	O
.	O

Vic	B-LOC
Labor	O
Deputy	O
Leader	O
James	B-PER
Merlino	I-PER
on	O
SKY	B-ORG
re	O
claims	O
of	O
a	O
porno	O
ring	O
operating	O
in	O
Vic	B-LOC
Premier	O
office	O
http://t.co/0ohNlSpwFB	O
(	O
@	B-PER
SimoLove	B-PER
)	O

Merlino	B-PER
:	O
"	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
pornographic	O
ring	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Premier	O
's	O
private	O
office	O
"	O
#springst	B-LOC
(	O
@	B-PER
AhronYoung	B-PER
)	O

Vic	B-LOC
Labor	B-ORG
's	O
James	B-PER
Merlino	I-PER
LIVE	O
on	O
Sky	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
right	O
now	O
#springst	O
(	O
@	B-PER
AhronYoung	B-PER
)	O

LIVE	O
NOW	O
on	O
@	B-ORG
SkyBusiness	B-ORG
602	O
:	O
Federal	B-PER
Industry	I-PER
Minister	I-PER
Ian	I-PER
MacFarlane	I-PER
announcing	O
funding	O
initiative	O
for	O
automotive	O
workers	O
.	O
(	O
@	B-PER
Staceylee_	B-PER
)	O

.	O
@	B-PER
PeterDutton_MP	B-PER
:	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Labor	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
has	O
been	O
quite	O
irresponsible	O
in	O
their	O
responses	O
today	O
#Ebola	O
#auspol	B-LOC

.	O
@	B-PER
PeterDutton_MP	B-PER
:	O
We	O
have	O
around	O
30	O
Australian	B-LOC
NGO	B-ORG
volunteers	O
in	O
West	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
at	O
present	O
#Ebola	O
#auspol	O

.	O
@	B-PER
PeterDutton_MP	B-PER
:	O
The	O
Labor	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
seems	O
to	O
be	O
divided	O
on	O
this	O
issue	O
#Ebola	O
#auspol	O

.	O
@	B-PER
PeterDutton_MP	B-PER
:	O
Ms	B-PER
Plibersek	I-PER
needs	O
to	O
explain	O
what	O
her	O
evacuation	O
plan	O
would	O
be	O
#Ebola	O
#auspol	O

.	O
@	B-PER
PeterDutton_MP	B-PER
:	O
We	O
have	O
provided	O
$	O
18	O
M	O
worth	O
of	O
support	O
for	O
efforts	O
in	O
West	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
#Ebola	O
#auspol	O

The	O
Wagner	B-ORG
family	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
airport	O
and	O
the	O
Toowoomba	B-LOC
neighbours	O
'	O
feud	O
.	O
http://t.co/SvEF1W6WdR	O
http://t.co/PiKibfllUQ	O

Bob	B-PER
Geldof	I-PER
"	O
blames	O
himself	O
"	O
for	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
his	O
daughter	O
Peaches	B-PER
from	O
a	O
heroin	O
overdose	O
.	O
http://t.co/kOSZn8o7Su	O
http://t.co/52Zjb8HVN9	O

How	O
Coles	B-PER
squeezed	O
suppliers	O
for	O
'	O
perfect	O
profit	O
day	O
'	O
.	O
http://t.co/9XoFEyn53k	O

Opinion	O
:	O
Last	O
night	O
was	O
a	O
taste	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
meltdown	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
http://t.co/OpPTetMtGX	O

Chinese	O
investors	O
snap	O
up	O
50	O
dairy	O
farms	O
.	O
http://t.co/8P2TWJIi4r	O

Robot	B-ORG
trucks	I-ORG
and	O
driverless	O
trains	O
?	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Rio	B-ORG
Tinto	I-ORG
's	O
"	O
Mine	O
of	O
the	O
Future	O
.	O
"	O
http://t.co/i60s3lREWv	O
#PoweringAustralia	B-LOC

ACCC	B-ORG
steps	O
up	O
action	O
against	O
Coles	B-PER
.	O
http://t.co/KnNGibMboC	O

Victorian	B-LOC
Premier	O
Denis	B-PER
Napthine	I-PER
:	O
MP	O
porn	O
claims	O
bizarre	O
and	O
absurd	O
.	O
http://t.co/0MOd2M5Peg	O
#vicpol	O
http://t.co/FmYNzxvjsA	O

Iraqis	O
beg	O
for	O
more	O
air	O
strikes	O
as	O
jihadis	O
advance	O
on	O
key	O
city	O
.	O
http://t.co/2AJvRA6iLq	O

Terrorists	O
close	O
on	O
Baghdad	B-LOC
as	O
Barack	B-PER
Obama	I-PER
rallies	O
allies	O
.	O
http://t.co/ysb2Uyvfa2	O

US	B-LOC
in	O
race	O
to	O
find	O
131	O
passengers	O
on	O
flight	O
with	O
Ebola	O
infected	O
nurse	O
.	O
http://t.co/zNxoDyUudD	O

Brisbane	B-LOC
dad	O
Mick	B-PER
Hannemann	I-PER
never	O
imagined	O
his	O
family	O
relying	O
on	O
food	O
aid	O
to	O
make	O
ends	O
meet	O
.	O
http://t.co/Kjrkh2aQGM	O
http://t.co/TbMlZkwJdU	O

Will	O
Apple	B-ORG
do	O
to	O
cars	O
what	O
it	O
has	O
done	O
to	O
music	O
players	O
,	O
phones	O
and	O
computers	O
?	O
http://t.co/9ndg3wEjxm	O
http://t.co/yBGD0WvQf7	O

Australian	B-ORG
Bureau	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Statistics	I-ORG
warns	O
of	O
cuts	O
to	O
services	O
.	O
http://t.co/XxW5uNUy6S	O

Opinion	O
:	O
Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
's	O
own	O
side	O
may	O
put	O
paid	O
to	O
parental	O
leave	O
.	O
http://t.co/j5sFtv3uKY	O
#auspol	O
http://t.co/8wYDPoilD6	O

Australian	O
racing	O
industry	O
reeling	O
from	O
the	O
second	O
death	O
of	O
a	O
jockey	O
in	O
as	O
many	O
days	O
.	O
http://t.co/dImX3R6H18	O
http://t.co/HXuBe2pfcs	O

Former	O
police	O
officer	O
Troy	B-PER
Grant	I-PER
elected	O
NSW	B-LOC
Deputy	O
Premier	O
.	O
http://t.co/6eFxTJgGy6	O
#nswpol	O
http://t.co/uJIW7lsn8u	O

.	O
@	B-ORG
Canva	B-ORG
's	O
free	O
drag-and-drop	O
design	O
tool	O
to	O
launch	O
on	O
the	O
iPad	O
.	O
http://t.co/Hkwu48DYWw	O
http://t.co/SCs8QoiBLq	O

Apple	B-ORG
leaks	O
iPad	O
Air	O
2	O
,	O
iPad	O
Mini	O
3	O
on	O
iTunes	O
http://t.co/KIjwRm5Sl1	O

An	O
American	B-LOC
dream	O
beckons	O
as	O
league	O
's	O
best	O
player	O
Jarryd	B-PER
Hayne	I-PER
says	O
farewell	O
.	O
http://t.co/c9dZee6xH0	O
#NRL	O
http://t.co/XL1J4TqAPm	O

Australia	B-LOC
's	O
first	O
public	O
sex-offender	O
register	O
to	O
be	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
memory	O
of	O
Queensland	B-LOC
teen	O
Daniel	B-PER
Morcombe	I-PER
.	O
http://t.co/QMFf9mmxvH	O

Richard	B-PER
Flanagan	I-PER
's	O
#BookerPrize	B-ORG
win	O
places	O
him	O
among	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
celebrated	O
authors	O
.	O
http://t.co/rNCvQxOPle	O
http://t.co/6ObfeAuDgA	O

US	B-LOC
in	O
race	O
to	O
find	O
passengers	O
on	O
flight	O
with	O
Ebola	O
infected	O
nurse	O
.	O
http://t.co/eZXkQ6Ikei	O

Think	O
we	O
’	O
re	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
a	O
retail	O
revolution	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
it	O
’	O
s	O
just	O
getting	O
started	O
:	O
http://t.co/EUAsdcGxZG	O

Closing	O
the	O
gap	O
on	O
breast	O
cancer	O
http://t.co/8AfE1GUigj	O

Men	O
lose	O
brains	O
over	O
mannequins	O
in	O
lingerie	O
:	O
preacher	O
http://t.co/3s1ldD8mfP	O

Food	O
groups	O
nourish	O
the	O
spirit	O
and	O
the	O
family	O
http://t.co/X26O3qZsAA	O
#auspol	O

Men	O
lose	O
brains	O
over	O
mannequins	O
in	O
lingerie	O
:	O
preacher	O
http://t.co/7G13gA1ABC	O

Australian	B-ORG
Bureau	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Statistics	I-ORG
warns	O
of	O
cuts	O
to	O
services	O
http://t.co/j2cwPMKop7	O
#auspol	O

Editorial	O
:	O
What	O
's	O
wrong	O
with	O
journalism	O
schools	O
-	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
teach	O
there	O
.	O
http://t.co/GJSkLpvhqK	O

The	O
future	O
of	O
remote	O
Australia	B-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/Ol3NFJb12n	O
http://t.co/kEbfhTYZM8	O

Army	O
sergeant	O
tells	O
inquest	O
of	O
the	O
moment	O
his	O
mates	O
were	O
murdered	O
http://t.co/03fHAjKYhp	O

Booker	O
Prize	O
winner	O
Richard	B-PER
Flanagan	I-PER
predicts	O
literary	O
'	O
golden	O
age	O
'	O
.	O
http://t.co/aoVF57jj9b	O

Former	O
cop	O
,	O
first-term	O
politician	O
Troy	B-PER
Grant	I-PER
set	O
to	O
be	O
NSW	B-LOC
deputy	O
premier	O
http://t.co/tYgRJkFzN8	O

Winds	O
and	O
surf	O
continue	O
to	O
wreak	O
havoc	O
as	O
storms	O
batter	O
NSW	B-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/aqosALfdX5	O

Foreign	O
demand	O
for	O
new	O
homes	O
surges	O
in	O
September	O
http://t.co/jj5pPxa90Z	O

Joe	B-PER
Hockey	I-PER
backs	O
'	O
shirt-front	O
'	O
threat	O
as	O
Russian	B-LOC
media	O
calls	O
Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
'	O
disturbed	O
'	O
.	O
http://t.co/zSt3flqnw5	O
#auspol	O
http://t.co/zRtOrRupfx	O

Biotech	O
giant	O
CSL	B-ORG
in	O
talks	O
with	O
WHO	B-ORG
over	O
Ebola	O
treatments	O
http://t.co/7Uk5G33i2C	O

Retail	O
supremacy	O
will	O
be	O
decided	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shopping	O
aisles	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
server	O
room	O
:	O
http://t.co/EUAsdcGxZG	O

NSW	B-LOC
deputy	O
premier	O
Andrew	B-PER
Stoner	I-PER
quits	O
as	O
shake-up	O
continues	O
http://t.co/Jl5J7koXu4	O

Clive	B-PER
Palmer	I-PER
drops	O
his	O
$	O
1	O
million	O
defamation	O
claim	O
against	O
The	B-ORG
Australian	I-ORG
newspaper	O
.	O
http://t.co/T2c9BinebA	O
http://t.co/DswsDj4t20	O

Frank	B-PER
Lowy	I-PER
and	O
sons	O
sink	O
more	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
cash	O
into	O
Westfield	B-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
.	O
http://t.co/9Y4m5QOHs2	O
http://t.co/uRQEbZEA5X	O

Palau	B-LOC
becomes	O
the	O
latest	O
country	O
to	O
decriminalise	O
homosexuality	O
.	O
http://t.co/m5ALR9m2mq	O

Converse	B-ORG
sues	O
Wal-	B-ORG
Mart	I-ORG
,	O
Skechers	B-ORG
and	O
others	O
for	O
alleged	O
Chuck	B-ORG
Taylor	I-ORG
rip-offs	O
.	O
http://t.co/yxGL61Cdm7	O

Foreign	O
buyers	O
are	O
snapping	O
up	O
one	O
in	O
every	O
six	O
new	O
homes	O
in	O
Australia	B-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/gxjqJJ7YMP	O
http://t.co/1eOcuJGrkM	O

The	O
resources	O
sector	O
must	O
invest	O
in	O
new	O
technologies	O
to	O
remain	O
competitive	O
:	O
http://t.co/NHXAqNJ8CW	O
#PoweringAustralia	B-LOC
http://t.co/ZJvuQtXSLE	O

Clive	B-PER
Palmer	I-PER
has	O
dropped	O
his	O
$	O
1	O
million	O
defamation	O
claim	O
against	O
The	B-ORG
Australian	I-ORG
newspaper	O
.	O
http://t.co/cdEocumfNP	O
http://t.co/DswsDj4t20	O

When	O
life	O
gets	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
a	O
second	O
chance	O
.	O
http://t.co/0nXBiP5MFA	O
http://t.co/cLKEZcxAyd	O

Paedophile	O
extradited	O
to	O
UK	B-LOC
over	O
links	O
to	O
Maddie	B-PER
McCann	I-PER
abduction	O
.	O
http://t.co/roX8xnKTIf	O

Cleaners	O
'	O
mops	O
caused	O
Qantas	B-ORG
A	O
380	O
cabin	O
to	O
flood	O
,	O
inquiry	O
finds	O
.	O
http://t.co/HmptaoxrGa	O

"	O
It	O
's	O
the	O
hardest	O
decision	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
had	O
to	O
make	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
"	O
-	O
Jarryd	B-PER
Hayne	I-PER
on	O
leaving	O
the	O
#NRL	B-ORG
for	O
the	O
#NFL.	B-ORG
http://t.co/Jtqxhb8HYx	O

Deputy	O
NSW	B-LOC
Premier	O
and	O
Nationals	B-ORG
leader	O
Andrew	B-PER
Stoner	I-PER
quits	O
politics	O
.	O
http://t.co/TseRbLFozb	O
http://t.co/uz7fuHXOzb	O

Eight	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
these	O
parents	O
turned	O
to	O
marijuana	O
to	O
keep	O
their	O
3	O
-	O
year-old	O
son	O
alive	O
.	O
http://t.co/RLOwnmgR90	O
http://t.co/XpIRcIJUfW	O

Opinion	O
:	O
Extremists	O
in	O
our	O
midst	O
will	O
wither	O
the	O
more	O
their	O
ideas	O
are	O
exposed	O
as	O
repulsive	O
.	O
http://t.co/9tyqHTZLfH	O
http://t.co/f6a3oLUlzc	O

How	O
to	O
look	O
fabulous	O
at	O
40	O
-	O
plus	O
:	O
the	O
new	O
rules	O
.	O
http://t.co/jjLePPPyOL	O
http://t.co/mhaY6OGz4i	O

Over	O
4000	O
young	O
people	O
now	O
forced	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
dole	O
.	O
http://t.co/v2eXLjwYMR	O
#auspol	O
http://t.co/weNpvNbocu	O

This	O
time	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
the	O
NSW	B-LOC
Blue	I-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
had	O
devastating	O
bushfires	O
.	O
Now	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
http://t.co/h3UcaHF5U8	O
http://t.co/SeWn2stF2Y	O

Foreign	O
doctors	O
treated	O
Kim	B-PER
Jong-un	I-PER
,	O
South	B-LOC
Korean	I-LOC
envoy	O
says	O
.	O
http://t.co/4KRXZXDDjB	O

Facebook	B-ORG
and	O
Apple	B-ORG
offer	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
female	O
staff	O
to	O
freeze	O
their	O
eggs	O
.	O
http://t.co/TtDp3wjVo1	O

Jarryd	B-PER
Hayne	I-PER
quits	O
rugby	O
league	O
to	O
play	O
NFL	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/kQe318lu9B	O
(	O
Pic	O
:	O
Getty	B-ORG
)	O
http://t.co/YJz0d0apDf	O

Northern	B-LOC
Territory	I-LOC
angry	O
over	O
order	O
to	O
kill	O
every	O
banana	O
tree	O
.	O
http://t.co/EmEGurk3IM	O
http://t.co/pW5TheICHx	O

Hizb	B-ORG
ut-	I-ORG
Tahrir	I-ORG
's	O
local	O
head	O
calls	O
for	O
the	O
overhaul	O
of	O
Aus­tralian	B-LOC
society	O
into	O
an	O
Islamic	O
totalitarian	O
state	O
.	O
http://t.co/TPGLxrMrgR	O
#auspol	O

Oscar	B-PER
Pistorius	I-PER
gave	O
Reeva	B-PER
Steenkamp	I-PER
's	O
parents	O
monthly	O
payments	O
.	O
http://t.co/ujGqgQXfer	O

One	O
of	O
Australia	B-LOC
's	O
best-loved	O
cartoon	O
characters	O
,	O
Blinky	B-PER
Bill	I-PER
,	O
is	O
set	O
for	O
the	O
big	O
screen	O
.	O
http://t.co/BIcnTdN6Bc	O
http://t.co/T4AtbhMDkE	O

Retired	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Sydney	I-ORG
media	O
lecturer	O
tells	O
all	O
about	O
bias	O
.	O
http://t.co/OwHGiiHY3E	O
http://t.co/AWTQa0TH47	O

Islamist	O
push	O
with	O
West	B-LOC
's	O
values	O
.	O
http://t.co/Z7PQRFgEep	O

Australian	B-LOC
jihadi	O
's	O
link	O
to	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
's	O
al-	B-LOC
Furqan	I-LOC
centre	I-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/4O60Utc3HH	O
http://t.co/1G0Ilt7Twl	O

Hundreds	O
seek	O
help	O
as	O
torrential	O
rain	O
and	O
high	O
winds	O
batter	O
NSW	B-LOC
.	O
http://t.co/wFB4abpGRc	O
http://t.co/CaYdWEj9WU	O

Gammy	B-PER
case	O
:	O
new	O
'	O
victim	O
'	O
emerges	O
from	O
child	O
sex	O
offender	O
's	O
past	O
.	O
http://t.co/VdBvwYTy9K	O
http://t.co/FOcUybVUUU	O

457	O
immigration	O
visas	O
revamped	O
for	O
‘	O
flexibility	O
’	O
http://t.co/FNn30VrMNN	O
#auspol	O

Richard	B-PER
Flanagan	I-PER
wins	O
Booker	O
prize	O
for	O
Narrow	O
Road	O
to	O
Deep	B-LOC
North	I-LOC
http://t.co/8tDUga59qn	O

Married	O
‘	O
Borat-style	O
’	O
:	O
dragged	O
over	O
threshold	O
http://t.co/qjvfJG9yyc	O

Dewani	B-PER
’	O
s	O
attacker	O
shot	O
her	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
husband	O
claims	O
http://t.co/vp6j5k0THq	O

Texas	B-LOC
nurse	O
given	O
blood	O
from	O
Ebola	O
survivor	O
http://t.co/gUTngkuxLC	O

Pilot	O
dies	O
as	O
plane	O
crashes	O
into	O
home	O
http://t.co/bJPom0ntkd	O

Tributes	O
flow	O
for	O
late	O
Lady	B-PER
Mary	I-PER
Downer	I-PER
http://t.co/0n6UxLZRun	O
#auspol	O

Malcolm	B-PER
Fraser	I-PER
demands	O
inquiry	O
into	O
land	O
rights	O
handling	O
http://t.co/tcGW4OLkuf	O
#auspol	O

Paperwork	O
burden	O
means	O
childcare	O
centres	O
have	O
less	O
time	O
for	O
kids	O
http://t.co/q9YpmZmnPJ	O
#auspol	O

Pravda	B-ORG
to	O
Putin	B-PER
:	O
'	O
wash	O
your	O
hands	O
after	O
shaking	O
Abbott	B-PER
's	O
grubby	O
paw	O
'	O
.	O
http://t.co/PgPbEoG2Ir	O
#auspol	O

Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
tones	O
down	O
language	O
on	O
Russia	B-LOC
but	O
keeps	O
it	O
‘	O
robust	O
’	O
http://t.co/rMYa476gRx	O

Older	O
mothers	O
pass	O
on	O
gene	O
mutations	O
to	O
babies	O
,	O
study	O
finds	O
.	O
http://t.co/LButZQZV4N	O

Winners	O
and	O
losers	O
in	O
farming	O
's	O
season	O
of	O
extremes	O
.	O
http://t.co/rs9CfyM8Z1	O
http://t.co/IiLXRgENtl	O

Pilots	O
swore	O
and	O
screamed	O
as	O
Air	B-ORG
France	I-ORG
plane	O
plunged	O
into	O
sea	O
,	O
transcript	O
reveals	O
.	O
http://t.co/bczJTM8Xxm	O

Canada	B-LOC
to	O
send	O
Ebola	O
vaccine	O
to	O
WHO	B-ORG
http://t.co/RTbGPh0t48	O

Bishops	B-ORG
scrap	O
welcome	O
to	O
gays	O
http://t.co/9usKcNRNgR	O

UK	B-LOC
call	O
for	O
unity	O
against	O
jihadists	O
http://t.co/I3BLksss5q	O

Juliette	B-PER
Lewis	I-PER
alleges	O
her	O
August	O
:	O
Osage	B-LOC
County	I-LOC
co-star	O
met	O
with	O
foul	O
play	O
:	O
http://t.co/XIqz3qvGBp	O

#Wallabies	B-ORG
coach	O
Ewen	B-PER
McKenzie	I-PER
quits	O
after	O
loss	O
to	O
All	B-ORG
Blacks	I-ORG
:	O
http://t.co/aR480QX1zs	O

Sydney	B-LOC
man	O
falls	O
from	O
tree	O
,	O
dies	O
http://t.co/ZP8v3RDSK8	O

Flood	O
warnings	O
for	O
WA	B-LOC
http://t.co/emOiNn2QUd	O

With	O
Christmas	O
just	O
over	O
2	O
months	O
away	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
our	O
tips	O
on	O
how	O
to	O
avoid	O
debt	O
during	O
the	O
silly	O
season	O
:	O
http://t.co/m5pe15nuvX	O

Sydney	B-LOC
restaurant	O
fire	O
cause	O
unknown	O
http://t.co/YcVL5v2NtQ	O

She	O
looked	O
amazing	O
-	O
but	O
did	O
Rachael	B-PER
Finch	I-PER
break	O
Spring	B-ORG
Racing	I-ORG
's	O
fashion	O
rules	O
today	O
?	O
http://t.co/dg88Te6jHF	O
http://t.co/8QaDUr3noK	O

Vic	B-ORG
Greens	I-ORG
bid	O
to	O
win	O
balance	O
of	O
power	O
http://t.co/jKKYCKGnxl	O

Man	O
's	O
body	O
found	O
in	O
Sydney	B-LOC
park	O
http://t.co/waWCaqamTU	O

NT	B-LOC
police	O
officer	O
faces	O
deception	O
charges	O
http://t.co/zljBc6LZsI	O

AC	B-ORG
/	I-ORG
DC	I-ORG
fuel	O
Phil	B-PER
Rudd	I-PER
rumours	O
http://t.co/Y8dYs7xjCe	O

Do	O
n't	O
wait	O
until	O
Ebola	O
hits	O
Australia	B-LOC
:	O
ALP	B-ORG
http://t.co/ALUrZZBytR	O

Images	O
released	O
over	O
fatal	O
Vic	B-LOC
assault	O
http://t.co/ukf0FrRH19	O

Two	O
arrested	O
over	O
40	O
-	O
year	O
Qld	B-LOC
cold	O
case	O
http://t.co/KSMO2J80LI	O

Bear	O
eats	O
man	O
's	O
body	O
in	O
remote	O
California	B-LOC
http://t.co/WKkkSZW5cm	O

'	O
Another	O
violent	O
and	O
senseless	O
assault	O
'	O
-	O
a	O
man	O
loses	O
his	O
life	O
after	O
an	O
unprovoked	O
attack	O
on	O
a	O
night	O
out	O
.	O
http://t.co/safIpsdGjb	O

Church	O
not	O
changing	O
views	O
:	O
Pell	O
http://t.co/XozYAqXziA	O

1	O
.	O
2	O
billion	O
live	O
on	O
less	O
than	O
$	O
1	O
.	O
35	O
a	O
day	O
http://t.co/13lpx6rRNR	O

SA	B-LOC
urged	O
to	O
follow	O
bushfire	O
plans	O
http://t.co/1ipqnOnHRu	O

Brisbane	B-LOC
pedestrian	O
killed	O
http://t.co/tIOqY8b3XT	O

As	O
debt	O
mounts	O
,	O
Caesars	B-ORG
in	O
talks	O
http://t.co/sQsqAq8roF	O

Glen	B-PER
Campbell	I-PER
retires	O
with	O
swansong	O
hit	O
http://t.co/P2xMGGF7iU	O

Ebola	O
's	O
deadly	O
past	O
:	O
What	O
have	O
we	O
really	O
learned	O
?	O
|	O
http://t.co/OSNbznavvP	O
http://t.co/I1RG5f4U9m	O

Manhattan	B-ORG
Transfer	I-ORG
singer	O
,	O
founder	O
dies	O
http://t.co/pQPlqdQ5Rs	O

Iggy	B-PER
Azalea	I-PER
slams	O
record	O
label	O
over	O
image	O
http://t.co/H11WCeAI2y	O

Body	O
of	O
missing	O
US	B-LOC
actress	O
found	O
http://t.co/oiJmUT7JZY	O

Who	O
in	O
God	O
are	O
all	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
via	O
@	B-PER
MattYoung	B-PER
|	O
http://t.co/tonEy9Q5gG	O
http://t.co/cJ9RaEczbt	O

Woman	O
rock	O
fisher	O
dies	O
on	O
NSW	B-LOC
south	I-LOC
coast	I-LOC
http://t.co/njBmpxthg1	O

Boxing	O
champ	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
my	O
beautiful	O
wife	O
again	O
|	O
http://t.co/meQT8mjs4F	O
http://t.co/mZCx80BRnM	O

Putin	B-PER
'	O
constructive	O
'	O
on	O
MH	O
17	O
access	O
:	O
Bishop	B-PER
http://t.co/Qxz48YAi2d	O

Melbourne	B-LOC
church	O
damaged	O
in	O
blaze	O
http://t.co/CWdUtMGQIP	O

'	O
You	O
're	O
never	O
free	O
'	O
-	O
my	O
brutal	O
life	O
as	O
an	O
ISIS	B-ORG
hostage	O
|	O
http://t.co/DiWBO8V5rY	O
http://t.co/1LCFrbUCW6	O

Mum	O
'	O
tried	O
to	O
sew	O
daughter	O
's	O
lips	O
shut	O
|	O
http://t.co/V7hnPa9n0x	O
http://t.co/vAHCx7vFri	O

Ouch	O
:	O
Credit	O
crunch	O
hits	O
Obama	B-PER
|	O
http://t.co/7DzlBgh1W8	O

Dane	B-PER
Cook	I-PER
:	O
I	O
slept	O
with	O
hundreds	O
of	O
groupies	O
|	O
http://t.co/DmlN0n5Gia	O
http://t.co/jA9QdhJndB	O

Models	O
quarantined	O
after	O
Ebloa	O
Flight	O
#brekkiewrap	O
|	O
http://t.co/E16wj54HM4	O
http://t.co/SFyOzCbm0i	O

WHO	B-ORG
admits	O
botching	O
Ebola	O
response	O
http://t.co/mn5Zoy9u7c	O

Philippine	B-LOC
rebels	O
free	O
kidnapped	O
Germans	O
http://t.co/GsOG5yadkE	O

Arrest	O
over	O
death	O
of	O
Australian	O
in	O
Uganda	B-LOC
http://t.co/s0WFGacp7K	O

WHO	B-ORG
says	O
Ebola	O
outbreak	O
ended	O
in	O
Senegal	B-LOC
http://t.co/u9PdOWh1si	O

Morgan	B-ORG
Stanley	I-ORG
's	O
income	O
nearly	O
doubles	O
http://t.co/i3ihRuJisR	O

Terror	O
charges	O
against	O
four	O
men	O
in	O
UK	B-LOC
http://t.co/0gjbg0wqBZ	O

GE	B-ORG
3	O
Q	O
profit	O
rises	O
on	O
oil	O
strength	O
http://t.co/V4lUTtWd6P	O

WA	B-LOC
parents	O
not	O
to	O
blame	O
for	O
girl	O
's	O
death	O
http://t.co/MriEaSPUX1	O

WA	B-LOC
toilet	O
filmer	O
sent	O
to	O
jail	O
http://t.co/xLhH0uzVLn	O

Flotation	O
goes	O
ahead	O
for	O
Jimmy	B-ORG
Choo	I-ORG
http://t.co/MLxigxe2DY	O

Aust	B-LOC
soldiers	O
'	O
were	O
n't	O
properly	O
guarded	O
'	O
http://t.co/t15xwite8j	O

Tas	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
exec	O
quits	O
,	O
ending	O
inquiry	O
http://t.co/5kbRotVigw	O

Follow	O
our	O
coverage	O
of	O
Day	O
5	O
of	O
Oscar	B-PER
Pistorious	I-PER
'	O
sentencing	O
tonight	O
in	O
South	B-LOC
Africa	I-LOC
tonight	O
|	O
http://t.co/5rm48JmdS1	O

Cambodia	B-LOC
Khmer	B-ORG
Rouge	I-ORG
genocide	O
trial	O
opens	O
http://t.co/jM7SuJup7w	O

CFS	B-ORG
warns	O
SA	B-LOC
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
bushfires	O
http://t.co/BCndBzWIZl	O

ANZ	B-ORG
boss	O
confident	O
in	O
China	B-LOC
's	O
growth	O
http://t.co/3TP0Dv30HP	O

Economists	O
looked	O
at	O
$	O
A	B-ORG
,	O
CPI	O
,	O
confidence	O
http://t.co/kSDY546KJ6	O

Hurricane	O
Gonzalo	B-LOC
bearing	O
down	O
on	O
Bermuda	B-LOC
http://t.co/acvJOQQ75f	O

Joyriding	O
Sydney	B-LOC
teens	O
found	O
by	O
police	O
http://t.co/4th14P1jnK	O

Teacher	O
quits	O
her	O
job	O
to	O
twerk	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
http://t.co/McViGyOCOj	O
http://t.co/SGs58OqK5w	O

Inflation	O
stays	O
benign	O
in	O
Sept	O
quarter	O
http://t.co/R3Ihru9AhG	O

Deadline	O
looms	O
for	O
hostage	O
in	O
Philippines	B-LOC
http://t.co/GxsBdNFDeW	O

Man	O
to	O
be	O
extradited	O
over	O
sex	O
abuse	O
claims	O
http://t.co/U1IOcQrio5	O

Victoria	B-LOC
's	O
IBAC	B-ORG
still	O
awaiting	O
reforms	O
http://t.co/6YEDlMU6Jm	O

Liver	O
transplanted	O
second	O
time	O
in	O
HK	B-LOC
man	O
http://t.co/NI8D2bjxiL	O

Stop	O
the	O
shirtfronts	O
:	O
how	O
fake	O
talk	O
fails	O
http://t.co/wU3xJRo6No	O

Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
has	O
been	O
talking	O
tough	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
MPs	O
want	O
him	O
to	O
tone	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
@farrm51	O
reports	O
|	O
http://t.co/JpAwamffAV	O

Dangerous	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
journalist	O
:	O
Greste	B-PER
http://t.co/c53FFz3NQw	O

CCC	B-ORG
revelations	O
'	O
an	O
embarassment	O
'	O
:	O
Barnett	B-PER
http://t.co/VOZyuicXko	O

SHORTEN	B-PER
on	O
Ebola	O
:	O
How	O
is	O
it	O
other	O
nations	O
can	O
see	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
provide	O
greater	O
support	O
when	O
Australia	B-LOC
says	O
its	O
all	O
too	O
hard	O
?	O
#auspol	O

Bill	B-PER
Shorten	I-PER
:	O
"	O
Australia	B-LOC
can	O
not	O
sleepwalk	O
its	O
way	O
through	O
this	O
Ebola	O
crisis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
anyone	O
thinks	O
the	O
govt	O
has	O
done	O
enough	O
"	O
.	O
#auspol	O

Abbott	B-PER
tells	O
Libs	B-ORG
to	O
'	O
stay	O
in	O
and	O
fight	O
'	O
http://t.co/z7NJhKK431	O

Chocolate	O
milk	O
craze	O
hits	O
Kiwi	O
shoppers	O
http://t.co/rXiWbN3HSK	O

'	O
He	O
's	O
like	O
a	O
cobra	O
'	O
:	O
Loyalty	O
scheme	O
under	O
investigation	O
by	O
consumer	O
watchdog	O
http://t.co/E11zyyIbnM	O
http://t.co/xivxtlwT6f	O

Pentecostal	O
movement	O
says	O
'	O
we	O
will	O
change	O
'	O
http://t.co/7uYrVaGpeK	O

US	B-LOC
company	O
takes	O
technology	O
to	O
new	O
depths	O
http://t.co/2SV8FlOtTl	O

Ridley	B-PER
Scott	I-PER
's	O
Ebola	O
drama	O
fast-tracked	O
http://t.co/atV2qd6nWY	O

Homes	O
should	O
meet	O
code	O
before	O
sale	O
:	O
expert	O
http://t.co/urpsBAOZ5I	O

Man	O
rescued	O
from	O
WA	B-LOC
cliff	O
The	B-ORG
Gap	I-ORG
http://t.co/bev6kmaKbs	O

Girl	O
's	O
fall	O
no	O
shock	O
to	O
Qld	B-LOC
safety	O
group	O
http://t.co/u9XVdDfCKU	O

Vic	B-LOC
man	O
arrested	O
over	O
historical	O
sex	O
abuse	O
http://t.co/8E9Rv19w5H	O

Lobbyist	O
'	O
never	O
lobbied	O
'	O
his	O
minister	O
dad	O
http://t.co/zutnUIRJ4N	O

New	O
test	O
for	O
shellfish	O
toxins	O
http://t.co/oz9MOHSUmt	O

Private	O
actions	O
are	O
company	O
business	O
http://t.co/4wN1H9ruhC	O

WA	B-LOC
,	O
Victorian	B-LOC
Powerball	B-ORG
players	O
split	O
$	O
50m	O
http://t.co/REsDbijAaj	O

Arrest	O
over	O
assault	O
on	O
Melbourne	B-LOC
bus	O
http://t.co/GuCWU9nUzx	O

Victorian	B-LOC
burglar	O
dies	O
during	O
break-in	O
http://t.co/y2vORcR8oV	O

Health	O
Minister	O
Peter	B-PER
Dutton	I-PER
:	O
"	O
Our	O
(	O
Ebola	O
)	O
response	O
is	O
to	O
go	O
above	O
what	O
is	O
recommended	O
by	O
international	O
health	O
authorities	O
.	O
"	O
#auspol	O

Health	O
Minister	O
Peter	B-PER
Dutton	I-PER
speaking	O
on	O
Ebola	O
:	O
"	O
The	O
different	O
states	O
will	O
act	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
way	O
in	O
terms	O
of	O
their	O
response	O
in	O
hospitals	O
"	O
.	O

Take	O
our	O
Aussie	B-LOC
TV	O
quiz	O
:	O
What	O
show	O
is	O
Sharon	B-PER
Strzelecki	I-PER
from	O
?	O
http://t.co/ZRsxHLZ1HJ	O

Vic	B-LOC
2014	O
/	O
15	O
surplus	O
forecast	O
slightly	O
down	O
http://t.co/aNrH1ozFl3	O

SkyCity	B-ORG
wins	O
bigger	O
share	O
of	O
high	O
rollers	O
http://t.co/mzkbbIn5xq	O

Challenge	O
men	O
not	O
victims	O
:	O
Rosie	B-PER
Batty	I-PER
http://t.co/UydXuJFRlF	O

Brothel	O
siege	O
accused	O
denied	O
bail	O
http://t.co/4khIRU6Oix	O

Belt	O
used	O
in	O
karaoke	O
bar	O
assault	O
http://t.co/GmQGE0iNbH	O

Police	O
officer	O
says	O
reports	O
not	O
her	O
role	O
http://t.co/gZIV6w8QE4	O

Community	O
reflects	O
on	O
a	O
fiery	O
milestone	O
http://t.co/5TGVfLSBpX	O

Official	O
language	O
watchdog	O
looking	O
into	O
John	B-PER
Baird	I-PER
's	O
tweets	O
http://t.co/62Q4NpUCm4	O

Justin	B-PER
Bieber	I-PER
sued	O
by	O
paparazzo	O
over	O
Hawaiian	O
beach	O
scuffle	O
http://t.co/TvwsrtW53i	O

Prime	O
Minister	O
Stephen	B-PER
Harper	I-PER
embarks	O
on	O
annual	O
tour	O
of	O
the	O
North	B-LOC
http://t.co/ssUzYVw6nk	O

Newfoundland	B-LOC
sisters	O
'	O
illness	O
diagnosed	O
in	O
U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
after	O
20	O
years	O
http://t.co/Xw4QrRG1of	O

Tooth	B-PER
fairy	I-PER
pays	O
premium	O
for	O
teeth	O
in	O
Atlantic	B-LOC
Canada	I-LOC
http://t.co/2sP8a12XFP	O

RCMP	B-ORG
confirm	O
double	O
homicide	O
in	O
Montague	B-LOC
area	O
http://t.co/NdyYcR2Yow	O

Justin	B-PER
Trudeau	I-PER
fulfilling	O
Liberal	B-ORG
hopes	O
ahead	O
of	O
2015	O
election	O
http://t.co/wSxKNFU63f	O

Have	B-PER
Alward	I-PER
's	O
Tories	O
been	O
'	O
proven	O
through	O
fire	O
?	O
'	O
N	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
B	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
voters	O
will	O
decide	O
Sept	O
.	O
22	O
http://t.co/bPuHuujpRy	O

Transport	B-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
's	O
lax	O
safety	O
practices	O
go	O
beyond	O
rail	O
http://t.co/E0RikVjDo3	O

RCMP	B-ORG
investigate	O
double	O
homicide	O
in	O
P	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
E	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
I	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
http://t.co/77dAw999CG	O

$	O
24	O
M	O
ad	O
campaign	O
for	O
Keystone	B-LOC
pipeline	O
had	O
little	O
impact	O
:	O
survey	O
http://t.co/H1TW9j1Enx	O

B	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
C	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
woman	O
with	O
dementia	O
leaves	O
final	O
right-to-die	O
plea	O
http://t.co/vYxl4nYHsZ	O

McCain	B-ORG
is	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
frozen	O
pizza	O
business	O
in	O
North	B-LOC
America	I-LOC
http://t.co/TVrzZEdvRu	O

Ontario	B-LOC
couple	O
builds	O
'	O
tiny	O
house	O
'	O
on	O
wheels	O
http://t.co/Pp8j7t67t8	O

Donations	O
help	O
woman	O
with	O
terminal	O
cancer	O
wed	O
in	O
Edmonton	B-LOC
http://t.co/iFRjr0gZ2j	O

Portrait	O
series	O
fights	O
stereotypes	O
about	O
aboriginal	O
people	O
http://t.co/pZrwqGrVS9	O

Durham	B-LOC
's	O
oldest	O
cold	O
case	O
:	O
Victim	O
's	O
family	O
reacts	O
to	O
acquittal	O
http://t.co/WM8tCfb8yI	O

Mounties	O
trace	O
Islamic	O
militants	O
to	O
Calgary	B-LOC
http://t.co/jjaX2cBuMg	O

Liberals	B-ORG
aiming	O
for	O
majority	O
government	O
in	O
2015	O
http://t.co/EqSkCYMXMD	O

Spy	O
agency	O
kept	O
private	O
communications	O
obtained	O
'	O
unintentionally	O
'	O
http://t.co/GFrtXbVEUR	O

Target	B-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
still	O
way	O
off	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
sales	O
numbers	O
show	O
http://t.co/PlaegxKcBe	O

Opposition	O
parties	O
call	O
for	O
government	O
action	O
on	O
child	O
deaths	O
http://t.co/q1kqx9Vhxh	O

Air	B-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
accused	O
of	O
discriminating	O
against	O
Muslim	O
man	O
http://t.co/STvyURKQnB	O

Driveway	O
sinkhole	O
nearly	O
swallows	O
BMW	O
http://t.co/BmcACsabkl	O

Ex-	O
Mountie	O
sentenced	O
to	O
4	O
years	O
for	O
cocaine-related	O
charge	O
http://t.co/zA26kCtTS4	O

Canucks	B-ORG
confirm	O
settlement	O
in	O
Moore	B-PER
,	O
Bertuzzi	B-PER
case	O
http://t.co/pL4rtHM5Mz	O

Canada	B-LOC
's	O
best	O
neighbourhood	O
in	O
Calgary	B-LOC
,	O
Winnipeg	B-LOC
,	O
Kitchener	B-LOC
?	O
http://t.co/q8jGCcDSNJ	O

Staples	B-ORG
to	O
close	O
140	O
stores	O
in	O
U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
and	O
Canada	B-LOC
this	O
year	O
http://t.co/r7IC4Iaq3z	O

Cohon	B-PER
wo	O
n't	O
seek	O
3rd	O
term	O
as	O
CFL	B-ORG
commissioner	O
http://t.co/3aUwYtzaGx	O

122	O
Albertans	B-LOC
diagnosed	O
with	O
E	O
.	O
coli	O
as	O
AHS	B-ORG
looks	O
for	O
cause	O
http://t.co/28frCURxQ1	O

TSX	B-ORG
hits	O
new	O
all-time	O
high	O
http://t.co/yJcSKiHmlK	O

Energy	B-ORG
East	I-ORG
Pipeline	O
route	O
crosses	O
961	O
waterways	O
:	O
report	O
http://t.co/ULhSeEqzJj	O

NDP	B-ORG
loses	O
MP	O
over	O
Mideast	B-LOC
conflict	O
position	O
http://t.co/jJaJSqpDYu	O

Quebec	B-LOC
farmed	O
mink	O
set	O
free	O
by	O
intruder	O
http://t.co/28z3fxwe5A	O

Tina	B-PER
Fontaine	I-PER
,	O
slain	O
teen	O
,	O
struggled	O
with	O
father	O
's	O
beating	O
death	O
http://t.co/bhTYf710wX	O

Denis	B-PER
Coderre	I-PER
optimistic	O
agreement	O
on	O
pensions	O
possible	O
http://t.co/x3D79Mr6JH	O

Rob	B-PER
Ford	I-PER
willing	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
drug	O
and	O
alcohol	O
tests	O
-	O
only	O
if	O
other	O
candidates	O
do	O
http://t.co/txETSUcsWo	O

In	O
Tuktoyaktuk	B-LOC
,	O
preparing	O
for	O
tourists	O
ahead	O
of	O
new	O
highway	O
http://t.co/ii0hM6KeLQ	O

Justin	B-PER
Trudeau	I-PER
gauges	O
Liberal	B-ORG
caucus	O
in	O
Edmonton	B-LOC
http://t.co/cvnugZDjjZ	O

Canadian	O
shot	O
putter	O
Armstrong	B-PER
finally	O
to	O
receive	O
Olympic	B-ORG
bronze	O
http://t.co/KXWULuEdCS	O

Ontario	B-LOC
man	O
quits	O
teaching	O
after	O
backlash	O
from	O
racy	O
novel	O
http://t.co/cwk2acco5k	O

James	B-PER
Moore	I-PER
pitches	O
changes	O
to	O
interprovincial	O
trade	O
http://t.co/bLMBW6T9Pi	O

U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
couple	O
,	O
12	O
children	O
and	O
dog	O
take	O
RV	O
tour	O
to	O
New	B-LOC
Brunswick	I-LOC
http://t.co/UcPdCxreTL	O

Missing	O
Ontario	B-LOC
sports	O
editor	O
's	O
car	O
found	O
,	O
search	O
continues	O
http://t.co/jX8acl33E7	O

Mulcair	B-PER
attacks	O
Conservatives	B-ORG
over	O
health	O
care	O
,	O
marijuana	O
stance	O
http://t.co/jUXVbuweJo	O

Kindergarten	O
early	O
or	O
late	O
,	O
on	O
parents	O
'	O
minds	O
http://t.co/JKveNa1Qi6	O

Camo-clad	O
man	O
with	O
pellet	O
guns	O
resembling	O
firearms	O
faces	O
charges	O
http://t.co/f16qqOIezA	O

Inuit	O
hunters	O
turn	O
to	O
chickens	O
for	O
sustainable	O
harvest	O
http://t.co/aDpmSEz0Nt	O

Peanut	O
and	O
almond	O
butters	O
recalled	O
over	O
salmonella	O
risk	O
http://t.co/lrIYqH7A0X	O

Never	O
mind	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
can	O
Justin	B-PER
Trudeau	I-PER
crack	O
Fortress	O
Quebec	B-LOC
?	O
http://t.co/bKCX1gs3CU	O

Justin	B-PER
Trudeau	I-PER
gets	O
RCMP	B-ORG
security	O
at	O
rally	O
following	O
break-in	O
http://t.co/yGgbdZYGLe	O

Pam	B-PER
Owen	I-PER
,	O
beaten	O
mental	O
health	O
worker	O
,	O
does	O
n't	O
blame	O
attacker	O
http://t.co/RFuKMyvX2w	O

Dave	B-PER
Hancock	I-PER
apologizes	O
to	O
Albertans	B-LOC
for	O
misuse	O
of	O
government	O
planes	O
http://t.co/SepiGQumxn	O

B	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
C	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
students	O
head	O
back	O
to	O
school	O
in	O
2	O
weeks	O
—	O
maybe	O
http://t.co/GpWVCpiaeY	O

Veterans	O
watchdog	O
finds	O
badly	O
wounded	O
soldiers	O
not	O
getting	O
disability	O
cheques	O
http://t.co/bQaPIJ8N0P	O

Toronto	B-ORG
Zoo	I-ORG
investigates	O
after	O
visitors	O
get	O
too	O
close	O
to	O
pandas	O
http://t.co/bGY0muwvVi	O

Calgary	B-LOC
radio	O
station	O
gives	O
up	O
plan	O
to	O
cut	O
pop	O
hits	O
in	O
half	O
http://t.co/SZgBc2X7bM	O

Tim	B-PER
Leiweke	I-PER
to	O
step	O
down	O
as	O
MLSE	B-ORG
president	O
/	O
CEO	O
:	O
report	O
http://t.co/RnuTSbQRq5	O

Blanc	B-PER
Sablon	I-PER
wants	O
to	O
leave	O
Quebec	B-LOC
,	O
join	O
N	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
L	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
http://t.co/HR9eRGfIgd	O

26	O
children	O
died	O
while	O
under	O
government	O
protection	O
in	O
N	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
L	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
since	O
2009	O
http://t.co/nlhZf2O36l	O

Trudeau	B-PER
defers	O
to	O
Mounties	B-ORG
'	O
expertise	O
on	O
security	O
http://t.co/uzqtARWuQ7	O

More	O
lenient	O
pot	O
laws	O
still	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
says	O
justice	O
minister	O
http://t.co/gDZG5NDsDd	O

Doctors	O
debate	O
end-of-life	O
care	O
at	O
Canadian	B-ORG
Medical	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
meeting	O
http://t.co/yaFysrdSCm	O

Labrador	B-LOC
woman	O
says	O
bear	O
in	O
live	O
trap	O
at	O
Tim	B-ORG
Hortons	I-ORG
'	O
cruel	O
'	O
http://t.co/ifGw5KTzWg	O

Tina	B-PER
Fontaine	I-PER
death	O
renews	O
calls	O
for	O
inquiry	O
into	O
missing	O
women	O
http://t.co/qSLHBvHFOx	O

Ontario	B-LOC
giant	O
could	O
be	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
next	O
NBA	B-ORG
star	O
http://t.co/z6FfHQcYBl	O

Maple	B-ORG
Leafs	I-ORG
creating	O
analytics	O
department	O
:	O
report	O
http://t.co/st0UfrXEPe	O

‘	O
Dirty	O
tricks	O
’	O
put	O
same-season	O
Arctic	B-LOC
relief	O
wells	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
:	O
Sierra	B-ORG
Club	I-ORG
http://t.co/0ocMcLhHcJ	O

Shakeil	B-PER
Boothe	I-PER
's	O
father	O
,	O
stepmother	O
file	O
notice	O
of	O
appeal	O
http://t.co/lFfNCovb1A	O

Aboriginal	O
activist	O
looks	O
at	O
harsh	O
realities	O
for	O
homeless	O
after	O
Fontaine	B-PER
,	O
Hall	B-PER
deaths	O
http://t.co/jQNMnYmDFT	O

Mount	B-LOC
Polley	I-LOC
spill	O
spurs	O
CNSC	B-ORG
order	O
to	O
check	O
uranium	O
ponds	O
http://t.co/tOixZHfmTW	O

Toronto	B-LOC
carjacking	O
sees	O
man	O
pistol-whipped	O
in	O
his	O
driveway	O
http://t.co/uX75H2Etn6	O

Tina	B-PER
Fontaine	I-PER
,	O
Faron	B-PER
Hall	I-PER
vigil	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
in	O
Winnipeg	B-LOC
http://t.co/JPARq6RyRM	O

'	O
Savage	O
'	O
pension	O
protest	O
at	O
Montreal	B-LOC
city	I-LOC
hall	I-LOC
condemned	O
by	O
mayor	O
http://t.co/jlEHcej1r3	O

Former	O
NHL	B-ORG
player	O
Moore	B-PER
reaches	O
settlement	O
with	O
Bertuzzi	B-PER
:	O
reports	O
http://t.co/hS0xGJ77ac	O

Top	O
10	O
most	O
livable	O
cities	O
include	O
Vancouver	B-LOC
,	O
Calgary	B-LOC
and	O
Toronto	B-LOC
http://t.co/0VKQpXa9dC	O

Aboriginal	O
groups	O
fear	O
for	O
George	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
caribou	O
herd	O
http://t.co/P8QZTy0GYl	O

Christopher	B-PER
Musqua	I-PER
,	O
'	O
high-risk	O
'	O
offender	O
,	O
wanted	O
on	O
Canada-wide	B-LOC
warrants	O
http://t.co/Rq7kG1pHZg	O

Stars	O
attending	O
this	O
year	O
's	O
TIFF	B-ORG
include	O
Bill	B-PER
Murray	I-PER
,	O
Channing	B-PER
Tatum	I-PER
and	O
Al	B-PER
Pacino	I-PER
http://t.co/gt1woKVLh8	O

Man	O
with	O
real-looking	O
pellet	O
guns	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
camouflage	O
arrested	O
in	O
Halifax	B-LOC
http://t.co/8eUk2vpLs6	O

Murderer	O
Evelyn	B-PER
Dick	I-PER
inspires	O
Hamilton	B-LOC
merchandise	O
line	O
http://t.co/kBQmUcaRv8	O

Justin	B-PER
Trudeau	I-PER
tries	O
to	O
shake	O
off	O
father	O
's	O
ghost	O
in	O
Alberta	B-LOC
http://t.co/MQkNK58yMW	O

Will	O
Toronto	B-LOC
's	O
airport	O
train	O
be	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
the	O
wallet	O
?	O
http://t.co/G5eCRIvVhI	O

Lac-	B-LOC
Mégantic	I-LOC
derailment	O
investigation	O
findings	O
released	O
today	O
http://t.co/2ZggjnaI39	O

Justin	B-PER
Trudeau	I-PER
's	O
home	O
break-in	O
:	O
Do	O
party	O
leaders	O
need	O
more	O
security	O
?	O
http://t.co/Gc4PI7i4MU	O

Khurram	B-PER
Sher	I-PER
terror	O
trial	O
verdict	O
expected	O
today	O
http://t.co/iuU6nCQUki	O

Popular	O
B	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
C	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
killer	O
whale	O
's	O
calf	O
finally	O
has	O
a	O
name	O
after	O
public	O
vote	O
http://t.co/V0zvBgG73c	O

Bodies	O
of	O
3	O
teens	O
who	O
drowned	O
in	O
Peace	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
recovered	O
http://t.co/Lg5AiWOkAy	O

Winnipeg	B-LOC
's	O
'	O
homeless	O
hero	O
'	O
Faron	B-PER
Hall	I-PER
found	O
dead	O
in	O
Red	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
http://t.co/rgvfCNISDW	O

How	O
the	O
defensive	O
shift	O
and	O
big	O
data	O
are	O
changing	O
baseball	O
http://t.co/nQ80zEdjeL	O

WATCH	O
:	O
Remembering	O
25	O
years	O
of	O
CBC	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
-	O
December	O
31	O
,	O
1999	O
:	O
Canada	B-LOC
rings	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
millennium	O
http://t.co/fHXtvCe6Bc	O
#CBCNN	B-ORG

Girl	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
bag	O
in	O
Red	B-LOC
River	I-LOC
;	O
police	O
seek	O
tips	O
on	O
slaying	O
http://t.co/8R2Bn6prOX	O

Alberta	B-ORG
PC	I-ORG
leadership	O
candidates	O
to	O
face	O
off	O
in	O
public	O
forum	O
http://t.co/0tTDV4D6TS	O

Rob	B-PER
Ford	I-PER
looking	O
for	O
answers	O
to	O
Toronto	B-LOC
's	O
'	O
raccoon	O
problem	O
'	O
http://t.co/MqGVjEk9AO	O

Rona	B-PER
Ambrose	I-PER
tells	O
doctors	O
anti-drug	O
campaign	O
not	O
political	O
http://t.co/vlBkAKu61t	O

Python	O
captured	O
in	O
Ontario	B-LOC
woman	O
's	O
living	O
room	O
http://t.co/i3Mu2nFHKN	O

Alberta	B-LOC
actor	O
in	O
Emmy-winning	O
Apple	B-ORG
ad	O
calls	O
it	O
'	O
a	O
wonderful	O
experience	O
'	O
http://t.co/k0mNYUSJ5r	O

Who	O
is	O
the	O
856	B-ORG
gang	I-ORG
that	O
’	O
s	O
moved	O
into	O
Yellowknife	B-LOC
?	O
http://t.co/MveWCR0yZ3	O

CRA	B-ORG
charity	O
audits	O
trigger	O
House	O
finance	O
committee	O
recall	O
http://t.co/vmduNsHFG2	O

N	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
B	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
air	O
ambulance	O
service	O
back	O
up	O
after	O
crash	O
that	O
killed	O
pilot	O
,	O
paramedic	O
http://t.co/ba9k4YzxbQ	O

WATCH	O
:	O
Remembering	O
25	O
years	O
of	O
CBC	B-ORG
News	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
-	O
April	O
23	O
,	O
2010	O
:	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
first	O
Olympic	O
Athlete	O
's	O
Parade	O
https://t.co/7LBEAb9MgY	O
#CBCNN	B-ORG

Bell	B-ORG
lawsuit	O
over	O
expiry	O
of	O
prepaid	O
plans	O
gets	O
green	O
light	O
http://t.co/bYHujYcurq	O

Mount	B-LOC
Polley	I-LOC
mine	O
spill	O
:	O
Minister	O
to	O
reveal	O
plans	O
for	O
investigation	O
http://t.co/TX4cni3Ij9	O

3	O
storylines	O
to	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
2014	O
Liberal	B-ORG
Party	I-ORG
caucus	O
http://t.co/wIZAiA7PH0	O

Tory	O
MP	O
Ryan	B-PER
Leef	I-PER
apologizes	O
for	O
joke	O
about	O
Trudeau	B-PER
break-in	O
http://t.co/yYAs5FsFoL	O

Remembering	O
25	O
years	O
of	O
CBC	B-ORG
News	O
Network	O
-	O
December	O
31	O
,	O
1999	O
:	O
Canada	B-LOC
rings	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
millennium	O
http://t.co/fHXtvCe6Bc	O
#CBCNN	O

Trudeau	B-PER
confident	O
Liberals	B-ORG
on	O
right	O
track	O
to	O
victory	O
in	O
2015	O
federal	O
election	O
http://t.co/E3IKvM81vH	O

Trudeau	B-PER
asks	O
RCMP	B-ORG
for	O
security	O
risk	O
assessment	O
after	O
break-in	O
at	O
his	O
home	B-LOC
http://t.co/T3nEnljTba	O

Drone	O
video	O
shows	O
stubborness	O
,	O
severity	O
of	O
Goodridge	B-LOC
Street	I-LOC
fire	O
http://t.co/K4yXbW3hvL	O

Prime	O
Minister	O
Stephen	B-PER
Harper	I-PER
takes	O
another	O
northern	O
tour	O
http://t.co/uOonGIVcvI	O

UPDATE	O
:	O
Eugenie	B-PER
Bouchard	I-PER
loses	O
to	O
Petra	B-PER
Kvitova	I-PER
at	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
http://t.co/prNpRXTBmN	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Canadian	O
Eugenie	B-PER
Bouchard	I-PER
loses	O
to	O
Petra	B-PER
Kvitova	I-PER
in	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
final	O
6	O
-	O
3	O
,	O
6	O
-	O
0	O
.	O
More	O
coming	O
.	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
Milos	B-PER
Raonic	I-PER
falls	O
to	O
Roger	B-PER
Federer	I-PER
in	O
straight	O
sets	O
in	O
the	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
semifinal	O
.	O

Manitoba	B-LOC
declares	O
flood	O
emergency	O
,	O
seeks	O
help	O
from	O
military	O
:	O
http://t.co/athfMRZwL8	O

Calgary	B-LOC
police	O
say	O
progress	O
is	O
being	O
made	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
missing	O
boy	O
,	O
grandparents	O
http://t.co/yKjZoc1Twq	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Ontario	B-LOC
can	O
invest	O
in	O
economy	O
while	O
balancing	O
books	O
:	O
Wynne	B-PER
http://t.co/tBLUR1VFIf	O

Ca	O
n't	O
stop	O
Bernardo	B-PER
from	O
communicating	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
world	O
:	O
Peter	B-PER
MacKay	I-PER
http://t.co/OD0NgSvGZM	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
UFC	B-ORG
's	O
Alexis	B-PER
Davis	I-PER
says	O
she	O
's	O
comfortable	O
being	O
the	O
underdog	O
http://t.co/ePNRZSPlRt	O

Arthur	B-PER
likely	O
to	O
lose	O
strength	O
but	O
bring	O
heavy	O
winds	O
,	O
rain	O
to	O
Atlantic	B-LOC
Canada	I-LOC
http://t.co/dJdGBLdwJG	O

Farmers	O
in	O
Manitoba	B-LOC
,	O
Saskatchewan	B-LOC
hit	O
by	O
flooding	O
,	O
crops	O
and	O
land	O
under	O
water	O
http://t.co/6mWDEhAnP0	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Money	O
Monitor	O
-	O
How	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
unclaimed	O
assets	O
http://t.co/39bc5WlRzz	O

Government	O
open	O
to	O
amendments	O
to	O
proposed	O
prostitution	O
law	O
:	O
Peter	B-PER
MacKay	I-PER
http://t.co/DBbFM0jneh	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
New	O
Movies	O
-	O
Clive	B-PER
Owen	I-PER
&	O
Juliette	B-PER
Binoche	I-PER
play	O
romantic	O
leads	O
http://t.co/EpxMdigyk1	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Lac-	B-LOC
Megantic	I-LOC
residents	O
still	O
haunted	O
by	O
train	O
disaster	O
http://t.co/QZ8r8zkA5w	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
Bouchard	B-PER
defeats	O
Halep	B-PER
to	O
reach	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
singles	O
final	O
.	O
More	O
coming	O
.	O

1st-set	O
tiebreaker	O
of	O
Halep-	B-PER
Bouchard	I-PER
semi	O
at	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
delayed	O
by	O
ill	O
fan	O
http://t.co/zno0J5TMHL	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Eastern	B-LOC
Saskatchewan	I-LOC
hit	O
hard	O
by	O
flooding	O
http://t.co/YjxmBAs8ls	O

Man	O
accused	O
of	O
killing	O
three	O
Mounties	B-ORG
to	O
appear	O
in	O
court	O
http://t.co/sNTkwuc6Pe	O

Arthur	B-PER
becomes	O
hurricane	O
,	O
will	O
bring	O
messy	O
weather	O
to	O
Atlantic	B-LOC
Canada	I-LOC
Saturday	O
http://t.co/p2JhZm3ZIG	O

After	O
Lac-	B-LOC
Megantic	I-LOC
,	O
critics	O
say	O
more	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
prevent	O
another	O
oil-by-rail	O
disaster	O
http://t.co/5keeivMxqV	O

ICYMI	B-ORG
VIDEO	O
:	O
Calgary	B-LOC
family	O
's	O
emotional	O
plea	O
for	O
son	O
's	O
return	O
http://t.co/OceLRV0lCF	O

A	O
look	O
at	O
diverse	O
teams	O
competing	O
in	O
second	O
'	O
Amazing	B-ORG
Race	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
'	O
http://t.co/gaPIVGNelV	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
Shirtless	O
jogger	O
who	O
yelled	O
at	O
Rob	B-PER
Ford	I-PER
a	O
‘	O
bad	O
apple	O
’	O
:	O
Doug	B-PER
Ford	I-PER
http://t.co/psk0nV6qVg	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
job	O
with	O
a	O
milliner	O
http://t.co/1uPQfjJzRX	O

Prairie	O
farmers	O
,	O
communities	O
tackle	O
flooding	O
as	O
more	O
declare	O
emergencies	O
http://t.co/4W909vK6m1	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Tim	B-ORG
Hortons	I-ORG
credit	O
card	O
with	O
built-in	O
buttons	O
a	O
first	O
in	O
Canada	B-LOC
http://t.co/Je6YxxqQWE	O

Calgary	B-LOC
police	O
chief	O
questions	O
whether	O
reward	O
would	O
help	O
in	O
Amber	O
Alert	O
case	O
http://t.co/HdRvhaiJd1	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Ontario	B-LOC
Tories	O
must	O
stop	O
'	O
attacking	O
people	O
'	O
:	O
Interim	O
leader	O
http://t.co/u11lXh4uop	O

Porter	B-ORG
Airlines	I-ORG
orders	O
to	O
pay	O
cash	O
to	O
passengers	O
bumped	O
from	O
domestic	O
flights	O
http://t.co/WWRW3pFFFN	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
'	O
Professional	O
scavenger	O
'	O
hunts	O
for	O
treasures	O
in	O
Montreal	B-LOC
http://t.co/fglYHYtPpA	O

Canadian	O
journalist	O
convicted	O
in	O
Egypt	B-LOC
in	O
'	O
terrible	O
state	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
'	O
family	O
says	O
http://t.co/oonOw2azcT	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Gaming	O
Goods	O
-	O
New	O
releases	O
offer	O
different	O
takes	O
on	O
war	O
http://t.co/xUMAvd7uh7	O

UPDATE	O
:	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
Eugenie	B-PER
Bouchard	I-PER
advances	O
to	O
semifinals	O
at	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
http://t.co/t5pa8IFSPh	O

Canada	B-LOC
's	O
Eugenie	B-PER
Bouchard	I-PER
has	O
advanced	O
to	O
the	O
semifinals	O
at	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
.	O
More	O
coming	O
.	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Vancouver	B-ORG
Canucks	I-ORG
GM	O
says	O
Ryan	B-PER
Miller	I-PER
is	O
'	O
intense	O
and	O
focused	O
'	O
http://t.co/r4deovd8b6	O

B	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
C	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
school	O
districts	O
to	O
show	O
teachers	O
summer	O
classes	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
held	O
http://t.co/Ukas3EpT7H	O

A	O
year	O
later	O
,	O
deadly	O
train	O
disaster	O
still	O
haunts	O
people	O
of	O
Lac-	B-LOC
Megantic	I-LOC
http://t.co/8Q7mZUZq64	O

UPDATE	O
:	O
Flooding	O
forces	O
evacuations	O
and	O
strains	O
sewers	O
on	O
waterlogged	O
Prairies	B-LOC
http://t.co/SjfI0nVScN	O

Rob	B-PER
Ford	I-PER
begs	O
for	O
another	O
chance	O
,	O
says	O
commitment	O
to	O
living	O
clean	O
'	O
unwavering	O
'	O
http://t.co/OIWAluvyAC	O

Rob	B-PER
Ford	I-PER
speaking	O
live	O
now	O
MT	O
@Perkel	O
:	O
Ford	B-PER
:	O
'	O
For	O
a	O
long	O
,	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
resisted	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
getting	O
help	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
complete	O
denial	O
.	O
#RobFord	B-PER

Railroad	O
involved	O
in	O
Lac-	B-LOC
Megantic	I-LOC
explosion	O
has	O
its	O
Canadian	B-LOC
assets	O
sold	O
http://t.co/AnKygll2ZR	O

Winnipeg	B-LOC
man	O
kept	O
kids	O
behind	O
bars	O
in	O
Mexico	B-LOC
,	O
exposed	O
them	O
to	O
prostitutes	O
,	O
drugs	O
http://t.co/afnHiPU0aj	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Gino	B-PER
Odjick	I-PER
fighting	O
his	O
'	O
hardest	O
battle	O
'	O
:	O
Son	O
http://t.co/SUCZwMuJrD	O

Canada	B-LOC
's	O
Bouchard	B-PER
through	O
to	O
Wimbledon	B-LOC
quarter-finals	O
with	O
win	O
over	O
Cornet	B-PER
http://t.co/328IyhPRyy	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Style	O
Session	O
-	O
Suits	O
for	O
summer	O
http://t.co/Ibdpf1hSyX	O

Despite	O
flooding	O
,	O
WestJet	B-ORG
takes	O
off	O
from	O
water-besieged	O
Manitoba	B-LOC
airport	O
.	O
http://t.co/SjfI0nVScN	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
Mulcair	B-PER
and	O
Trudeau	B-PER
help	O
celebrate	O
Toronto	B-LOC
pride	O
festival	O
http://t.co/6vmdssJT4X	O

RT	O
@	B-ORG
CdnPress_Arts	B-ORG
:	O
Bestselling	O
author	O
@	B-PER
jenniferweiner	B-PER
draws	O
on	O
personal	O
experience	O
for	O
'	O
All	O
Fall	O
Down	O
'	O
http://t.co/j1lfa0wbhB	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
Stampeders	B-ORG
'	O
Jon	B-PER
Cornish	I-PER
helping	O
fight	O
homophobia	O
in	O
sport	O
http://t.co/wRiLf3sLe3	O

Voters	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
polls	O
today	O
in	O
four	O
federal	O
byelections	O
in	O
Ontario	B-LOC
and	O
Alberta	B-LOC
http://t.co/o8ERNukBI3	O

Prairies	B-LOC
hope	O
for	O
dry	O
skies	O
to	O
ease	O
flooding	O
http://t.co/xhrxR2T9D3	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
Meet	O
the	O
Habs	B-ORG
draft	O
pick	O
with	O
a	O
colourful	O
personality	O
http://t.co/1xQJklCtZh	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
Men	O
's	O
summer	O
music	O
festival	O
fashions	O
http://t.co/HtCXWlDsTF	O

Indian	O
rocket	O
successfully	O
launches	O
2	O
small	O
Canadian	O
satellites	O
http://t.co/yDaTUnqnVR	O

A	O
not-so-long	O
weekend	O
this	O
year	O
,	O
as	O
Canada	B-LOC
Day	O
falls	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
http://t.co/d5t3bxgSZc	O

After	O
150	O
years	O
on	O
U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
soil	O
,	O
artifact	O
from	O
Charlottetown	B-LOC
is	O
sailing	O
home	O
http://t.co/u5AzTL4nmR	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Should	O
Canada	B-LOC
Day	O
always	O
make	O
a	O
long	O
weekend	O
?	O
http://t.co/JqeIxBQ8bK	O

Experts	O
say	O
former	O
Canuck	B-ORG
Gino	B-PER
Odjick	I-PER
's	O
illness	O
is	O
extremely	O
rare	O
and	O
nearly	O
always	O
fatal	O
http://t.co/CbYHOPwXSh	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Kathleen	B-PER
Wynne	I-PER
hopes	O
for	O
collaboration	O
with	O
mayors	O
on	O
transit	O
http://t.co/IcAwAsN2iO	O

Bell	B-ORG
supports	O
pick-and-pay	O
,	O
calls	O
for	O
changes	O
to	O
local	O
TV	O
business	O
model	O
http://t.co/icA1onRTZy	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Next	O
Ontario	B-LOC
lieutenant-governor	O
to	O
focus	O
on	O
'	O
sustainability	O
'	O
http://t.co/wDzIlqnrlM	O

Love	O
and	O
learn	O
?	O
Pride	O
seems	O
to	O
outpace	O
knowledge	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
Canada	B-LOC
:	O
poll	O
http://t.co/WZU1fknKKf	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Try	O
this	O
quick	O
knot	O
braid	O
hairstyle	O
on	O
hot	O
summer	O
weekends	O
http://t.co/qGui7imx86	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Canadian	O
prankster	O
's	O
show	O
'	O
Nathan	B-PER
For	O
You	O
'	O
back	O
for	O
Season	O
2	O
http://t.co/bpNt6O8hxQ	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
@dj_friend	O
is	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Next	O
Big	O
Thing	O
:	O
'	O
The	O
Killing	O
'	O
resuscitated	O
on	O
Netflix	B-ORG
http://t.co/FVXOby59bU	O

A	O
century	O
later	O
,	O
Canada	B-LOC
before	O
the	O
First	O
World	O
War	O
seems	O
a	O
world	O
apart	O
http://t.co/dijoCRPnu9	O

One	O
hundred	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
Europe	B-LOC
began	O
its	O
slow	O
sleepwalk	O
towards	O
war	O
http://t.co/ZIvfDx0Qr9	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Report	O
says	O
police	O
dog	O
bites	O
rampant	O
in	O
B	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
C	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
http://t.co/YQOXFnpj6N	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
'	O
Amazing	O
Race	O
Canada	B-LOC
'	O
host	O
aims	O
to	O
step	O
up	O
his	O
game	O
for	O
Season	O
2	O
http://t.co/InK9G1bNpc	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Andrew	B-PER
Wiggins	I-PER
:	O
Winning	O
NBA	B-ORG
draft	O
does	O
n't	O
'	O
feel	O
real	O
'	O
http://t.co/4TcIVyUE0x	O

Cleveland	B-LOC
Cavaliers	O
select	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
Andrew	B-PER
Wiggins	I-PER
with	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
pick	O
in	O
NBA	B-ORG
draft	O
http://t.co/DfeV4vLOWi	O

Former	O
Vancouver	B-ORG
Canuck	I-ORG
Gino	B-PER
Odjick	I-PER
says	O
he	O
's	O
been	O
diagnosed	O
with	O
rare	O
terminal	O
illness	O
http://t.co/MQt8DIl1Po	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
B	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
C	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
grand	O
chief	O
'	O
ecstatic	O
'	O
over	O
Supreme	O
Court	O
land	O
title	O
ruling	O
http://t.co/rKWhxKE4nO	O

ICYMI	O
VIDEO	O
:	O
More	O
than	O
200	O
marry	O
at	O
Grand	O
Pride	O
wedding	O
in	O
Toronto	B-LOC
http://t.co/ZsTd7yK79X	O

RCMP	B-ORG
recover	O
Brad	B-PER
Jacob	I-PER
's	O
stolen	O
2014	O
Olympic	O
ring	O
.	O
http://t.co/MF9fIHWsR5	O

VIDEO	O
:	O
Optimus	B-PER
Prime	I-PER
is	O
back	O
in	O
new	O
'	O
Transformers	B-ORG
'	O
movie	O
http://t.co/SBhN05SUSX	O

Canada	B-ORG
Post	I-ORG
cuts	O
home	O
delivery	O
but	O
continues	O
postage-free	O
mail	O
for	O
MPs	O
http://t.co/lJ3t2lkvj9	O

Australian	O
Prime	O
Minister	O
Tony	B-PER
Abbott	I-PER
to	O
meet	O
Harper	B-PER
and	O
GG	B-PER
today	O
http://t.co/DxcRTGDgP5	O

Harper	B-PER
stands	O
firm	O
against	O
'	O
extreme	O
nationalist	O
,	O
imperialist	O
'	O
Putin	B-PER
http://t.co/E2qCvwu9GW	O

'	O
Freedom	O
,	O
democracy	O
,	O
justice	O
'	O
:	O
Harper	B-PER
,	O
world	O
leaders	O
mark	O
70	O
years	O
since	O
D-Day	O
http://t.co/RsUbOUNBzw	O

Vets	O
giving	O
D-Day	O
one	O
last	O
salute	O
wonder	O
about	O
the	O
world	O
they	O
're	O
leaving	O
behind	O
http://t.co/klprz0O7qj	O

Court	O
clarifies	O
aboriginal	O
sentencing	O
rules	O
http://t.co/krwuouerFP	O

Harper	B-PER
begins	O
D-Day	O
sojourn	O
in	O
Normandy	B-LOC
,	O
will	O
meet	O
vets	O
at	O
Juno	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
http://t.co/P5XloPmtxU	O

New	O
link	O
RT	O
@	B-PER
mariababbage	B-PER
:	O
Dissecting	O
Ontario	B-LOC
leaders	O
'	O
energy	O
claims	O
via	O
CP	O
's	O
@	B-PER
steve_rennie	B-PER
:	O
http://t.co/TKCD96IBdL	O
#voteon	O
#ONpoli	O

Elections	O
watchdog	O
mutes	O
criticism	O
of	O
bill	O
overhauling	O
election	O
rules	O
http://t.co/MLwKeQSMs0	O

Info	O
watchdog	O
warns	O
access	O
system	O
fragile	O
as	O
complaints	O
to	O
her	O
office	O
rise	O
http://t.co/0d9hLLc3Nn	O

Today	O
on	O
the	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
:	O
Vets	O
'	O
spouses	O
take	O
centre	O
stage	O
http://t.co/lVbU2DXDzm	O

Warrants	O
issued	O
for	O
arrest	O
of	O
U	B-LOC
.	I-LOC
S	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
,	O
UK	B-LOC
nationals	O
in	O
alleged	O
bribery	O
case	O
http://t.co/tGq4X3nIBT	O

Witness	O
with	O
immunity	O
appears	O
at	O
robocalls	O
trial	O
http://t.co/uHodCumy2Z	O

Today	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	B-LOC
:	O
Veterans	O
descend	O
on	O
Parliament	B-LOC
to	O
protest	O
changes	O
to	O
benefits	O
http://t.co/4oVecka4II	O

Side	O
trip	O
to	O
Ukraine	B-LOC
on	O
Saturday	O
added	O
to	O
Harper	B-PER
's	O
European	O
itinerary	O
http://t.co/y7xG9TKQDM	O

JoAnne	B-PER
Buth	I-PER
leaves	O
Senate	B-ORG
to	O
return	O
to	O
her	O
"	O
roots	O
"	O
in	O
agriculture	O
http://t.co/Q5TwWJ0GqV	O

Quebec	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Appeal	I-ORG
judge	O
Clement	B-PER
Gascon	I-PER
nominated	O
to	O
Supreme	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
http://t.co/EFsYCaDNBD	O

UPDATE	O
:	O
Commons	O
officials	O
,	O
not	O
political	O
rivals	O
,	O
said	O
NDP	B-ORG
broke	O
mail	O
rules	O
http://t.co/CjNKM6Dijd	O

Speaker	O
says	O
NDP	B-ORG
mailouts	O
broke	O
Commons	O
rules	O
;	O
investigation	O
widens	O
http://t.co/LExf0iFR5v	O

Harper	B-PER
heads	O
off	O
to	O
Europe	B-LOC
for	O
G	B-ORG
7	I-ORG
,	O
D-Day	O
events	O
,	O
with	O
Putin	B-PER
on	O
his	O
mind	O
http://t.co/W6Ja65soCL	O

Missile	O
defence	O
program	O
would	O
mean	O
smoother	O
decisions	O
,	O
clearer	O
threats	O
:	O
general	O
http://t.co/lMeC68YAPV	O

Harper	B-PER
on	O
U	B-LOC
.	O
S	B-LOC
.	O
climate-change	O
coal	O
crackdown	O
:	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
done	O
that	O
http://t.co/Vw54ioH9vO	O

Survey	O
says	O
buying	O
sex	O
should	O
be	O
illegal	O
,	O
but	O
selling	O
it	O
should	O
n't	O
be	O
an	O
offence	O
http://t.co/PAoM6bhuwC	O

Today	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	B-LOC
:	O
court	O
appearances	O
,	O
security	O
and	O
pipeline	O
testimony	O
http://t.co/rFJLJa28kT	O

Ottawa	B-LOC
posts	O
$	O
6	O
.	O
7	O
billion	O
deficit	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
but	O
remains	O
ahead	O
of	O
pace	O
for	O
year	O
http://t.co/XVE0iAt0Sb	O

Today	O
on	O
the	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
:	O
Harper	B-PER
wraps	O
up	O
women	O
,	O
child	O
health	O
forum	O
in	O
Toronto	B-LOC
http://t.co/gIKrxH5TY5	O

Speaker	O
contradicts	O
Mulcair	B-PER
on	O
NDP	B-ORG
bulk	O
mailings	O
,	O
satellite	O
offices	O
http://t.co/UC8WvK5W86	O

Tories	B-ORG
defend	O
choice	O
of	O
government	O
insider	O
for	O
federal	O
privacy	O
czar	O
http://t.co/CsRwUeciBr	O

Jordan	B-LOC
's	O
queen	O
calls	O
child	O
deaths	O
an	O
outrage	O
,	O
thanks	O
Harper	B-PER
for	O
support	O
http://t.co/kAv6tMrL1t	O

Alexander	B-PER
blasts	O
opposition	O
as	O
immigration	O
bill	O
goes	O
to	O
second	O
reading	O
http://t.co/moE1gQTR8B	O

MacKay	B-PER
says	O
he	O
wants	O
consensus	O
with	O
Quebec	B-LOC
on	O
Supreme	B-ORG
Court	I-ORG
judge	O
http://t.co/l4V9FhsIdb	O

New	O
Tory	B-ORG
defence	O
shopping	O
list	O
for	O
military	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
work	O
in	O
progress	O
http://t.co/VXhzg3wS9G	O

Immigration	O
bill	O
poised	O
for	O
second	O
reading	O
in	O
Commons	O
as	O
critics	O
raise	O
alarms	O
http://t.co/BRNRz2hVB3	O

Former	O
soldier	O
Sen	B-PER
.	I-PER
Romeo	I-PER
Dallaire	I-PER
says	O
he	O
's	O
resigning	O
from	O
Senate	B-ORG
http://t.co/QaUXwoQKfG	O

Today	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	B-LOC
:	O
Harper	B-PER
heads	O
to	O
Toronto	B-LOC
for	O
maternal	O
,	O
child	O
health	O
summit	O
http://t.co/lDL8B1bt2P	O

Electronic	O
spy	O
agency	O
gathers	O
personal	O
information	O
in	O
cyberdefence	O
role	O
http://t.co/m7tiYElJiq	O

Harper	B-PER
's	O
kids	O
,	O
moms	O
aid	O
plan	O
for	O
poor	O
countries	O
polarizes	O
at	O
home	O
http://t.co/qeIDd35GQX	O

Federal	O
government	O
working	O
to	O
remove	O
outdated	O
job	O
posting	O
from	O
Canada	B-LOC
Job	O
Bank	O
http://t.co/hUvSa8N4EY	O

Chiefs	O
gather	O
in	O
Ottawa	B-LOC
to	O
decide	O
fate	O
of	O
$	O
1	O
.	O
9	O
-	O
billion	O
First	O
Nations	O
education	O
bill	O
http://t.co/DKYAXLhnhd	O

Sexual	O
assault	O
and	O
harassment	O
not	O
part	O
of	O
military	O
culture	O
,	O
says	O
top	O
commander	O
http://t.co/vOTiYu4JhX	O

Big	O
banks	O
,	O
government	O
agree	O
on	O
no-cost	O
accounts	O
for	O
low-income	O
seniors	O
,	O
youth	O
http://t.co/YxyiuKtEBN	O

Liberal	B-ORG
MP	O
John	B-PER
McKay	I-PER
secretly	O
taped	O
criticizing	O
Trudeau	B-PER
http://t.co/XzqtVz5X3J	O

Today	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	B-LOC
:	O
First	B-LOC
Nations	I-LOC
leaders	O
begin	O
the	O
task	O
of	O
finding	O
a	O
new	O
leader	O
http://t.co/On9LUvpHX8	O

Canada	B-LOC
clicks	O
OK	O
for	O
use	O
of	O
airborne	O
devices	O
http://t.co/6zRGs8aMzx	O

Muslim	O
group	O
takes	O
next	O
step	O
in	O
court	O
action	O
against	O
PMO	B-ORG
spokesman	O
http://t.co/l25XYm0EgS	O

Search	O
on	O
for	O
17	O
-	O
year-old	O
boater	O
missing	O
near	O
North	B-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
http://t.co/tgINt7Sgmz	O

#Barrie	B-LOC
man	O
charged	O
after	O
female	O
forced	O
to	O
perform	O
sex	O
to	O
pay	O
drug	O
debts	O
:	O
police	O
http://t.co/aMVmEm7FQG	O

ICYMI	O
Clerical	O
error	O
snatches	O
Thornhill	B-LOC
riding	O
from	O
Liberals	O
,	O
gives	O
it	O
to	O
Tories	O
http://t.co/Zo23qzKnjg	O
#onpoli	O

McGuinty	B-PER
says	O
his	O
office	O
was	O
'	O
overwhelmingly	O
verbal	O
,	O
'	O
kept	O
few	O
records	O
http://t.co/1OFXAmni8o	O
#onpoli	O

UPDATED	O
Wynne	B-PER
to	O
bring	O
back	O
legislature	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
re-introduce	O
budget	O
;	O
Tories	O
lick	O
wounds	O
http://t.co/riIUn42Mvp	O
by	O
@	B-PER
mariababbage	B-PER
@CPnewsboy	O

Wynne	B-PER
promises	O
to	O
bring	O
back	O
legislature	O
on	O
July	O
2	O
,	O
re-introduce	O
budget	O
http://t.co/fjTKKUUlvf	O

Our	O
@	B-ORG
Storify	B-ORG
on	O
the	O
Ontario	B-LOC
election	O
#voteon	O
http://t.co/xWsYrudMzU	O

Our	O
latest	O
on	O
the	O
Ontario	B-LOC
election	O
:	O
Liberals	B-ORG
cruise	O
to	O
surprise	O
majority	O
#voteon	O
http://t.co/pFjxNn5gqe	O

New	B-ORG
Democrats	I-ORG
seats	I-ORG
largely	I-ORG
unchanged	I-ORG
in	O
Ontario	B-LOC
election	O
,	O
but	O
power	O
changes	O
in	O
majority	O
government	O
#voteon	O
http://t.co/UJAlSs9KHp	O

So	O
what	O
will	O
the	O
next	O
#onpoli	O
budget	O
look	O
like	O
?	O
Hint	O
:	O
exactly	O
like	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
triggered	O
the	O
election	O
.	O
Highlights	O
:	O
http://t.co/EYxA4zbLbs	O

With	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
stepping	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
contention	O
for	O
the	O
PC	B-ORG
leadership	O
?	O
We	O
highlight	O
5	O
possibilities	O
:	O
http://t.co/iE13NF9VIQ	O
#voteon	O

Latest	O
story	O
:	O
Ontario	B-LOC
Liberals	B-ORG
cruise	O
to	O
unexpected	O
majority	O
http://t.co/dYKmxhkYFE	O

Latest	O
story	O
:	O
Hudak	B-PER
falls	O
well	O
short	O
in	O
Ontario	B-LOC
campaign	O
,	O
steps	O
down	O
as	O
PC	O
leader	O
http://t.co/NlPVxw6IGK	O

.	O
@	B-PER
kathleen_wynne	B-PER
says	O
election	O
victory	O
belongs	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
takes	O
pride	O
in	O
being	O
the	O
province	O
's	O
1st	O
elected	O
female	O
Premier	O
.	O
#voteon	O

.	O
@	B-PER
kathleen_wynne	B-PER
says	O
job	O
now	O
is	O
to	O
build	O
the	O
province	O
up	O
for	O
all	O
residents	O
irrespective	O
of	O
party	O
loyalty	O
.	O
#voteon	O

Newly	O
reelected	O
Premier	O
@	B-PER
kathleen_wynne	B-PER
is	O
giving	O
her	O
victory	O
speech	O
.	O
#voteon	O

.	O
@	B-PER
andreahorwath	B-PER
says	O
her	O
job	O
is	O
to	O
fight	O
for	O
"	O
change	O
that	O
makes	O
sense	O
.	O
"	O
Ends	O
speech	O
.	O
#voteon	O

.	O
@	B-PER
andreahorwath	B-PER
congratulates	O
all	O
candidates	O
,	O
promises	O
to	O
keep	O
holding	O
new	O
government	O
accountable	O
.	O
#voteon	O

.	O
@	B-PER
andreahorwath	B-PER
now	O
speaking	O
,	O
promises	O
#ondp	B-ORG
will	O
"	O
keep	O
fighting	O
"	O
for	O
Ontario	B-LOC
families	O
.	O
#voteon	O

From	O
Liberal	B-ORG
hq	I-ORG
:	O
RT	O
@	B-PER
mariababbage	B-PER
:	O
Big	O
cheers	O
as	O
Hudak	B-PER
announces	O
resignation	O
as	O
leader	O
.	O
#voteon	O
#ONpoli	B-LOC
@	B-ORG
CPOntario	B-ORG

She	O
speaks	O
soon	O
.	O
RT	O
@	B-PER
allisonjones_cp	B-PER
:	O
Crowd	O
still	O
sparse	O
at	O
Andrea	B-PER
Horwath	I-PER
HQ	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
dozen	O
supporters	O
mingling	O
with	O
staffers	O
.	O

Early	O
story	O
:	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
steps	O
down	O
as	O
#pcpo	B-ORG
leader	O
:	O
http://t.co/0pTEYjAsHb	O
#voteon	O

icymi	B-ORG
RT	O
@CPnewsboy	O
:	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
quits	O
.	O
#voteon	O

.	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
says	O
it	O
's	O
an	O
honour	O
to	O
represent	O
Niagara	B-LOC
West-	I-LOC
Glanbrook	I-LOC
,	O
offers	O
general	O
thanks	O
.	O

Breaking	O
:	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
says	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
leading	O
Progressive	B-ORG
Conservatives	I-ORG
into	O
the	O
next	O
election	O
,	O
will	O
stay	O
on	O
until	O
new	O
ldr	O
chosen	O
.	O

.	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
says	O
he	O
's	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
campaign	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
the	O
"	O
clear	O
vision	O
"	O
behind	O
it	O
.	O

.	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
says	O
@	B-PER
kathleen_wynne	B-PER
has	O
a	O
mandate	O
to	O
deliver	O
meaningful	O
change	O
,	O
calls	O
for	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
"	O
wasteful	O
bureaucracy	O
.	O
"	O
#voteon	O

.	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
is	O
addressing	O
supporters	O
.	O
Thanks	O
crowd	O
for	O
local	O
reelection	O
,	O
congratulates	O
rivals	O
.	O
#voteon	O

Against	O
long	O
odds	O
,	O
Wynne	B-PER
lives	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
Via	O
@	B-PER
mariababbage	B-PER
:	O
http://t.co/0pf0NOX06b	O

Ontario	B-LOC
Liberals	B-ORG
win	O
fourth	O
mandate	O
;	O
cross	O
into	O
majority	O
territory	O
http://t.co/nztm5TUuyI	O

Canadian	B-ORG
Press	I-ORG
election	O
call	O
:	O
the	O
Ontario	B-LOC
Liberals	B-ORG
have	O
been	O
reelected	O
with	O
an	O
majority	O
mandate	O
.	O
#Voteon	O

The	O
PC	B-ORG
's	O
may	O
have	O
lost	O
some	O
seats	O
tonight	O
,	O
but	O
@	B-PER
timhudak	B-PER
has	O
been	O
reelected	O
in	O
Niagara	B-LOC
West-	I-LOC
Glanbrook	I-LOC
.	O
#OnPoli	O

Unsurprisingly	O
,	O
@	B-PER
kathleen_wynne	B-PER
has	O
been	O
reelected	O
in	O
her	O
riding	O
of	O
Don	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
West	I-LOC
.	O
#Voteon	O

Liberal	B-ORG
hopes	O
were	O
pinned	O
on	O
Toronto	B-LOC
area	O
,	O
&	O
the	O
numbers	O
show	O
why	O
:	O
currently	O
leading	O
in	O
21	O
of	O
24	O
races	O
.	O
NDP	B-ORG
up	O
in	O
2	O
,	O
PCs	B-ORG
have	O
edge	O
in	O
1	O
.	O

Canadian	B-ORG
Press	I-ORG
election	O
call	O
!	O
Liberals	O
reelected	O
,	O
majority	O
or	O
minority	O
still	O
to	O
be	O
determined	O
.	O

Liberals	B-ORG
have	O
an	O
official	O
elected	O
seat	O
now	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
Leading	O
in	O
51	O
other	O
races	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
.	O
#VoteOn	B-LOC

The	O
Conservatives	B-ORG
and	O
NDP	B-ORG
are	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
with	O
a	O
seat	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
but	O
Liberals	B-ORG
leading	O
right	O
now	O
.	O
#OnPoli	O

Keep	O
track	O
of	O
results	O
in	O
realtime	O
with	O
our	O
interactive	O
riding	O
map	O
:	O
http://t.co/SAncPGNGGZ	O
#VoteOn	O

The	O
polls	O
are	O
closed	O
&	O
our	O
team	O
is	O
ready	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
all	O
results	O
!	O
@	B-PER
cpnewsboy	B-PER
@	I-PER
mariababbage	I-PER
@	I-PER
allisonjones_cp	I-PER
@	I-PER
dianamehta	I-PER
@	I-PER
perkel	I-PER
@	I-PER
mich_mcq	I-PER

For	O
highlights	O
from	O
the	O
leaders	O
HQs	O
,	O
follow	O
@	B-PER
mariababbage	B-PER
with	O
libs	B-ORG
,	O
@cpnewsboy	O
with	O
PCs	B-ORG
,	O
@	B-PER
allisonjones_cp	B-PER
with	O
ndp	B-ORG
.	O
#OnPoli	O

One	O
hour	O
until	O
polls	O
close	O
&	O
our	O
election	O
coverage	O
begins	O
!	O
Stay	O
tuned	O
right	O
here	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
details	O
.	O
#OnPoli	O

Elections	B-ORG
Ontario	I-ORG
going	O
after	O
handful	O
of	O
voters	O
who	O
post	O
photos	O
of	O
their	O
ballots	O
http://t.co/DKR5yRRF3x	O

#Target	B-ORG
execs	O
take	O
another	O
run	O
at	O
the	O
Canadian	O
marketplace	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
mindset	O
(	O
via	O
@dj_friend	O
)	O
http://t.co/gU7WQGS5zO	O
#retail	O

#CareerDirection:	O
The	O
importance	O
of	O
a	O
flexible	O
workplace	O
with	O
Jennifer	B-PER
Reynolds	I-PER
of	O
@	B-ORG
WCMCanada	B-ORG
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/oDQaPvQfAg	O

Prominent	O
Canadian	O
lawyer	O
,	O
businessman	O
Purdy	B-PER
Crawford	I-PER
dies	O
at	O
age	O
82	O
.	O
The	O
story	O
:	O
http://t.co/OM6zyQS2fI	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Veteran	O
Canadian	O
businessman	O
and	O
Bay	B-LOC
Street	I-LOC
lawyer	O
Purdy	B-PER
Crawford	I-PER
has	O
died	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
law	O
firm	O
says	O
.	O

Statistics	B-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
to	O
re-release	O
July	O
jobs	O
report	O
on	O
Friday	O
to	O
fix	O
unspecified	O
calculation	O
error	O
.	O

How	O
to	O
spot	O
a	O
Ponzi	B-PER
or	O
pyramid	O
scheme	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
with	O
@	B-PER
RossMarowits	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/FCNuDXih5e	O

Here	O
's	O
one	O
area	O
where	O
Canadians	O
are	O
doing	O
better	O
since	O
the	O
recession	O
.	O
.	O
.	O
http://t.co/2mVle2lXXC	O
#economy	O
#networth	O

Canada	B-LOC
added	O
200	O
jobs	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
Statistics	B-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
says	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
http://t.co/xOXfhSk1Vv	O

.	O
@	B-ORG
AirCanada	B-ORG
reported	O
the	O
most	O
profitable	O
quarter	O
in	O
its	O
history	O
today	O
.	O
The	O
details	O
via	O
@	B-PER
RossMarowits	B-PER
:	O
http://t.co/hSA4i1WTKr	O

#BCE's	B-ORG
second-quarter	O
profits	O
get	O
a	O
boost	O
from	O
customers	O
upgrading	O
their	O
wireless	O
subscriptions	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
maurinor	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/jjMyZCvriK	O

#Manulife	B-ORG
raises	O
its	O
dividend	O
for	O
first	O
time	O
in	O
five	O
years	O
as	O
profits	O
more	O
than	O
triple	O
http://t.co/GyPLqXIXIW	O

#Dorel	B-ORG
profits	O
grow	O
nearly	O
15	O
per	O
cent	O
in	O
Q	O
2	O
on	O
strong	O
#bicycle	O
sales	O
http://t.co/q1bElsDxgP	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
RossMarowits	B-PER
)	O

Athabasca	B-ORG
,	O
PetroChina	B-ORG
agree	O
on	O
path	O
to	O
closing	O
Dover	B-LOC
#oilsands	O
sale	O
http://t.co/SY4hs6ekVK	O
(	O
via	O
oil	O
and	O
gas	O
reporter	O
@	B-PER
LaurenKrugel	B-PER
)	O

UPDATED	O
-	O
@	B-ORG
CineplexMovies	B-ORG
hurt	O
by	O
box-office	O
doldrums	O
http://t.co/8u9EdQ1Y4C	O
#movies	O
#boxoffice	O
(	O
via	O
@dj_friend	O
)	O

Want	O
a	O
job	O
?	O
Study	O
nursing	O
or	O
pharmacy	O
,	O
says	O
@	B-ORG
Workopolis	B-ORG
study	O
http://t.co/NbN6FbByNZ	O
#career	O
#jobs	O
#healthcare	O

.	O
@	B-ORG
TimHortons	B-ORG
raises	O
outlook	O
,	O
as	O
customers	O
spend	O
more	O
at	O
#breakfast	O
and	O
#lunch	O
http://t.co/3CUmqD2DaV	O
#coffee	O
#doughnut	O

#CareerDirection:	O
When	O
do	O
you	O
teach	O
your	O
kids	O
computer	O
code	O
?	O
@	B-PER
heatherpayne	B-PER
weighs	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
discussion	O
.	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/sdPHaZo4ta	O

Will	O
free	O
shipping	O
become	O
the	O
new	O
normal	O
with	O
retailers	O
in	O
Canada	B-LOC
?	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
LindaNguyenTO	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/Und1lKpzTI	O
#retail	O
#Walmart	B-ORG

#OnTheJob	O
with	O
floral	O
designer	O
@	B-PER
MacKayNeville	B-PER
,	O
who	O
has	O
arranged	O
for	O
the	O
#Queen	B-PER
and	O
#EltonJohn	B-PER
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/Xt2McvXx9V	O

#BlackBerry	B-ORG
beefs	O
up	O
its	O
security	O
assets	O
with	O
anti-eavesdropping	O
firm	O
Secusmart	B-ORG
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
dj_friend	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/s10mCCAQuK	O
#cdntech	O

Stock	O
markets	O
reporter	O
Malcolm	B-PER
Morrison	I-PER
outlines	O
what	O
to	O
watch	O
out	O
for	O
this	O
week	O
.	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/cKz2f3uT5U	O
#TSX	O
#Nasdaq	B-ORG
#NYSE	O

Tech	O
sector	O
still	O
struggles	O
with	O
recruiting	O
#women	O
http://t.co/VZUMHqE0Bt	O
#tech	O
#business	O
(	O
with	O
comment	O
from	O
@	B-ORG
googlecanada	B-ORG
@	B-ORG
SAP	B-ORG
@	B-ORG
CanWIT	B-ORG
)	O

What	O
it	O
's	O
like	O
being	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
tech	O
sector	O
via	O
@	B-PER
heatherpayne	B-PER
@	B-PER
llcodedotcom	B-PER
http://t.co/kw0P5O4EaB	O
#tech	O
#women	O
#coding	O
#CareerDirection	O

Food	O
,	O
gasoline	O
prices	O
rise	O
as	O
annual	O
#inflation	O
increases	O
to	O
2	O
.	O
4	O
%	O
in	O
June	O
http://t.co/6FvcptBGdk	O
#cdnpoli	O
#cdnbiz	O
#cpi	O

Would	O
you	O
drink	O
#TimHortons	B-ORG
coffee-flavoured	O
beer	O
?	O
Our	O
video	O
dept	O
asked	O
some	O
Canadians	O
:	O
http://t.co/8xZDRAGEbs	O

Disney	B-ORG
titles	O
coming	O
to	O
#Netflix	B-ORG
Canada	B-LOC
starting	O
next	O
year	O
.	O
http://t.co/1Y6hhY5KB2	O
#movies	O
#TV	O

Shares	O
of	O
#BlackBerry	B-ORG
drop	O
after	O
Apple	B-ORG
,	O
IBM	B-ORG
announce	O
business	O
app	O
partnership	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
dj_friend	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/coH8HPLAeQ	O
#cdntech	O

Real	O
minimum	O
wage	O
has	O
n't	O
increased	O
in	O
nearly	O
40	O
years	O
,	O
say	O
Statistics	B-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
.	O
http://t.co/h7zp5LaX2W	O
#economy	O

The	B-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
says	O
the	O
#economy	O
is	O
not	O
doing	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
expected	O
.	O
The	O
story	O
:	O
http://t.co/LnRTiPkm45	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Bank	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
keeps	O
its	O
trendsetting	O
overnight	O
interest	O
rate	O
at	O
one	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O

BREAKING	O
:	O
Barrick	B-ORG
Gold	I-ORG
Corp	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
says	O
president	O
and	O
CEO	O
Jamie	B-PER
Sokalsky	I-PER
will	O
step	O
down	O
on	O
Sept	O
.	O
15	O
.	O

#Bell	B-ORG
and	O
#Rogers	B-ORG
plan	O
to	O
shut	O
down	O
Viewer	O
's	O
Choice	O
pay-per-view	O
(	O
via	O
@dj_friend	O
)	O
http://t.co/5SpKSPrPmD	O
#media	O

Developing	O
an	O
online	O
brand	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
land	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
A	O
look	O
at	O
how	O
to	O
build	O
your	O
career	O
from	O
reporter	O
@	B-PER
maurinor	B-PER
.	O
http://t.co/fFdMarXzQz	O

Women	B-ORG
in	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
CEO	O
@	B-PER
JenReynolds__	B-PER
talks	O
about	O
the	O
characteristics	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
leader	O
.	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/V3JOQgFNwa	O

#Lionsgate	B-ORG
pairs	O
with	O
e-commerce	O
giant	O
#Alibaba	B-ORG
for	O
streaming	O
movie	O
service	O
in	O
China	B-LOC
(	O
via	O
@dj_friend	O
)	O
http://t.co/ktjT4wvjZa	O

Fitch	B-ORG
Ratings	I-ORG
says	O
Canada	B-LOC
's	O
real	O
estate	O
market	O
is	O
overvalued	O
by	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
20	O
%	O
http://t.co/p9pZwIc9YX	O
#realestate	O

Would	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
cost	O
of	O
a	O
basic	O
cellphone	O
package	O
in	O
Canada	B-LOC
rose	O
this	O
much	O
since	O
last	O
year	O
?	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
DavidPaddon	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/75rBnYM7g4	O

Follow	O
our	O
team	O
of	O
business	O
reporters	O
:	O
@dj_friend	O
,	O
@	B-PER
LindaNguyenTO	B-PER
,	O
@	B-PER
maurinor	B-PER
,	O
@	B-PER
RossMarowits	B-PER
,	O
@	B-PER
LaurenKrugel	B-PER
,	O
@	B-PER
DavidPaddon	B-PER

#Bombardier	B-ORG
unveils	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
C	O
Series	O
orders	O
as	O
airshow	O
gets	O
underway	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
RossMarowits	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/cXpgwNUL4Y	O

AMOLED	O
or	O
LCD	O
?	O
Reporter	O
@	B-PER
michaeloliveira	B-PER
takes	O
a	O
closer	O
look	O
at	O
mobile	O
screen	O
displays	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/z7wAGELbac	O
#cdntech	O

Reporter	O
Malcolm	B-PER
Morrison	I-PER
looks	O
at	O
what	O
to	O
expect	O
on	O
stock	O
markets	O
this	O
week	O
,	O
including	O
Bank	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
rates	O
(	O
VIDEO	O
)	O
http://t.co/t4bYS8ejvj	O

Worried	O
about	O
getting	O
a	O
mortgage	O
?	O
Here	O
are	O
a	O
few	O
tips	O
before	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
move	O
.	O
(	O
via	O
@maurinor	O
)	O
http://t.co/9na3AMRG5E	O
#MoneyMonitor	O

#Canada's	B-LOC
unemployment	O
rate	O
rises	O
to	O
7	O
.	O
1	O
%	O
as	O
Ontario	B-LOC
hit	O
by	O
significant	O
job	O
losses	O
http://t.co/0s5aVCQsyS	O
#economy	O

Analysts	O
say	O
that	O
Canadian	O
women	O
's	O
clothing	O
retailers	O
are	O
headed	O
for	O
a	O
tough	O
year	O
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
RossMarowits	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/68XeYaYeOF	O

Unionized	O
workers	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Mail	I-ORG
vote	O
to	O
approve	O
new	O
contract	O
http://t.co/UvG1yHRwgA	O
#media	O

#Cogeco	B-PER
is	O
abandoning	O
its	O
IPTV	B-ORG
project	O
and	O
will	O
turn	O
to	O
a	O
partnership	O
with	O
#TiVo	B-PER
(	O
via	O
@	B-PER
DavidPaddon	B-PER
)	O
http://t.co/PZXrqF2zA3	O
#telecom	O
